Chapter 1303 – Clash of Dragon and Phoenix

On the arena stage, the auras of the two people were extremely powerful. On one side was Lin Ming, his aura swift and fierce, piercing through all. On the other side was Xiao Moxian, her aura like a blazing inferno, scorching down the skies.

At this time, Xiao Moxian suddenly attacked. She slashed her whip, and with a howling sound, the space around her seemed to be cut down. Even if a mountain were placed in front of her, that mountain would be shattered by her whip!

A soft whip was an extremely difficult weapon to create and also an extremely difficult type of weapon to train in. However, once one mastered it, its trajectory was easily changeable and very difficult to defend against!

Lin Ming swept out his spear. A swift and powerful spear light met this whip, and with a crackling explosion, the whip light and spear light struck each other, producing a sound like rolling thunder.

Within Xiao Moxian’s pupils, black flames suddenly shimmered. Her entire body was enveloped in roiling black flames as her speed rose to a dramatic new level!

A Dark Phoenix was a divine bird of the skies; its speed was not any worse than a Golden-winged Roc’s.

“Hahahahaha!” Xiao Moxian happily chuckled. “When I have fought other juniors of my generation, none of them have been able to keep up with my speed. If you can’t keep up with me, there’s no way for you to fight me!”

Xiao Moxian’s voice was like the clarion cry of a phoenix. As she spoke, she pumped her whip at Lin Ming. This whip transformed into 10,000 whip shadows in the air, filling the skies, completely covering Lin Ming!

Whether it was in attack speed or her movement speed, Xiao Moxian was unparalleled. She could only be called a young girl that was blessed by the heavens themselves. In the aspect of talent, no one was able to keep up with her!

Golden Roc Shattering the Void! Mystic Lightning Shade!

Lin Ming revolved two movement techniques at the same time. Even as he did so, he also opened the Gate of Wonder, erupting with his highest level of speed.

Woosh woosh woosh!

Lin Ming instantly avoided hundreds of whip shadows. His speed was extremely fast, forming dozens of afterimages as he soared through the air.

However, there were simply far too many whip shadows and they were far too fast. Just as his afterimages formed, they were nearly instantly slashed apart by these whip shadows, turning into nothing!

Even if Lin Ming’s movements were nimble and agile and he was able to avoid more and more whip shadows, he was eventually being corralled into a dead end!

“Lin Ming’s movement martial skills are too low level!”

In the honored seating section, an old World King suddenly spoke out. At their cultivation, besides judging transcendent divine mights, they could determine how weak or strong other cultivation methods were.

“That is a problem of inheritance. Lin Ming’s background has placed tremendous limits on him! Otherwise, having an Empyrean level movement technique is the most basic foundation of all.”

Golden Roc Shattering the Void and Mystic Lightning Shade were not martial skills created by an Empyrean. Within the lower realms, these skills were certainly enough to shock and awe everyone, but in the Divine Realm, these skills seemed quite shabby when compared to those of geniuses from Empyrean influences.

If it weren’t for Lin Ming supporting everything with the Gate of Wonder and forcefully upping his movement speed, then these whip shadows might have immediately defeated him.

“I’ll force you into a dead end and see just what you’ll do then.”

Xiao Moxian grinned. At this moment, Lin Ming was covered with endless whip shadows with nowhere else to go.

“Prime Emperor Lotus Flower – grandmist space!”

Behind Lin Ming, the phantom of an Azure Dragon suddenly appeared and a blood red lotus slowly bloomed. The vast and boundless grandmist space erupted, surging outwards, swallowing up all the whip shadows!

Pa pa pa pa!

A terrifying explosive sound filled the air. Many of the whip shadows that were swallowed up by the grandmist space blew up. However, Xiao Moxian’s attacks were too violent and fierce. A great deal of origin energy still penetrated through the grandmist space and drilled through Lin Ming’s protective true essence.

With a crackling sound, Lin Ming’s protective true essence issued a series of bursting sounds. Power broke into his body, causing wanton chaos!

“Gate of View!”

Lin Ming opened the Gate of View and simultaneously activated the power of the dragon bone. His defensive abilities suddenly rose to a dramatic new level. Never ending world power erupted from Lin Ming’s inner world, forcefully suppressing the chaotic true essence within him.

Hu -!

Lin Ming fell onto the arena, his face flushed red as blood tumbled in his body. Xiao Moxian’s speed was indeed terrifying. Her attacks were tricky and swift, just like a deadly viper.

“Eh? You blocked it?”

Xiao Moxian’s eyes flashed with a bit of surprise. “Your domain is really amazing. It was actually able to swallow up my attacks… it seems that my striking power was insufficient just now. But that was only once. Now I will be serious. I advise you to show me your complete strength, otherwise you’re going to lose in an extremely ugly fashion!”

As Xiao Moxian spoke, she spread out her arms. In that instant, for several hundred miles all around, all of the power of fire gathered to her, forming a massive origin energy vortex. Her aura climbed up without stopping and behind her the shade of a Dark Phoenix began to gradually form. This didn’t look like a phantom, but was vivid and real, just like a true Dark Phoenix!

As this Dark Phoenix appeared, the pressure of a God Beast fell onto the entire audience!

The Dark Phoenix faced the heavens and released a long cry. Its voice pierced through the clouds and cracked apart mountains.

Suddenly, behind Xiao Moxian, a pair of voluminous black wings stretched out!

These wings were large, expanding 15 feet out in each direction. Combined together, they could easily wrap around Xiao Moxian’s small body, completely folding her within them.

These were phoenix wings!

These wings were not transformed from energy, but were wings of true flesh and blood!

These wings were a part of Xiao Moxian’s body; they were the symbol of a phoenix’s true descendant!

With a gentle flap of her wings, Xiao Moxian rose into the air. At this time, she was like a dark angel, mysterious and beautiful, but also containing a terrifying power.

“Let me caution you. When I reveal my Dark Phoenix wings, that is when my attacks can display their highest level of power! Moreover, my mortal body defense is extremely strong. A normal attack cannot break through my defense!”

Xiao Moxian tittered. This was the powerful body she inherited from her mother. Even if she didn’t cultivate, her bodily strength would far surpass that of almost all body transformation martial artists.

As the audience looked at the flying Xiao Moxian, they were completely stunned. After transforming, Xiao Moxian with her Dark Phoenix wings was like a goddess of night. Her atmosphere and strength were as different as night and day from before. Her entire body exuded a sacred aura.

“How terrifying! This is the descendant of a God Beast and a person! In the entire Divine Realm, that is a miracle of life that might not appear in a hundred million years. Her strength is mind-boggling!”

“It’s more than just a hundred million years. I fear that in these last 3.6 billion years, the number of monstrous geniuses like Xiao Moxian can be countered on a single hand! It might be possible that she is unique, the only one to have existed!”

The child of a human and a God Beast might have appeared somewhere along the river of history. But, 3.6 billion years was simply far too long a span of time. No one was able to trace back this entire span of time and determine if there were such precedents in ancient times.

“We have underestimated Xiao Moxian’s strength! I thought that she would be the weakest among the three top Empyrean descendants because she was limited by her age. But now, it seems that might not be true. Don’t forget, she still hasn’t used her Heaven Absorbing Demon Art or the power of her nearly sixth level Laws!”

“Lin Ming might lose this battle.”

“It’s not a shame even if he loses. Lin Ming is already extremely good. For him to reach this step even though he comes from a mere peak Holy Land and also has a humble mortal background, that in itself is enough for him to be proud of.”

Within the raging winds, Lin Ming stood tall upon the arena stage. His body was straight and tall, just like a spear.

As he saw Xiao Moxian unleash her Dark Phoenix wings, he knew that this would be a grueling battle. Xiao Moxian was absolutely not an opponent he could defeat in one move, because her defensive capabilities were also phenomenal.

Roar!

Behind Lin Ming, the Azure Dragon phantom appeared once more. The power of the dragon bone revolved to the limit. Dragon and Phoenix, two extreme geniuses clashing together!

“You have absorbed the blood of the Azure Dragon, right? Interesting. However, your bloodline density will never compare to mine!” Xiao Moxian laughed, her words coming from her absolute confidence. Amongst humanity, any genius’ bloodline was nothing to her!

“Take this!”

Xiao Moxian’s arms flashed. She hurtled forwards even as she slashed her whip at Lin Ming!

This whip strike was several times stronger than the one before. The tail of the whip was also alight with black flames. Xiao Moxian was using her Laws in this attack! After transforming into her phoenix form, even her Fire Laws had become incomparably fierce and wild!

Heretical God Tree!

Lin Ming didn’t hold back. He poured all of his strength into his inner world and summoned the phantom of the Heretical God Tree. The Heretical God Force opened to the limit. As he thrust out his spear, a towering blue lotus smashed into that brutal black whip!

To use the Heretical God Tree to suppress Xiao Moxian’s Darkfire Laws!

In that moment, the entire Heretical God Tree seemed to shine with a flaming light. In the skies, the phantoms of the Azure Dragon and Dark Phoenix crashed together, violently struggling!

Chapter 1306 – Might Of The Concept Of The 33 Layered Heavens

The three types of energies were like three massive seals, forcefully stabilizing Lin Ming’s inner world. No matter what sort of fierce or violent waves the Heaven Absorbing Demon Art stirred up, his inner world remained unshaken.

For this situation to occur was also because of the difference in the heights of the Laws.

The Heaven Absorbing Demon Art, no matter how high level it was, was still a cultivation method of the essence gathering system. What it absorbed was true essence.

But within Lin Ming’s inner world, true essence, spirit essence, and astral essence had fused together, turning into the Laws of the 33 Layered Heavens’ power of divinity, and surpassing the boundary of true essence. Because of this, the Heaven Absorbing Demon Art was unable to absorb it.

“Mm!?”

Within the black vortex, Xiao Moxian was startled. Facing Lin Ming, another strange situation had occurred!

“How could you be immune to my Heaven Absorbing Demon Art!?”

Xiao Moxian couldn’t understand what was happening. Even if a Divine Lord realm powerhouse were standing in front of her, even they couldn’t say that they wouldn’t be affected by her Heaven Absorbing Demon Art.

After seeing her own Heaven Absorbing Demon Art fail so suddenly, Xiao Moxian wanted to change techniques, but Lin Ming was already rushing towards her!

“Three Essences As One!”

Spirit essence, true essence, and astral essence fused together. Lin Ming thrust out his spear, pouring all of his power into it. Besides Heavenly Dao Judgment, Three Essences As One was also one of his strongest techniques.

On the Divine Seal Altar’s 33rd step, Lin Ming had once displayed this ability to resist the tribulation of dao tablets 80,000 feet up, and relied on this to overcome it. As for Dragon Fang, who had also been climbing up the Divine Seal Altar, he had been defeated by the tribulation of dao tablets.

And now, Lin Ming wasn’t just using Three Essences As One, but also fusing in the power of thunder and fire heavenly tribulation!

This was nearly equal to using the power of divinity as the foundation to stimulate Heavenly Dao Judgment!

In that instant, behind Lin Ming, the towering Heretical God Tree shimmered into existence.

Within Lin Ming’s body, deeply buried in his flesh and blood, inner world, and soul, the Law runes of the 33 Layered Heavens began to emit a brilliant light!

All around Lin Ming, the phantoms of the 33 Heavenly Dao stone tablets appeared!

Deep within Vast Universe Heavenly Palace, as Empyrean Vast Universe saw these phantoms, he was immensely surprised.

These 33 stone tablets were the great tribulation that existed 80,000 feet up the Divine Seal Altar’s 33rd step! Lin Ming’s technique was actually able to show a faint charm of the dao tablet tribulation!

This was a phenomenon that appeared in Lin Ming’s technique after he comprehended the Concept of the 33 Layered Heavens.

The Concept of the 33 Layered Heavens was not some useless comprehension. It would enhance Lin Ming’s Laws and combat ability, and as time passed, this enhancement would become increasingly potent.

This was also the true capital that Lin Ming possessed to resist these extreme talents of the Divine Realm.

As Xiao Moxian saw the Heaven Absorbing Demon Art fail and Lin Ming hurtle towards her, she immediately reversed her true essence. Behind her, the black vortex began to spin in reverse.

“Counterforce – Heaven Absorbing Demon Art!”

The Heaven Absorbing Demon Art was able to swallow energy; it could naturally emit energy too.

Counterforce Heaven Absorbing Demon Art – that was to release the energy held within Xiao Moxian’s body and use it to exterminate the enemy!

The massive black vortex began to compress, shrinking down.

That swirling black vortex fell into Xiao Moxian’s hand, and then was shot out by her!

It formed a dao diagram, colliding with Lin Ming’s Three Essences As One!

In that moment, a terrifyingly bright light shot out into the heavens, covering the world!

Bang!

Lin Ming’s arms shook and his palms cracked apart. As the Phoenix Blood Spear struck the Heaven Absorbing Demon Art dao diagram, it bent into a crescent moon. The phantoms of the 33 dao tablets along with the power of thunder and fire crashed down.

Ka ka ka!

Cracks began to appear all over the Heaven Absorbing Demon Art! Then, it completely collapsed!

“What!?”

Xiao Moxian’s beautiful expression changed colors. She cried out in alarm. Her Counterforce Heaven Absorbing Demon Art had actually been broken!

In this crucial moment, Xiao Moxian closed up her wings once more, forcefully withstanding Lin Ming’s attack!

Peng!

Xiao Moxian was sent flying back once more. This time, her wings were nearly pierced through by the spear light. Her body crashed into the ground as countless stones were sent flying away.

The terrifying energy gradually subsided.

Lin Ming spat out a mouthful of blood. His right arm had been fractured and his chest was also covered with blood!

These were injuries created by the impact and shaking force from resisting the Heaven Absorbing Demon Art.

Xiao Moxian’s great strength has completely surpassed Lin Ming’s imagination. He originally thought that even though he might not take first place, he should still be able to advance into the top three rankings. But, if he had known that Xiao Moxian was so strong beforehand then he wouldn’t have thought such.

As the dust settled and wild energy dissipated, Lin Ming fell onto the ground, supporting himself with the Phoenix Blood Spear. His organs were broken in many places and he was heavily wounded.

As the audience saw the result of this battle, they didn’t know what words to say to express their feelings.

This was an unbelievable battle in which both parties were ridiculously strong.

“Junior-apprentice Sister Xiao Moxian has grown far too fast. I haven’t seen her in just a year and this is where she is at. Her talent is truly frightening.”

In the contestant waiting area, White King sighed with emotion. He and Xiao Moxian could be considered friends. Just a year ago, Xiao Moxian was only at the early Divine Sea realm. At that time, he didn’t think that Xiao Moxian was much stronger than he was.

Now after a year passed, White King had made some progress, but Xiao Moxian had leapt into the skies, reaching unimaginable levels.

If she had several more years to grow, just what would happen then?

And what was even more frightening was Lin Ming. In this battle he had resorted to several trump cards and had forcefully suppressed Xiao Moxian. This was a truly hard fought victory! With his mortal body and middle Divine Sea realm cultivation, he had defeated Xiao Moxian with her God Beast bloodline. That was a truly incredible feat!

“For him to climb up the Divine Seal Altar’s 33 steps is truly extraordinary. His techniques have the Concept of the Divine Seal Altar’s 33 steps integrated into them. It’s hard to imagine just what boundary his Laws have reached.”

As White King was thinking, Xiao Moxian rose up from the deep pit she had crashed into once more.

But now, her black wings were covered with blood and the wing bones had been pierced through by a spear light. Her beautiful face was also wan, making one feel as if she were feeble and sick.

“She still hasn’t fallen…”

Lin Ming’s eyelids jumped up. His current state was extremely poor. He had fused together true essence, astral essence, and spirit essence, utilizing Three Essences As One and also using the power of heavenly tribulation. Just then he had surpassed the limits of his body. That strike was his extreme peak, and his soul, body, and inner world found themselves hard-pressed to withstand the burden. All of his blood vitality was in chaos; it would be impossible for him to fight like that again.

But even so, he hadn’t managed to thoroughly defeat Xiao Moxian. One could see just how formidable the body of a God Beast was from this!

“I originally thought that Xiao Moxian’s bodily defensive abilities were about the same as mine, but now it seems that those wings of hers far surpass my defensive capabilities.”

As Lin Ming was thinking this, Xiao Moxian suddenly spat out a mouthful of blood. The wings on her back began to slowly fold in and contract, and the runes on her body also began to fade away.

After several breaths of time, Xiao Moxian completely resumed her human form. She was nearly unable to stand steadily. It was impossible for her to continue maintaining her true phoenix form.

Lin Ming couldn’t burn his blood essence forever, and Xiao Moxian also couldn’t display her phoenix true form in perpetuity. At least, this was her limit before she experienced her first nirvana rebirth and heavenly tribulation.

“You…”

Xiao Moxian ground her teeth together. Her condition was worse than Lin Ming’s and she wasn’t able to use her phoenix true form right now. She was nearly like a delicate woman, extremely weak. However, her hand still held the Dragon Tendon Whip; she clearly wasn’t willing to concede.

“That’s enough, Little Sister, you’ve lost.”

At this time, a light voice echoed out. Fairy Frost Dream was like a goddess falling from the highest heavens as she floated down to the stage. As she arrived, all of the raging waves of heat and flame, and even the Fire Laws completely retreated, as if they were blown away by a winter breeze.

Fairy Frost Dream lightly stepped forwards as if she were walking on lotuses until she stopped beside Xiao Moxian, gently helping her up. Then, she looked at Lin Ming, her eyes pausing on him for several breaths of time. She said in a low voice, “You’re very special.”

Her simple words contained an intriguing meaning.

This battle –

Xiao Moxian, defeated! Lin Ming, victorious!

The audience still hadn’t regained their composure. They were all shocked, as if they were watching a dream.

“Lin Ming actually won… how much longer will he continue winning for?”

“I really have no idea. But, in this battle, he’s used everything he has.”

“At a similar boundary he defeated Xiao Moxian with her God Beast body. Even a young Empyrean isn’t enough to describe him.

A young Empyrean was the most glorious title to describe young geniuses in the Divine Realm. And in this First Martial Meeting, there were actually six people that were worthy of such a name.

But if words were used to describe Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian, young Empyrean was clearly not enough.

Chapter 1307A – White Hot

“This boy Lin Ming…”

Deep within Vast Universe Heavenly Palace, Empyrean Vast Universe gazed at Lin Ming for a long time. Lin Ming had created a miracle by climbing up the 33 steps of the Divine Seal Altar, and through this he knew that Lin Ming must have experienced some sort of special lucky chance that allowed him to come into contact with the Concept of the 33 Layered Heavens ahead of time.

Moreover, although the Concept of the 33 Layered Heavens was related to Empyrean Divine Seal and its might was unimaginable, it was still an ancient Concept, one that belonged to a different era. Beyond that, the inheritances of the Concept of the 33 Layered Heavens had already been cut off. It was unknown whether or not Lin Ming would be able to display its power in the future.

On just this point alone, it was impossible to place Lin Ming on par with Xiao Moxian, Frost Dream, and others of their level.

But just now in his moves, Lin Ming had actually reformed the phantoms of the dao tablets from the Divine Seal Altar’s 33rd step, ultimately overcoming all obstacles to defeat Xiao Moxian. How could Empyrean Vast Universe not be startled by this.

At the same boundary, he was able to suppress someone with the body of a God Beast; that was far too shocking!

“I really have no idea just what achievements Lin Ming will have in the future!” Empyrean Vast Universe muttered to himself.

And at this time, from beside him, Empyrean Divine Dream dimly said, “3.6 billion years, a single samsara. 3.6 billion years ago, a peerless powerhouse appeared within the Divine Realm who managed to surpass the boundaries of an Empyrean. And perhaps now, that cycle will continue once more…”

“What?” Empyrean Vast Universe turned his head and looked at Empyrean Divine Dream with incredulity sketched on his face. “Are you saying that Lin Ming has the possibility of surpassing the realm of an Empyrean!?”

To Empyrean Vast Universe, an Empyrean was an existence near the peak of martial arts. Although he also knew that the legends said there existed a boundary above an Empyrean, legends were only legends. When Xiao Moxian declared she would surpass an Empyrean in the future, Vast Universe hadn’t taken her seriously.

To surpass an Empyrean… wasn’t that easier said than done!?

And now, Empyrean Divine Dream actually spoke these words, causing him to pause. He knew that with Divine Dream’s character, she would never speak nonsense or needless words. Moreover, she was an incomparably mysterious character with a foresight far higher than all others’. Her cultivation had also reached a realm that he was unable to comprehend.

In fact, even if Empyrean Vast Universe learnt that Empyrean Divine Dream had seen the road that lay beyond an Empyrean, he would not be amazed, just a bit shocked.

Empyrean Divine Dream said, “For someone to surpass an Empyrean, that is not only a question of destiny or talent. There also needs to be an era created just for them. Now, this fated era approaches, and there indeed may be extreme characters that are born who possess the possibility of doing so, but whether or not that person who surpasses an Empyrean will be Lin Ming is still unknown. It can only be said that he has a minor chance to do so.

“There is Xiao Moxian and Frost Dream…

“Xiao Moxian also has a small chance. As for Frost Dream, she has her own road, a road that is lonely and separate from all else. Besides me and her, no one can speculate or interfere with her future.”

“Mm?” Empyrean Vast Universe froze for a moment. Was there something special about Frost Dream’s background or life experiences?

He wanted to ask, but he could tell that Divine Dream wasn’t about to speak any further on this topic. He could only suppress the questions in his heart.

At this time, in the massive tournament arena, the hundreds of millions of spectators were all cheering and busily discussing as before. Waves upon waves of excited shouts echoed through the air, not calming down for an extremely long time!

Even though many people had lost a great deal of violet sun crystals because of Lin Ming, most of them were still filled with praise towards him. In truth, for the heroic young elites that were able to attend these finals, a few hundred million in wealth was a number they could easily afford.

Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian’s battle was far too shocking. What happened had far exceeded their understandings and imaginations!

Moreover, to those martial artists that were able to watch the battle, this was a lucky chance!

Let alone normal juniors or young elites of sects, even Holy Lord powerhouses or half-step World King masters were able to obtain some inspirations!

This was not an exaggeration. Holy Lord powerhouses and ordinary World Kings possessed a cultivation and strength that far exceeded Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian. But in terms of the heights of Laws, they only studied common Laws that were subordinate the rule of the Heavenly Dao.

As for Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian, Lin Ming had a self-created elementary transcendent divine might and had also comprehended the Concept of the 33 Layered Heavens. He was able to manifest the Heretical God Tree and release dual thunder and fire tribulations. Lin Ming’s moves possessed the charm of the Heavenly Dao! It wasn’t too excessive to call Lin Ming a weaker and younger version of an Empyrean.

As for Xiao Moxian, there was even less to say. Once a God Beast grew up, that would be the same level existence as an Empyrean. Xiao Moxian’s phoenix true flames also possessed the charm of an Empyrean.

The two both cultivated the Fire Laws, but the Fire Laws they used were able to reach heights that ordinary Space Laws and Time Laws couldn’t match.

For the heroic young elites spectating their battle, this level of Laws was nearly impossible for them to understand. One needed to be a Divine Lord, Holy Lord, or half-step World King to see the power within their moves and obtain comprehensions from them.

In a battle between two middle Divine Sea martial artists, even a Holy Lord had to study their moves. Just how amazing was that!

For Lin Ming to win this battle was truly mind-boggling. He had stepped into the highest ranks of all junior geniuses. He had surpassed Dragon Fang and was able to compete with the likes of Frost Dream.

The match had already ended, but Xiao Moxian still stood on the arena stage, grasping the Dragon Tendon Whip. She didn’t seem to be leaving just yet.

“Lin Ming, I admit that I lost this fight, but I won’t give up here nor am I convinced. Half a year from now, I wish to fight with you again!”

Xiao Moxian bit down with her little jade-like tiger canines, clenching her fists tightly. She was someone who was proud at heart. This was the first time she had ever lost to someone at her own boundary!

Of course she couldn’t accept this!

“Half a year…”

Lin Ming’s eyebrows flew up. Half a year, that was enough time for Xiao Moxian’s strength to grow to an even greater degree. And, most importantly, it was said that Xiao Moxian’s natural temperament was that of a playful girl who loved to mess around all the time. She possessed a childlike innocence, completely disparate from someone like Hang Chi who trained diligently. If she was frustrated because of this loss and decided to try her best to catch up, then half a year from now, it would be difficult to estimate just how strong she would grow.

And, if her phoenix divine body were to experience its first nirvana, then that would be even more unimaginable.

Even Lin Ming could feel the pressure!

Xiao Moxian’s declaration was even far more compelling than Dragon Fang’s.

“I will wait for you.”

Lin Ming slowly and clearly said. His current talent was indeed lacking. The reason he defeated Xiao Moxian now was due to his superiority in age; this was not the victory Lin Ming wished for. If he couldn’t suppress Xiao Moxian at the same age, then how could he possibly reach the peak of all martial arts?

Only if their ages were closer together and they were also at the same boundary would Lin Ming truly have won after defeating Xiao Moxian.

This fantastical match had come to a conclusion. Vast Universe Heavenly Palace had also earned a great profit – most people had bet on Xiao Moxian to win.

At this time, Vast Cosmos stepped onto the arena stage, loudly announcing, “To all those here, after the referees have discussed this matter, in order to save time and increase the excitement of the tournament, the 10 individuals in the finals will be further split into two groups. The first group will have six people and the second group will have four people. Those from the first and second groups will no longer battle each other.”

“The first six placings in the tournament will be decided through continued round robin matches between the six people in the first group. Seventh through tenth place will be decided by the four people in the second group. At the end, the highest ranked individual of the second group may challenge the lowest ranked individual of the first group. The winner will either stay or move to the first group and will take sixth place!”

As Vast Cosmos spoke, the audience paused for a moment. Dividing into groups?

“The first group of six people are the default choices for the final top six rankings of the tournament. I wonder just who they are?”

“There’s no need to ask. It’s clear that the finalists have already diverged into two groups themselves. The strong are ridiculously strong and the weak have too great a gap separating them. Although the first place of the second group has the qualifications to challenge the last place of the first group, the chances are that they will lose. It’s simply a formality, there’s no need to think about it!”

“Well… fighting like this is better. We can get straight to the interesting matches and won’t have to face situations where the outcome is already evident at the start. But as it stands, this means the tournament has entered the white hot heated stage. Every battle will be a strong collision!”

Vast Cosmos’s decision gained the approval and satisfaction of many in the audience. Like this, the tournament would be much more compact and wouldn’t be needlessly dragged out.

“Now I will announce the names of the six individuals in the first group. The six people in the first group are – Frost Dream! Hang Chi! Xiao Moxian! Lin Ming! Jun Bluemoon! Dragon Fang!”

“Then, for the names of the four individuals in the second group. The four people in the second group are – Lord Monster, White King, Shiku, and Hua Xuan.”

These two lists were well within everyone’s expectations. Even though the Monster Prince was incomparably arrogant, he still couldn’t oppose these choices. He could only clench his fists and grind his teeth together. To him, this First Martial Meeting was the greatest of all shames!

He couldn’t even enter the first group; he had to fight in the second.

Even if he obtained total victory in the second group he would still be disgraced! After he returned to the monster race, all of his brothers would laugh at him and mock him. Although he had loudly bragged that he would become the Monster Emperor in the future, the truth was that he faced stiff competition from countless strong competitors. His brothers and sisters were all powerful individuals who stood against him. Whether or not he would actually succeed in becoming the Monster Emperor was unknown.

“Xiao Moxian, Lin Ming, you best remember me!”

The Monster Prince shifted all of his hatred onto Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian. It was these two that had miserably beaten him up, shaming him. In particular, Xiao Moxian. She was the one who had absorbed his life’s true essence, leaving him without any face left and even greatly damaging his cultivation.

………

After the groups were announced, there was a six hour break time for contestants to restore their strength.

This was also for Xiao Moxian and Lin Ming to recover. The two of them had consumed the greatest amount of energy.

Six hours later, Vast Cosmos announced the next matches.

Everyone in the audience was bubbling with excitement to hear this!

Of those in the first group, there was not a weak person amongst them. No matter who fought who, it would truly be a battle between two similar opponents, filled with wondrous expectations!

“Honored audience! Now, the matches for the new groupings will soon begin. The first round of matches will be – Frost Dream against Dragon Fang! Lin Ming against Jun Bluemoon! Hang Chi against Xiao Moxian!

“Vast Universe Heavenly Palace has opened a special gambling bet for the match between Hang Chi and Xiao Moxian. Hang Chi’s victory has a compensation rate of 1.6, and Xiao Moxian’s victory has a compensation rate of 2.1.”

In every round of matches, Vast Universe Heavenly Palace would open up a separate gambling bet aimed at the most tense and suspenseful match which would also receive the most attention.

Hang Chi was an extremely low profile and mysterious character. But in his fight with Xiao Moxian, he was sure to reveal his full strength. Everyone would finally be able to see his true abilities. As for Lin Ming against Jun Bluemoon, that would also be a fantastic showdown. Although Lin Ming’s chances were slightly higher, Jun Bluemoon had remained incomparably mysterious this entire time. There was a possibility that there would be an expected winner.

“My match is Jun Bluemoon.”

Lin Ming looked at Jun Bluemoon sitting not too far away in the contestant seating area. He wore all white clothes and held the rust-stained sword in his hands, his hair as white as snow.

Towards an unknown and mysterious opponent, Lin Ming would never underestimate them.

And at this time, Frost Dream and Dragon Fang stepped into the arena. Without a doubt, Frost Dream was powerful. But Dragon Fang wasn’t weak either. Many people were looking forwards to this match, waiting to see just what abilities Frost Dream would display.

Chapter 1311 – Against Hang Chi

The six paths of samsara were an idea of the Buddhist belief. It was reasonable that Lin Ming’s Samsara martial intent originated from the Buddhist belief. When Lin Ming first stepped onto the road of martial arts, the Samsara martial intent had played an extremely important role. However, afterwards, Lin Ming had used it less and less. This was because the Samsara martial intent was unable to follow his rapid rise in strength.

After all, the Sorcerer of the Southern Wilderness was only an ordinary powerhouse of the Divine Realm. The martial arts inheritances they left behind were naturally eliminated.

And now, from Hang Chi, Lin Ming could see an even deeper level of the Samsara martial intent. In fact, it might even be a small portion of this transcendent divine might, the Wheel of Samsara!

If this were true then there was a tremendous amount of space for the Samsara martial intent to improve. Domain type skills were already extremely rare, and the Samsara martial intent was also related in many ways to the soul forging system. If Lin Ming could combine the two together, his soul forging system cultivation could reach a new level.

As Lin Ming was thinking this, on the arena stage, Xiao Moxian and Hang Chi’s battle had already reached a superheated phase.

To use the Samsara Domain to contend against the Heaven Absorbing Demon Art!

In the skies, two massive vortexes tore at each other, energy recklessly surging outwards. The images of a gilded golden Buddha and a dark flaming phoenix appeared, dividing the world, struggling against each other! This fight was even more intense than the battle between Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian!

Xiao Moxian’s Heaven Absorbing Demon Art failed to shake Hang Chi’s foundation in the end.

Not to mention that Hang Chi had the Wheel of Samsara stabilizing his inner world, his thoughts and mind were extremely steadfast and unwavering. His body also had a certain zen aura, making him seem as steady and calm as the endless earth!

His body and his spirit were firm and unyielding, tempered through endless trials, invincible!

Bang!

The vortexes exploded and a crazy amount of energy swept wildly outwards. Xiao Moxian switched her technique yet again.

“Counterforce Heaven Absorbing Demon Art!”

A massive amount of dark energy spewed forth. Hang Chi sat cross-legged in the void, his hands bent up in prayer, as motionless as the world.

This Hang Chi gave off an undefeatable feeling. His foundation was simply too solid. It was hard for an attack to pose a threat to him.

Bang!

The brilliant lights died down. Xiao Moxian paled as she drew back several hundred feet.

She wasn’t injured. From start to finish, Hang Chi had never attacked her. He had only countered Xiao Moxian’s attacks.

Of course, in such an intense collision of attacks, it was inevitable that there would be a backlash.

“I don’t want to fight, I don’t want to fight anymore!” Xiao Moxian released her phoenix true form and pursed her mouth, saying, “If you aren’t going to let me hit you then at least pretend to be injured!”

Hang Chi faintly smiled. He folded his hands together, saying, “Junior-apprentice Sister Xiao Moxian’s moves are simply too strong. This poor monk is older than junior-apprentice sister by 12 years and is just around half over your age. Even so, my strength only barely surpasses yours. If I don’t try my best in battle and pretend to be injured, then I fear that I won’t be able to control it well enough and I will be severely beaten to the point of spitting out blood. I will really have failed then.”

“What a liar. Haven’t you already cultivated your incorruptible diamond Vajra body? How can I possibly wound you with one strike?” Xiao Moxian curled her lips, as if all of this was too funny.

But as the audience heard this exchange, all of them were shocked. Xiao Moxian had just admitted defeat like this.

Although the fight had been intense, the truth was that Hang Chi had maintained the upper hand from the start. It could be said that even though he was going easy on Xiao Moxian, he never used any of his true attack techniques.

Moreover, listening to Xiao Moxian’s meaning, Hang Chi’s defensive capabilities were also terrifying.

That diamond Vajra body must be some sort of secret Buddhist technique.

“I’m speechless. He is too abnormal! His Laws are strong, his body is strong, his foundation is solid, and even his defense is amazing. Just who can defeat him?”

“Even the might of Hang Chi’s attacks are horrible. From beginning to end he never truly attacked Xiao Moxian.”

“Maybe only Frost Dream has a chance of defeating Hang Chi. It’s possible that Hang Chi might not be any worse than Frost Dream!”

“It looks like the first three rankings have already been settled. First and second place should belong to Frost Dream and Hang Chi. As for Lin Ming, he’s third! After that, I think that Xiao Moxian should be forth. As for fifth and sixth place, it will depend on the victor between Dragon Fang and Jun Bluemoon.”

“Hang Chi is 38 years old! While he was cultivating for 38 years, do you really think he just wasted his time? Just look at Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian for instance and imagine what degree they’ll reach once they are 38 years old!”

The First Martial Meeting was not absolutely fair. Age was an extremely influential factor.

“Lin Ming, this Hang Chi is too fierce.”

Mo Eversnow sincerely said from within the Magic Cube space. Besides the unknown factor of Frost Dream, out of all the heroic young elites present, Hang Chi didn’t have the greatest talent but he was the strongest. Even someone as fierce as Xiao Moxian had been suppressed by him!

“I understand… two years from now, Dragon Fang will likely be the same as Hang Chi. If I did not train for two years and fought Dragon Fang again, then I would lose without a doubt.” In terms of talent within this First Martial Meeting, Xiao Moxian was the undisputed number one. Because Lin Ming had displayed the Concept of the 33 Layered Heavens, he had been listed as second. Frost Dream was an unknown, and Hang Chi, Jun Bluemoon, and Dragon Fang all had talent listed around third to sixth place.

Mo Eversnow said, “There’s no need to hurry, you still have time. You can display the breadth of your potential bit by bit.”

“Mm.” Lin Ming nodded. To be first place on the Earth Proclamation was already a result to be proud of. He could only try his best for the Heaven Proclamation.

After this round of matches concluded, Vast Cosmos announced the next round.

The first match was – Lin Ming against Hang Chi!

The second match was Xiao Moxian against Frost Dream.

The third match was Jun Bluemoon against Dragon Fang.

This time, the most tense match was between Jun Bluemoon and Dragon Fang. Vast Universe Heavenly Palace had specifically opened up a separate gambling bet for this match.

As for Lin Ming against Hang Chi, or Xiao Moxian against Frost Dream, there was no separate bet set up for these two matches because there simply wasn’t anything worth gambling for. Although there was a slight chance that someone would cause an upset, the hope of that happening was too small. Even if Hang Chi’s compensation rates were extremely low, most people would likely still bet on him and Vast Universe Heavenly Palace would suffer a great loss.

“It seems I really am fighting Hang Chi.”

Lin Ming took a deep breath. Without a doubt, this would be a difficult battle.

Four hours of resting time later, the new round of matches officially began.

Lin Ming opened his eyes from meditation and stepped onto the arena stage. As he walked on, he could see a young, bald monk wearing linen robes and straw sandals already standing on stage, smiling at him. Hang Chi had already been waiting on the arena stage for the last two hours, where he had been deep in meditation.

As Hang Chi saw Lin Ming walk on stage, he began to walk forwards until he was 1000 feet away.

“Benefactor Lin, this poor monk greets you.” Hang Chi pressed his palms together and bowed.

Lin Ming greeted him back with common martial arts courtesy. His impression towards Hang Chi wasn’t bad at all. This young monk held no earthly desires and was pure in heart and mind, only wishing to wholeheartedly cultivate. This sort of person wouldn’t have a poor moral character.

As the audience saw the two people on the arena stage, all of them widened their eyes lest they miss the least bit of action.

Many people believed that Hang Chi had the capability of fighting with Frost Dream. As for Lin Ming, his strength was evident to all. Although Lin Ming was inferior to Hang Chi, he should still be able to force out some of Hang Chi’s cards. This would surely be an intense battle!

“Match, begin!”

Vast Cosmos loudly proclaimed.

With Vast Cosmos’s announcement, Hang Chi took out a long staff. As he did so, his aura changed.

At the start, Hang Chi had seemed like a gentle and naïve young monk. But now, his aura was solemn and dignified, deep and profound, his entire body containing a dreadful slumbering strength, just like a mountain.

His monk robes fluttered about him. With any simple movement, there wasn’t the slightest flaw in his stance. He was impregnable.

“Benefactor Lin, make your move!”

No matter who Hang Chi fought, he would always allow his opponent to attack first. Lin Ming wasn’t polite – he immediately thrust out his spear. On the Phoenix Blood Spear, purple flames lit up. The first four level Concepts of Fire fused together, fusing onto the spear shaft along with the fifth level Concept.

Virtual Disintegration!

Lin Ming used the fifth level Laws from the start. He was well aware that an attack on the level of the Blue Lotus Flame Dance didn’t even have the qualifications to probe his moves, let alone break through his defense.

“Concept of Virtual Fire?”

Hang Chi’s complexion changed. He brought his staff smashing down. With a brilliant light, the phantom of a bright Buddha appeared behind Hang Chi!

In fighting Lin Ming, Hang Chi didn’t use the Arhat Staff or other simple techniques like Leopard Climbing the Wall. He immediately summoned his Laws and Buddhist strength.

However, those simple techniques weren’t useless at all, because they were already deeply ingrained into Hang Chi’s bones!

Every single motion and movement of Hang Chi’s stemmed from the myriad 10 million senior supreme elders of Mount Potala; they were the total summary of their life experiences, all of them containing exquisite truths! In truth, the direct disciples of Mount Potala, from the very time they began to cultivate, whether it was using their fists, staffs, practicing movement techniques, or even drawing water, sweeping the floor, walking, eating, sleeping – every single thing they did had the mystery of martial skills fused within it.

These simple moves couldn’t create an Empyrean, but when fighting someone at the same level, they would always give an advantage.

Hang Chi was in such a situation. He had accumulated all this training over time, and these movements had already fused into his very being, becoming habits that were a part of his life.

Peng!

The purple flames of Lin Ming’s Virtual Disintegration were broken apart by Hang Chi’s staff shadows!

Hang Chi did not possess the Three Lives Pupils, but his strike was still accurate, directly striking the weak point of Virtual Disintegration. This stemmed from a natural martial arts intuition.

The explosive purple flame shockwaves that rushed out were unable to pose any threat to Hang Chi. As someone that followed the Buddhist principles, Hang Chi had long severed himself from worldly sins and emotions like jealousy and hate, thus this virtual fire had nearly no influence on him.

“Benefactor Lin’s age is so low and yet your attainments in the Laws have reached such heights. Moreover, this seems like a self-created technique. Your perception is truly amazing… then, this humble monk will now make his move.”

As Hang Chi spoke, a strong gray energy began to gather behind him. A breathtaking aura that left one gasping for breath fell down, covering all.

This was the first time that Hang Chi attacked on his own initiative. When he fought with Xiao Moxian, he had primarily been defending himself, but now he was actively attacking!

“Wheel of Samsara!”

Hang Chi grasped his staff, drawing an arc through the air. Then, from behind him, a round and exquisite Buddhist chart appeared. This Buddhist chart was all-encompassing, as if the countless lives in the universe were contained within it.

This was Mount Potala’s transcendent divine might!

Chapter 1312 – Samsara To Samsara

“That’s the Wheel of Samsara! Even Xiao Moxian lost to that move!”

The entire audience had an extremely profound impression of the Wheel of Samsara phantom that appeared behind Hang Chi. The Wheel of Samsara was too strong. Even Xiao Moxian with her phoenix true form wasn’t able to break past it.

“I wonder how Lin Ming will block this!”

Rumble rumble rumble!

The golden Wheel of Samsara came pressing down. Hang Chi stood within the center of the Wheel of Samsara, his monk robes still and plain, just like a godly Buddha.

Before the Wheel of Samsara arrived, Lin Ming could already feel the terrifying pressure contained within it. Although this was clearly a gold and holy Buddhist cultivation method, the truth was that this Wheel of Samsara contained a sharp, icy energy, making it seem as if needles were digging into Lin Ming’s body, making him feel an incomparable pain.

This cold energy was the power of samsara contained within the Wheel of Samsara.

Although Buddhist cultivation methods were filled with a gentle brilliance, often focusing on mercy and compassion, they also didn’t lack the path of slaughter, the grip of grudges, spells of resentment, blood pond hells, asura battlefields, and all other sorts of evil methods.

Where there was light, there was shadow. Where there was good, there was evil. Good and evil were dependent on each other; they were indivisible concepts.

Without evil, without murder, without suffering, without illness, aging, and death, without asura hells, if all of society lived in perpetual bliss and blind happiness, how could there be the Buddhist path?

If so, no one would believe in Buddhism in this world. The sins of humanity were an essential part of Buddhism.

In the six paths of samsara within the precepts of Buddhism, only the paths of divinity and humanity were the pure moral ways. The path of asura was neither good nor evil, and as for the last three paths, each was worse than the last!

Facing the Wheel of Samsara, it was impossible for Lin Ming to hold back, otherwise he would suffer instant defeat here.

He didn’t doubt that Hang Chi’s techniques were far more formidable than Xiao Moxian’s.

Lin Ming released the Heretical God Force to the limit, combusting the blood of the Ancient Phoenix, as well as fusing the three energies within him!

Three Essences as One, Heavenly Dao Judgment!

The phantom of the Heretical God Tree crazily grew from behind Lin Ming. With Heavenly Dao Judgment, he resisted the Wheel of Samsara!

In that instant, dark clouds billowed in the skies. A terrifying power began to gather together, forming a sword of thunderfire heavenly tribulation that thrust straight towards the Wheel of Samsara!

Kacha!

The sword of heavenly tribulation crashed into the Wheel of Samsara. A terrifying wave of energy rushed outwards. Lin Ming’s sword of heavenly tribulation broke apart again and again, but the Wheel of Samsara continued its push downwards!

Rumble rumble rumble!

The massive Wheel of Samsara was like a horrifyingly large grinding pan, grinding apart all, continuing to fall!

Hang Chi stood on the Wheel of Samsara, a brilliant divine light shining forth from his body. It was as if all rules in this world were crushed beneath his feet!

The Wheel of Samsara continued to sink. No one doubted that once this Wheel of Samsara pressed down, even a 100,000 foot mountain would be pulverized to power!

Lin Ming’s expression was solemn. His entire body emitted explosive popping sounds as the power of the dragon bone was released from his body!

Terrifying waves of strength rippled through Lin Ming’s body. He opened all seven gates, his mortal bodily strength instantly achieving a level of 100 million jins!

“Hahh!”

Lin Ming’s muscles bulged outwards. Blue veins bulged and several blood vessels exploded. He poured all of his strength into the Phoenix Blood Spear as the broken sword of heavenly retribution appeared once more!

Ka ka ka!

A mind-shaking sound spread through the world. The sword of heavenly retribution cut down once more on the Wheel of Samsara. Then, the Wheel of Samsara suddenly trembled as a golden crack appeared in its center!

As the crack appeared, the Wheel of Samsara’s radiance dimmed down and it stopped falling!

And the sword of heavenly retribution that Lin Ming formed by combining the power of thunder tribulation and fire tribulation cracked and reformed again and again. Lin Ming continued to revolve his energy to the limit. This dreadful consumption of energy had already surpassed the limits of an ordinary martial artist. If they were to try this their inner world would have already collapsed.

But Lin Ming relied on his solid foundation to forcefully withstand this burden.

Although he had just barely managed to do so, he had truly withstood the impact of the Wheel of Samsara!

More and more golden cracks appeared on the Wheel of Samsara, as if it would disintegrate soon!

“He blocked it! Lin Ming has blocked Hang Chi’s frontal attack!”

Hang Chi gave off an unfathomable feeling to all present, as if there was no one that could rival him. Most people believed that the difference in strength between Hang Chi and Lin Ming was far too large. If Hang Chi didn’t hold back then Lin Ming would have quickly lost.

But now, Hang Chi had attacked Lin Ming with his transcendent divine might, the Wheel of Samsara, yet that attack had been blocked by Lin Ming. This left everyone watching dumbfounded.

With Lin Ming’s age, he should already have been proud of the fact that he was able to stand on the same stage as Hang Chi. As for warding off this strike, that was truly an unmatched honor!

“Eh?”

Hang Chi revealed a startled color on his face, surprised that Lin Ming was able to crush his Wheel of Samsara. This attack was one that was almost at his full strength.

As Hang Chi saw more and more cracks appear on the Wheel of Samsara, his expression became much more solemn. He said, “Benefactor Lin’s talent is truly amazing. Perhaps in three more years, this poor monk might not be able to suppress you anymore. But now, although Benefactor Lin’s Heavenly Dao Judgment is high in the Laws, it still lacks a bit of accumulation and foundation. It seems that Benefactor Lin hasn’t comprehended this move long enough ago…”

Not only was Hang Chi astonishingly powerful, but he immersed himself all year round in martial arts, and thus his eyesight was spectacularly sharp. He was able to quickly understand the weaknesses in his opponent’s moves.

Lin Ming’s Heavenly Dao Judgment was comprehended just before the First Martial Meeting began. Up until now, he had only used it a few times, and he truly was lacking in practice. These flaws were all laid bare by Hang Chi.

As Hang Chi spoke, there was a rumbling sound and the Wheel of Samsara beneath his feet was broken apart by Lin Ming!

Heavenly Dao Judgment cut straight towards Hang Chi!

Facing Lin Ming’s attack, Hang Chi began to speak Buddhist sutras, his body glowing with a golden radiance.

“Samsara Domain, Eight Sectioned Stupa!”

Hang Chi spoke these words in a soft voice. Then, the shattered pieces of the Wheel of Samsara dissolved into the power of samsara where it was wildly absorbed by him, circling around his body and forming the Samsara Domain.

Then, with a loud bang, a titanic golden pagoda fell over Hang Chi. This divine pagoda glowed with a circulating golden divine light, filling the air with the breath of the Great Dao. This divine pagoda had eight floors, each floor possessing its own god.

Of these gods, some were gentle and solemn, some were fierce and overflowing with killing intent, some were as calm as a Buddha, and some were like an asura.

A stupa. In other words, a Buddhist pagoda!

Hang Chi summoned the Eight Sectioned Stupa, with eight gods stabilizing it. For a time, the entire space for a thousand feet around Hang Chi was suppressed by this pagoda, forming a sacred realm which could not be shaken!

Bang!

Lin Ming’s Heavenly Dao Judgment crashed into this Eight Sectioned Stupa; the power of thunder and fire erupted!

The divine pagoda violently shook and its light dimmed down, but within this divine pagoda, Hang Chi wasn’t injured at all. Or, it would be easier to say that he hadn’t felt any impact at all.

As the audience saw this, they immediately sucked in a breath of cold air.

Hang Chi’s defense was too terrifying!

Whether it was the Wheel of Samsara or the Eight Sectioned Stupa, they gave off an unshakable feeling.

Moreover, what was most dreadful was that according to Xiao Moxian’s words, Hang Chi still possessed an incorruptible diamond Vajra body. Even that arrogant Xiao Moxian didn’t believe that she could break through Hang Chi’s formidable defense!

“Lin Ming’s attack was very strong, but Hang Chi is ridiculous. Just the moves and defensive abilities he has displayed so far are mind-boggling, much less the fact that he has more secret arcane abilities to defend himself. I have no idea just how strong his body is!”

“That’s right, even after breaking through Hang Chi’s defensive technique with so much effort, they would still find that they cannot injure a single hair of his main body at all. How despairing is that!”

“He really is invincible. Just by virtue of his terrifying defense, Hang Chi is already in an invincible position! Lin Ming will lose… Heavenly Dao Judgment is his strongest attack. If that doesn’t work then there is nothing more he can do.”

As the audience spoke, in the skies, the light of Heavenly Dao Judgment detonated, turning the entire world into a sea of purple and red.

Lin Ming looked at Hang Chi, his complexion dignified. Up until now, Hang Chi was the most horrifying opponent he had ever faced. Perhaps he might not possess Xiao Moxian’s compatibility with the Laws or her God Beast body’s ability to withstand attacks, but just by relying on his deep foundation and all those various techniques at his disposal, he was nearly undefeatable at his step.

“Benefactor Lin, let me give you a warning. This poor monk’s Eight Sectioned Stupa is supported with the strength of eight gods from the Buddhist principles. It is a harmonic balance of Laws that is an offensive and defensive ability. Unless your strength far surpasses my own, it is impossible for you to break through my Eight Sectioned Stupa from the outside. When I am placed within the Eight Sectioned Stupa, it is impossible for ordinary attacks to reach me. However, my Eight Sectioned Stupa uses the power of the Wheel of Samsara as the foundation. In the end, it can be called a derivative technique of my transcendent divine might, the Wheel of Samsara. If you can see through this poor monk’s Samsara Domain then you will be able to break through this move from its very foundations.”

During this fierce battle, Hang Chi actually told his opponent how to break through his abilities. The way in which the disciples of Mount Potala competed in martial arts contests was truly unique.

As the audience heard this, they were all left speechless. “Hang Chi is really crazy. He’s actually telling his opponent the weaknesses in his own technique and waiting for him to try and break through it.”

“Don’t be an idiot. How can that possibly be called a weakness? See through his Samsara Domain? That’s just a joke and a half!”

Out of all the contestants, only Dragon Fang and his Three Lives Pupils had the chance of seeing through Hang Chi’s Samsara Domain. As for the others, it was no longer a question of how great their perception was; it simply wasn’t something a human could accomplish.

“Samsara Domain…”

Within Lin Ming’s mind, he recalled the 72 Sorcerer Pagodas that the Sorcerer of the Southern Wilderness left behind. In the Sorcerer Pagoda, Lin Ming had experienced 100 samsaras and had gained a profound understanding of the Samsara martial intent.

Now that Lin Ming faced Hang Chi’s Samsara Domain, he wondered. With his understandings of the Samsara martial intent, could he possibly see a hint of the mysteries within the Samsara Domain?

If he had to say, the hopes of this were very slim.

Even though Lin Ming’s perception was extremely high, the Sorcerer of the Southern Wildness had likely never come into contact with the core inheritances of the Wheel of Samsara. In all likelihood he had been an outer disciple of Mount Potala. How could an outer disciple’s cultivation methods possibly compare to those of an Empyrean direct disciple?

Although he knew it was impossible, Lin Ming still intended to give it a try. Even if he didn’t plan on succeeding and this attempt failed, it would still temper and further develop his Samsara martial intent. This type of powerful cultivation method certainly couldn’t be abandoned, but had to be developed whenever he had the chance.

Lin Ming held the Phoenix Blood Spear downwards. He took a deep breath. Then, his aura changed.

From behind him, the power of samsara constantly gathered. His two pupils turned into whirling black vortexes.

Lin Ming had displayed the Samsara martial intent. As the audience saw this, they were all taken aback with shock!

Chapter 1316 – Dream Cultivation

Empyrean Divine Seal’s lifetime of knowledge and abilities were all written in the Divine Seal Art. This was a comprehensive cultivation method, not just a single move.

It included the countless Laws of the Divine Realm, including the five elemental Laws, the Life Laws, Yin Yang Laws, and so forth.

But, the main focus of the Divine Seal Art was the Space Laws and Time Laws.

These two Laws were the Laws that Empyrean Divine Seal was most skilled in.

When Lin Ming had discovered the Ancient Elysium Seal deep beneath Immemorial Imperial City, he found that Empyrean Divine Seal had used the Ancient Elysium Seal as an array eye to suppress an unknown existence. The sealing technique he used was recorded within the Divine Seal Art.

Lin Ming found it hard to imagine just what type of existence was suppressed by Empyrean Divine Seal’s Divine Seal Art for 3.6 billion years and still hadn’t died.

Even though Lin Ming had now inherited a tiny incomplete soul fragment of Empyrean Divine Seal, he still didn’t have any memories of this.

Like this, Lin Ming was lost in a deep sleep, constantly experiencing the memories left behind by Empyrean Divine Seal.

And on the arena stage, the battles were carrying on.

In Xiao Moxian and Frost Dream’s match, Frost Dream had defeated Xiao Moxian without any problems. At this point, only Frost Dream and Hang Chi still had unbroken winning streaks.

The third match of the second round was Jun Bluemoon against Dragon Fang.

Many people were looking forwards to this battle. Although the two of them had lost to Lin Ming, the disparity wasn’t too great, especially with Jun Bluemoon, who had withstood Lin Ming’s Heavenly Dao Judgment without suffering any injuries.

As soon as Jun Bluemoon stepped on stage he used his Yin Yang Laws. However, these Laws were seen through by Dragon Fang’s Three Lives Pupils.

Then, Dragon Fang suppressed Jun Bluemoon. Even Jun Bluemoon’s finishing move, the 64 Yin Yang Trigrams Sword was seen through by Dragon Fang’s All Existence to Void.

However, Jun Bluemoon was extremely tough. Although he was suppressed, he still wasn’t defeated.

The two brutally fought for an hour, exchanging over a thousand moves and wounding each other again and again. They slowly began to reach their limits, but in the end, Jun Bluemoon’s endurance proved to be superior. With a small advantage, Jun Bluemoon took the lead and won a hard-earned victory against Dragon Fang.

This difficult victory showed that the two youths were individually matched. Who won or who lost, luck and their current condition played an extremely large role.

Thus, the second round in the first group of six people ended like this. Even so, Lin Ming still hadn’t woken up.

Vast Cosmos announced the beginning of the third round.

This round should have been where Lin Ming and Frost Dream battled, but because Lin Ming had fallen into a deep sleep, Frost Dream drew a bye. This left behind Hang Chi, Dragon Fang, Xiao Moxian, and Jun Bluemoon still competing. In truth, among these four people, most of them had already fought, thus there weren’t many matches left.

The two matches for this round were Hang Chi against Jun Bluemoon and Dragon Fang against Xiao Moxian.

Compared to the last matches, these were much less anticipated.

“Frost Dream hasn’t gone on stage… I wanted to watch Frost Dream fight Lin Ming!” Some audience members knew that Frost Dream had drawn a bye and were somewhat dissatisfied.

Frost Dream was the dream lover of many heroic young elites. They all wanted to see Frost Dream in action. Even if there wasn’t any suspense in the match between Frost Dream and Lin Ming, they still wished to see her roll over her opponents with absolute strength.

It could only be said that Frost Dream was too popular.

Compared to Frost Dream and Xiao Moxian, Lin Ming simply didn’t have much support.

“It doesn’t matter if Frost Dream fights Lin Ming or not; it’s just a small interlude, Frost Dream will win no matter what. The only one who can truly compete with Frost Dream here is Hang Chi. But, I think that Hang Chi has higher chances of losing. Just look at when Frost Dream fought Dragon Fang. She defeated him without much effort.”

“Speaking about it… what’s going on with Lin Ming? Are his injuries really that heavy? An Empyrean Heavenly Palace shouldn’t be lacking in medicines, right? With all sorts of wonderful medicines at his use, he still didn’t immediately recover?”

“It must be a soul injury. Hang Chi is a kind and merciful person so he should know what his limits are. However, Lin Ming wanted to show off his strength, and even though he knew he wasn’t Hang Chi’s match, he still used that World King level Minor Samsara Path to struggle with Hang Chi’s transcendent divine might, the Wheel of Samsara. How could a World King level cultivation method possibly triumph over a transcendent divine might? There is a gap in cultivation methods and also a gap in cultivation realms; the result of the match was already decided from the beginning. Even so, Lin Ming wanted to fight and the aura he displayed was so powerful that it made others feel he wasn’t much weaker at all. Finally, all of that caused him to be injured too heavily. This is just a martial arts contest but he was so reckless…”

An old man shook his head, his voice filled with regret. A soul injury was not easy to cure. If a martial artist’s soul was injured, that was definitely bad news.

Luckily, this had happened in Vast Universe Heavenly Palace. There were many precious soul recovery medicines here so Lin Ming should be in a much better position.

But even so, in this case, if Lin Ming still remained unconscious and missed the third round of matches and allowed Frost Dream to draw a bye, this would be proof that his injuries were extremely heavy!

This sort of wound was likely to leave permanent damage behind!

To a genius, this was undoubtedly a tremendous loss! It might even affect his future achievements.

“If he really is heavily injured then Lin Ming’s losses will be great. Isn’t Vast Cosmos the referee? How come he didn’t stop the match?”

“How could it be so easy? All of these geniuses are difficult to measure with common sense. Even for a half-step Empyrean, it’s impossible for them to determine who is weaker or stronger before they fight. There are bound to be unexpected surprises. This time Lin Ming truly didn’t consider the situation. These young ones are far too spirited.”

As Lin Ming was unconscious, news of his situation spread through the arena. As people heard this, they began to think that Lin Ming had tried too hard to show off in front of Hang Chi, and had suffered a soul wound because of it. Not even Vast Cosmos was able to cure him.

This was the heart of human jealousy, something everyone possessed. As the audience saw Lin Ming suffer, some of them were sorry for him but some were also gloating at his suffering. For instance, the Skydark Holy Lands’ Nether Limitless was extremely happy to hear this. The deeper Lin Ming’s wounds were, the better it was.

At this time, deep within Vast Universe Heavenly Palace, Empyrean Vast Universe said to Empyrean Divine Dream, “What is wrong with Lin Ming? I don’t feel as if his soul has been injured, so why hasn’t he awoken after such a long time?”

Let alone Empyrean Vast Universe, not even Empyrean Divine Dream was able to see through the divine soul mark that Empyrean Divine Seal left behind.

Empyrean Divine Dream shook her head, saying, “It’s hard to say. Perhaps it might have something to do with the time he climbed up the Divine Seal Altar’s 33rd step.”

“If he continues to stay asleep then the tournament will end. He still has a match left with Frost Dream. Do you plan on sentencing Lin Ming to a loss?”

Although Empyrean Vast Universe didn’t think that Lin Ming had a chance of winning, it was still too careless to so easily decide someone’s defeat.

Divine Dream said, “Have Lin Ming placed into a time enchantment… a 1:100 time flow. He should be able to wake up. Characters like him will not fall from the altar so easily and he still has a long road awaiting him. He will surely pass this trial.”

As Divine Dream spoke, Empyrean Vast Universe could only concur. He sent an order to Xin Shenzi to have Lin Ming placed into a 1:100 time flow enchantment.

Xin Shenzi himself was a Great World King master so it was easy for him to lay down such an enchantment. After he set down Lin Ming in a good position, he reached out and waved his hands. Four jade bunnies leapt out from his spirit beast chart, transforming into four beautiful young girls within the enchantment.

These four young girls all originated from the monster race and their cultivations were equal to a late Revolving Core realm human’s. They were only a single step away from making a breakthrough. The jade bunny clan of the monster race had a naturally docile and gentle temperament. They had fallen into dire straits and were rescued by Xin Shenzi. At the time, Xin Shenzi just happened to have a spirit beast chart magic tool, so he accepted them as his secret disciples.

“The four of you will be responsible for looking after Lin Ming. Do not allow the slightest error to occur. Until he wakes up, immediately report to me any changes that occur.”

“Yes.”

Following that, within the time enchantment, the four Revolving Core young girls of the monster race spent every second of the day watching and caring for Lin Ming. Their actions were orderly and meticulous.

However, when these four young girls entered the enchantment to care for Lin Ming, they never imagined it would be for such a long time.

Soon, half a year passed and Lin Ming still remained asleep as before!

For such a long time, these four young girls constantly stared at the face of a single young man and their lives were naturally boring. Luckily, Lin Ming had an extraordinarily handsome face with an excellent and dashing temperament. Looking at him all day was a comfortable experience.

This continued to eight months, nine months…

Lin Ming still didn’t wake up.

If an ordinary person slept for such a long time, their body would have become smelly and covered with sores. However, Lin Ming remained clean and free of dust the entire time. He exuded a hint of masculinity that was pleasant to smell. Thus, these four young girls didn’t have to do something so embarrassing like wiping down his body or helping him bathe.

Slowly, one year passed…

During this year, Lin Ming constantly comprehended within the samsara world. Immersed in a sea of Laws, he forgot time, and forgot all else.

He even forgot the memory that he had been struck by the Wheel of Samsara and was experiencing a long dream. Rather, he thought that this was his life, that this was reality.

Every day was spent in non-stop pondering and meditation. Sometimes Lin Ming was like a rock, sitting still for an entire month. Within this dream, his body was surrounded with countless dao patterns and Law fragments, These dao patterns ran over him like trickling water before flowing into his body and then slowly leaking out from his pores. Everything seemed harmonious, like a perfect cycle.

What sort of character was Empyrean Divine Seal? The runes he left behind contained not only comprehensions of Laws but also fragments of memories. How could this be comprehended in several days or even several months?

Even with Lin Ming’s perception, wanting to thoroughly comprehend these things and reform the Divine Seal Art was extremely difficult!

In a year of time, Lin Ming had comprehended only a tenth of the Laws that Empyrean Divine Seal had left behind. He had just barely managed to cross into the threshold of the Divine Seal Art.

Beyond that, there were also many Laws. However, Lin Ming wasn’t able to comprehend them because his boundary was simply far too shallow.

Empyrean Divine Seal’s boundary was just far too high. Just this tiny insignificant soul fragment was enough for Lin Ming to enjoy for a hundred years, allowing him to meditate on it for two or three large boundaries.

The truth was that this was something that only Lin Ming could do. If someone else were here, then even if they were a top extreme character like Hang Chi or Jun Bluemoon, they would still be powerless when facing Empyrean Divine Seal’s Laws.

This was because they had yet to comprehend the Concept of the 33 Layered Heavens. It was also because of this point that Lin Ming was able to obtain Empyrean Divine Seal’s inheritance.

Chapter 1317 – Cultivating the Divine Seal Art

Another year and another month passed. Deep in meditation, Lin Ming suddenly opened his eyes.

He was sitting down cross-legged in a vast and unknown space of the universe, filled with endless mist and dust. With just a glance, everything around him was wrapped in a dim haze. The surrounding space was filled with the chaotic power of space and time. Space twisted, making it impossible to identify just what direction was which, and even the flow of time was in complete upheaval. Deep within this area, even one’s normal breathing and heart rate were affected.

“I’ve arrived at this space again…” Lin Ming whispered to himself, his eyes bright and shining. He had named this space the divine seal space.

Every time he entered the divine seal space, Lin Ming was able to become aware of many things.

He closed his eyes and silently sensed the rich Space and Time Laws here. This place was like the primordial soup before the universe was formed, and the Laws here were still in their most primitive state. Wanting to become aware of these Laws was extremely easy.

During this year, Lin Ming had already comprehended the Time and Space Laws to large success of the fifth level.

It had to be known that before this, Lin Ming’s attainments in the Time and Space Laws weren’t high at all. He had only been comparable to a genius from an ordinary Holy Land, far from reaching the level of an Empyrean descendant like Dragon Fang. He wasn’t even able to compare with someone like the Monster Prince.

Lin Ming’s understandings into these two Laws were so poor that he couldn’t even display them in actual combat, otherwise he wouldn’t have needed to summon the Heretical God Tree phantom when he fought the Monster Prince. He had done so because ordinary Thunder and Fire Laws did not possess the ability to resist the Monster Prince’s Space and Time Laws.

In just a year, Lin Ming had been able to reach large success of the fifth level Concepts in the extremely difficult to study Time and Space Laws. He had surpassed the Monster Prince and was only slightly inferior to Dragon Fang. This speed of improvement was horrifying.

Moreover, although the boundary of Lin Ming’s Space and Time Laws was inferior to Dragon Fang’s, the Time and Space Laws that Empyrean Divine Seal comprehended were of an exorbitantly high level; they were far from what ordinary Space and Time Laws could hope to compare with.

As Lin Ming was enlightening himself on the Space and Time Laws here, at this moment, the endless dust in this space began to converge together at a single point. The mist and dust seemed thin, but there was an endless volume. In terms of weight, it could easily surpass a million trillion jins.

Lin Ming could see this swirling vortex of dust rapidly grow. A swallowing force latched onto him, making him feel as if he were being sucked into this whirlpool.

Lin Ming’s mind chilled as he rapidly retreated. He watched with his own eyes as this vortex grew increasingly large, finally condensing into a star!

Dust and mist forming a star?

Lin Ming was stunned, “Is this the forming process of a star?”

As Lin Ming was thinking over this, that massive star began to burn. An incomparably horrifying light erupted from within it. The total amount of energy in this eruption was so great that the all-out strike of an Empyrean was completely overshadowed.

Lin Ming recalled the time when he had absorbed the blood essence of the Ancient Phoenix. In that dream world, he had seen the scene of the phoenix undergoing nirvana. That phoenix had been bathing within the blazing hot core of a star, its body in the process of being reborn.

Without a doubt, this was a sun!

“Am I witnessing the formation of a sun?” Lin Ming thought. He could feel the fire origin energy around him being stirred up, becoming more and more hot. Because of the amount of heat that this sun was releasing, the surrounding temperature was so high that even metal essence would instantly turn to steam. If a giant meteor were to fall into this sun, it would quickly be melted away, vanishing into nothing.

Lin Ming didn’t retreat. As he faced this sun, he began to slowly realize the Fire Laws.

His Fire Laws had been stranded at the fifth level Concept for an extremely long time; he hadn’t yet been able to trace the threshold to the sixth level Concept. This also caused Lin Ming’s Laws to be at a much lower height than those of Dragon Fang and the others.

And Lin Ming was well aware that the sixth level Concept was Yang Flames – in other words, the fires of a sun!

The first four levels of the Fire Laws, whether it was Burning Heat, Annihilation, Creation, or Manifestation, these were fires of the mortal world. As for the fifth level Fire Laws, that was Virtual Fire. The flames of jealousy, boiling anger, overflowing rage, heated hatred, all of these were flames transformed from the human mind. They could be called spiritual fires.

Then, upon arriving at the sixth level Laws, it was the fires of the sun. The fires of the sun had an essential difference from fires of the mortal world.

The fires of the mortal world produced flames from burning materials, but as for the fires of the sun, that was similar to releasing energy and flames from completely annihilated matter. This sort of absolute annihilation produced a power thousands of times greater.

A phoenix’s nirvana meant to undergo nirvana within the center of a sun. A grown-up phoenix would choose to undergo nirvana in the center of a blazing star. The more powerful the phoenix was, the more terrifying the star they chose.

Only when facing a true sun could one comprehend the real sixth level Concept of the Fire Laws – Yang Flames!

But now, with the current Lin Ming’s cultivation, it was still far too early for him to thoroughly comprehend Yang Flames; it was simply impossible. Even so, if he managed to trace upon the threshold of the Concept of Yang Flames and add a bit of that power to his Fire Laws, then there would be no comparison between his moves before and after!

The sun became increasingly bright and blazing. Lin Ming felt his entire body burning, even as he was constantly enlightening himself on everything happening. At this time, the sun rapidly grew as if it would explode at any moment.

Lin Ming was bewildered. He could feel that this sun was about to collapse so he rapidly drew backwards.

In this illusory virtual space, his speed was extraordinarily quick. He soon retreated a million miles back. And at this time, the sun suddenly detonated with an incomparably terrifying divine light, seeming as if the entire universe would be swallowed up. With an explosion of sound, dreadful waves of heat destroyed everything and even the void was shaken to the point of collapse!

In that moment, Lin Ming thought he had died. It was impossible for a human to resist such a horrifying explosion.

Hu – hu – hu –

Terrifying flames swept over Lin Ming.

Lin Ming took a deep breath. He was certain that if this weren’t a virtual space, he would have already turned to ash just now, even if he were another million miles farther away.

The flames gradually dissipated. The sun was already destroyed. It began to gradually collapse, its volume rapidly becoming smaller. It eventually shrank a trillion times smaller. All of that matter, light, space, and time, everything was sucked into it.

Slowly, the sun evolved into a star of absolute darkness.

Lin Ming knew that this star, according to Empyrean Divine Seal’s viewpoint, was called a black hole.

Every black hole had a very small radius of space around it that formed an ‘absolute horizon’.

Within the Divine Seal Art, this space was called the black hole horizon. It was impossible for any matter that fell into the black hole horizon to emerge again. This was an absolute enchantment of time and space. Even if an Empyrean were to fall into it, they wouldn’t be an exception.

The black hole horizon destroyed all matter, space, and time. It was the end point of all Space and Time Laws!

As for Empyrean Divine Seal, he had cultivated the Space and Time Laws to the boundary of a black hole. He was able to have space and time form a black hole!

This was also one of the moves within the Divine Seal Art when it was cultivated to an extremely high boundary.

By creating a black hole and using the absolute Space and Time Laws to seal away all, even a divine god would be permanently sealed, unable to escape!

Divine Seal, Seal the Divine!

This was where Empyrean Divine Seal and the Divine Seal Art’s name originated from. There was no exaggeration in these names either. In the past, Empyrean Divine Seal truly did possess the ability to seal away gods. This was because he was an existence that had surpassed an Empyrean.

That was…

The realm of True Divinity!

It was naturally impossible for Lin Ming to practice to this boundary, but if it was just reproducing a tiny bit of the black hole horizon’s charm, he was still able to barely accomplish that.

Witnessing the creation of a black hole with his own eyes had the greatest benefits to Lin Ming’s comprehension of the Divine Seal Art.

Lin Ming sat down before this black hole, recalling everything that had just happened, “To seal off the space, everything that enters will not be able to break through that cage. To seal off time, everything that falls into the black hole horizon will fall into an eternally timeless moment, locked into a single moment of forever. Their body will stop for all time. With all of this combined together, with matter, time, and space compressed to the limit, that is what it means to truly seal something.”

As Lin Ming spoke, all sorts of changes occurred within his inner world.

In his body’s inner world, all of the world power and all of the energy gathered together, slowly forming a whirlpool. Lin Ming was using the energy within himself to simulate the formation of a sun.

In cultivating the Divine Seal Art, the symbol of truly beginning training in it was to form a miniature black hole in one’s inner world. All future practice would center around this miniature black hole.

However, forming this miniature black hole was extremely risky. If one’s foundation was lacking, not only would that miniature black hole not form, but their inner world would directly collapse because it wouldn’t be able to withstand the sudden changes in energy.

Although Lin Ming was now sleeping, the process of forming a miniature black hole was truly occurring in reality. The real world was in sync with the dream world. If there was a single mistake, then Lin Ming’s inner world would crack apart and he really would die.

This process was not hurried at all. Just like the birth, growth, and death of a sun, for the formation of the miniature black hole in the body, that process needed the accumulation of time and continuous evolution!

And at this time, 400 days had already passed. That was four days in the outside world.

The First Martial Meeting tournament had basically ended two days ago. There were only two matches that had yet to be fought.

One was Frost Dream against Hang Chi, and the other was Frost Dream against Lin Ming!

Now there had been a pause for two days. The audience had long been impatient with waiting.

“What’s going on? How come Hang Chi and Frost Dream’s showdown hasn’t begun yet? Are they fighting today? They couldn’t be playing with us, right?”

The several hundred million spectators present were all anticipating watching Hang Chi and Frost Dream’s battle. That would surely be the most splendid battle of the First Martial Meeting!

“I heard that the organizers originally intended for Frost Dream to first fight Lin Ming before the battle between Frost Dream and Hang Chi. But since Lin Ming was severely wounded and hasn’t awoken yet, the competition was delayed for a few days.”

Of these two matches, Hang Chi against Frost Dream should have been at the very end. It was the prime showdown of the First Martial Meeting and should have been the last battle where the champion was decided. However, because Lin Ming’s soul was grievously wounded and he had fallen into a deep sleep, the battle between Lin Ming and Frost Dream had been delayed.

Chapter 1321 – Cultivation Great Success

As Lin Ming was thinking this, he released complete control of the energy sphere, allowing it to erupt!

For a time, Lin Ming’s dark inner world was filled with an endlessly dazzling brilliance, like countless golden divine swords tearing apart all!

Rumble rumble rumble!

A terrifying energy rolled out like turbulent waves, rushing towards the edges of Lin Ming’s inner world!

For a time, Lin Ming’s inner world was forced to withstand an unimaginably great impact, nearly cracking in the process.

Ka ka ka ka ka!

Massive fragments of space were torn open. Lin Ming’s inner world was brutally torn asunder by this energy, expanding outwards. An unspeakable pain spread through his body. In that moment, he felt as if he were dying!

These changes were directly reflected on Lin Ming’s sleeping body. His main body suddenly shook as he spat out a mouthful of blood!

Bang!

The stone bed beneath Lin Ming collapsed, unable to withstand this power. Pieces of stone flew into the air!

Within the time enchantment, the four young jade bunny girls were frightened.

As they saw Lin Ming’s face whiten, his body shake, and blood seep out of his mouth and nostrils, they were all panic-stricken.

Lin Ming had originally been severely injured and had been sleeping for the last year and a half. And now, if anyone saw this they would think he was on the verge of death.

Lin Ming’s situation became increasingly bad. His face had turned deep purple and now blood was streaming from his ears and eyes!

The four jade bunny girls were scared silly. “Hu-hurry and report this to Senior Xin Shenzi! Lin Ming is about to die!”

A young girl said. She nervously fumbled with a sound transmitting talisman and lit it. Young girls of the jade bunny race were naturally good-hearted and gentle individuals. They had been watching over Lin Ming for the last year and a half, and now that they saw him have such an accident, they were certainly worried about him.

Just as the light of the sound transmitting talisman was extinguished, Lin Ming’s body wildly shook. Because his clothes couldn’t withstand the impact of his exploding inner world, they were all torn apart! These were top-grade saint artifacts! But under such an impact there was no possibility for these clothes to remain intact.

As Xin Shenzi heard this news he was shocked. He resolutely reported this to Empyrean Vast Universe and raced towards the time enchantment as fast as he could. Lin Ming’s current status was very special. If something were to happen to him, that would be a loss to the entire martial world.

Deep within Vast Universe Heavenly Palace, the light of a sound transmitting talisman flashed in front of Empyrean Vast Universe.

“Mm? Lin Ming is severely wounded and vomiting blood? His life is in critical danger?”

Empyrean Vast Universe thought that this message would be about Lin Ming awakening, but he never imagined this would happen.

“Divine Dream.” Empyrean Vast Universe turned to Divine Dream. Divine Dream faintly pressed her eyebrows together before saying, “Let us go and take a look.”

“That’s all we can do.” Empyrean Vast Universe nodded. Lin Ming’s situation was extremely complicated. It was hard to imagine just what was happening to him.

The two Empyreans flashed and in the next moment they had arrived in the time enchantment. They saw Lin Ming’s entire body colored a deep purple with blood leaking from his head. The stone bed underneath him had completely collapsed.

“Greetings, Honorable Master! And greetings, Senior Divine Dream!”

Xin Shenzi bowed towards Empyrean Vast Universe and Empyrean Divine Dream. As for the four jade bunny girls behind him, they all cried out in alarm at these words. How could they have expected that these two people that suddenly appeared in front of them would be two legendary Empyreans!

Two Empyreans had come to personally see Lin Ming, and they even came together?

The four young girls immediately kneeled on the ground, deeply bowing. The difference between an Empyrean and a Revolving Core or Divine Sea martial artist was even greater than the difference between an emperor and a commoner. It was reasonable for them to deeply bow like this.

“What’s wrong?” Empyrean Vast Universe frowned as he looked towards Xin Shenzi.

Xin Shenzi said, “This disciple has just probed Lin Ming. His inner world is completely chaotic right now, and even seems as if it will collapse. This disciple is useless and does not know what is happening. Although this disciple can forcefully stop this change, I believe that would be the incorrect decision. Thus, I quickly enveloped Lin Ming in another time enchantment to delay the changes in his inner world as much as possible before Honorable Master was able to arrive.”

If a time enchantment could accelerate time, it could also decelerate time. Just as Empyrean Vast Universe was about to step forwards to check himself, Empyrean Divine Dream flicked a single finger and melted away Xin Shenzi’s time enchantment.

“Divine Dream?”

Empyrean Vast Universe was surprised. However, he also knew that Divine Dream had her own reasons for doing things.

Empyrean Divine Dream shook her head, saying, “There is no need to panic. He should be fine…”

“Mm?” Empyrean Vast Universe was startled. He probed Lin Ming’s inner world with his senses and only felt that there were some unknown changes occurring within him.

His inner world had become unfathomably deep, even faintly seeming as if it would swallow his own senses.

Although this attractive force was very weak on Empyrean Vast Universe, it was still enough for him to draw back his senses. This was also because Empyrean Vast Universe’s divine sense was too strong. If it were a martial artist with a lower cultivation, then perhaps their divine sense really would be sucked in by this absorbing force.

“This inner world is…”

Empyrean Vast Universe was startled. Many martial artists had special bloodlines or physiques. For instance, Xiao Moxian’s phoenix true form or Hang Chi’s reincarnated Buddha.

And every so often, there would be those with strange inner worlds and souls. These variation souls and variation inner worlds weren’t too rare. Empyrean Vast Universe suspected that Lin Ming was also in this sort of situation.

“Inner world variation?”

This thought instantly raced through Empyrean Vast Universe’s mind. If so, then Lin Ming really was too heaven-defying. If a talent like him also had a variation inner world, how could other geniuses still live?

At this time, within the samsara dreamland, Lin Ming was still meditating in that vast and boundless space of nothingness. His complexion became increasingly pale but his halted breathing had subsided.

His inner world had been swept over by a wild storm with everything left in a chaotic mess. Besides the Heretical God Tree, all of the mountains and rivers and lakes and plains were all utterly destroyed!

However, above this region, there was an invisible anomaly in space. As light passed near a certain point in the void, it curved, bending around it. Unless one was skilled in the Space Laws it would be impossible to see this, because this point was hidden in the void, twisting all light around it.

This spot was the black hole seed that Lin Ming had condensed with the Divine Seal Art!

A black hole was the most terrifying celestial body in the universe. There was almost nothing that could destroy a black hole. If a black hole fell into a sun, it would eventually swallow that sun, ultimately causing an unimaginable explosion!

Lin Ming had simulated the explosion of a fire star with his true essence and then finally condensed it into a black hole seed. Although it was far from truly achieving the level of an actual black hole, as Lin Ming’s cultivation rose, the total energy within that black hole seed would become higher and higher and the traction force would become increasingly terrifying until the moment when all space and time would be sucked into it, finally evolving into an end point of all space and time!

The moment that Lin Ming’s black hole seed had truly formed, he seemed to have opened wide a great and mystical door before him.

As this door opened, the aura of the Great Dao blew towards him with indescribable glory!

This aura of the Great Dao had an essential difference from the baptism of the Heavenly Dao Laws one experienced during the crossing of Ninefall. This aura contained the Concept of the 33 Layered Heavens and stood at almost the highest point of all Laws.

The aura of the endless Great Dao surged into Lin Ming’s inner world. Then, his inner world that was reduced to rubble and ruins by the explosion of true essence and energy began to glow with reborn vitality.

The explosion of that sphere of energy had been far too terrifying. Even though Lin Ming’s foundation was extremely solid, there were still all sorts of ruptured areas within his inner world.

Now, all of these damaged places were being repaired by this strength.

The fragmented rubble fused into the earth. New mountains rose and new rivers began to flow. An incomparably rich world power condensed, forming origin energy clouds in the skies. Because these clouds were too thick and heavy, they began to rain down with drops of origin energy.

This origin energy rain gathered into the dry streams and channels as it fell, turning into fresh and wonderful currents.

As the land was watered, plants began to sprout and colorful spirit flowers started to bloom.

In that moment, Lin Ming’s strength rapidly climbed, reaching unprecedented heights!

Hu – !

Afterwards, that vast aura swept out from Lin Ming’s body, recklessly spinning around him like heavy mercury!

As Empyrean Vast Universe felt this boundless aura, he was startled. This was clearly the aura of the 33 Layered Heavens’ Great Dao. Empyrean Vast Universe had obtained the remnant soul of the ancient Divine Seal Altar’s artifact spirit. It was impossible for him to misidentify this aura.

The two Empyreans as well as Xin Shenzi were naturally unaffected by this aura; at most, they were slightly amazed by the vast glory of it. But behind these three masters, the four young jade bunny girls that were kneeling were baptized by this aura. They fell into a trance, feeling reborn.

In just several breaths of time, they had greatly benefited. They even faintly felt as if they would break through to the next boundary.

“This… this is…”

The four young girls flushed red. This was a tremendous lucky chance. It was no longer a question of helping them break through to the next realm, but instead caused the Laws within their bodies to change on a qualitative level. This meant that in the future, their martial arts achievements would reach even further heights.

They were all excited to the point of wanting to hop around, but with the presence of two Empyreans here, they stilled themselves.

Xin Shenzi smiled in understanding, “These last 500 days have been hard on you. This can be considered payment in kind, the cause and effects of this world.”

Xin Shenzi didn’t know what happened to Lin Ming, but what he could be certain about was that Lin Ming had undoubtedly experienced a massive lucky chance. His strength had rapidly risen by leaps and bounds!

This sort of lucky chance was bewildering. Just a faint aura from Lin Ming’s breakthrough alone was enough to greatly benefit these four young jade bunny girls and increase their potential.

Xin Shenzi looked towards Empyrean Vast Universe, but Empyrean Vast Universe was actually looking at Divine Dream. He had no idea what was happening within Lin Ming.

“Is this because of the Divine Seal Altar?”

Empyrean Vast Universe always had this guess in his mind. He had refined a replica of the ancient Divine Seal Altar using a fragment of its artifact spirit, and this replica also contained the mystical charm of the Concept of the 33 Layered Heavens.

Now, it appeared that the comprehensions Lin Ming gained from mounting the Divine Seal Altar finally began to transform into true strength today!

Chapter 1322 – Awakening And Exiting

Empyrean Divine Dream gently nodded, saying, “When Lin Ming climbed up the Divine Seal Altar’s 33 steps, he withstood the baptism of the ancient Concept of the 33 Layered Heavens contained within it. This baptism greatly affected him, but because the time was too short, the influence from the Concept of the 33 Layered Heavens had to manifest. As time passed, this advantage will become increasingly obvious.”

Empyrean Vast Universe shook his head as he heard Divine Dream’s confirmation. He said, “This is the flow of destiny. I am far from being able to compare to Lin Ming. Although I have luck, I lack destiny. The result is that my work was given as a gift to this junior Lin Ming…”

As Empyrean Vast Universe spoke of the Concept of the 33 Layered Heavens, he couldn’t help but deeply sigh. At the start, he really had been able to obtain a fragment of the ancient Divine Seal Altar. In terms of luck, Empyrean Vast Universe was not bad at all.

However, even though Empyrean Vast Universe meditated on the Divine Seal Altar fragment for many years afterwards, he was only able to touch upon the threshold of the 33 Layered Heavens’ Laws, and wasn’t able to transform that into his own strength. As for the Divine Seal Altar fragment, he had later taken that as a foundation to create an Empyrean spirit treasure.

This harvest was not worthy of mentioning in comparison to Lin Ming.

If one entered a treasure mountain and returned empty-handed, that was not because one’s luck was bad but because one’s destiny was lacking.

Luck was only a part of destiny. Talent, will, perception, mentality, soul – all of those were equally important parts of destiny.

Luck only provided opportunities. Whether one could grasp those opportunities depended on themselves.

Empyrean Divine Dream slowly said, “Lin Ming’s destiny is truly amazing. If this was in the past, then Lin Ming would eventually develop into a leader amongst Empyreans. And now, in this great world, Lin Ming even has the smallest of chances of surpassing the boundary of an Empyrean and becoming a True Divinity!”

“True Divinity!? That’s too exaggerated!”

Empyrean Vast Universe had a great response as he heard this. Although he knew that Lin Ming possessed heaven-defying talent, the realm of True Divinity was something that existed only in myths. Empyrean Vast Universe didn’t even believe that someone like Xiao Moxian had the chance of becoming a True Divinity in the future.

Even if Empyrean Divine Dream said ‘smallest of chances’, Empyrean Vast Universe still couldn’t accept this. Was becoming a True Divinity really that easy?

“Throughout the endless epochs, how many Empyreans have failed to become a True Divinity? Divine Dream, even you, someone who has achieved the peak in every aspect, aren’t you also unable to take that final step into True Divinity? Your praise of Lin Ming seems rather too high. Even for someone as talented as Lin Ming, I do not believe that in the past billion years, amongst the infinite lives born in the Divine Realm and the lower realms, there hasn’t been someone similar to him. Aren’t Xiao Moxian and Frost Dream also similar in comparison?

“Let alone the last billion years, even for the last 3 billion years there has never been a True Divinity supreme being that has appeared. There have only been stories, and these stories are far too exaggerated, without any credibility at all.”

Empyrean Vast Universe was clearly very sensitive to the term True Divinity. This was also reasonable. In the legends, it was said that those that stepped into True Divinity could refine stars, crush planets, and there were even fables that said that True Divinities could live as one with the world, living in everlasting immortality!

The former wasn’t considered much. Although the increase in strength seemed wonderful, it was still within the realm of acceptability. After all, a powerful Empyrean could already crush planets. Of course, that was only crushing planets. If they wanted to crush suns that were tens of thousands of times larger than a planet, even an Empyrean was far lacking.

To chase after a stronger strength was the wish and drive of all martial artists. But, what truly enticed an Empyrean was the promise that they could live in perpetuity!

This attraction was simply too great to an Empyrean.

When one cultivated to the realm of an Empyrean, they truly held control of a world and dominated the lives of trillions upon trillions of people. With all of these before them, how could they willingly accept the end of their own mortality and turn into dust?

The path of martial arts was to struggle with the heavens. Every time one made a breakthrough, their lifespan would increase several times over. This was a tremendous lure to many martial artists, driving them to painstakingly cultivate and also one of the greatest motivations that caused them to constantly risk their lives in the most dire of dangers.

Divine Dream said, “In the past, there indeed might not have been this possibility. But now, in this universe, there truly exists this hope. Not only does Lin Ming have this hope, but so does Xiao Moxian; one could even say her hopes are much greater.”

As Divine Dream spoke like this, Empyrean Vast Universe seemed as if he wanted to say something, but eventually didn’t. Even though he was an Empyrean, he always felt that speaking in terms of the universe seemed far too remote. A True Divinity… was that something that could truly be reached in this world?

Empyrean Vast Universe was silent for some time before saying, “According to what you say, do you happen to think that Lin Ming might be able to defeat Frost Dream?”

Empyrean Vast Universe also felt the mysterious and exceptional presence around Frost Dream. To every heroic young elite, defeating Frost Dream was a near-impossibility.

Divine Dream slowly said, “Frost Dream surpasses the younger generation by far too much. To compare Lin Ming to Frost Dream is unfair to begin with…”

She only spoke to here before not speaking again. Frost Dream was personally raised by Divine Dream. As for what Frost Dream’s limits were, only Divine Dream would know.

Frost Dream had already surpassed the concept of ‘young elites’.

At this time, on the ruined stone bed, Lin Ming violently coughed. Every cough was followed by fresh blood.

Divine Dream glanced at Lin Ming and flicked a finger, tossing out a crystalline pill. This pill was glittering and transparent, exuding a cold air that made it seem as if it were carved from ice.

The pill slowly flew in front of the four young jade bunny girls. Without any emotion in her voice, Divine Dream said, “Feed this pill to Lin Ming. Tell him that two hours from now, his match with Frost Dream will officially begin.

“Remember, he only has two hours.” As Divine Dream spoke, she floated away. Empyrean Vast Universe also stepped forwards and disappeared.

At this time, Lin Ming slowly opened his eyes. The first image to enter his eyes was those four curious jade bunny girls…

During his 500 days of sleep, Lin Ming had a hazy understanding of what was happening outside. He hadn’t fallen into the 100 Cycles of Samsara without being able to extract himself. Although Lin Ming hadn’t been able to compare with Hang Chi, the difference hadn’t been too great. He had the ability to resist the Wheel of Samsara, and although he had fallen unconscious, the truth was that he had voluntarily allowed himself to fall into such a state. Thus, Lin Ming knew that these four young girls had looked after him for these past 500 days.

“Thank you.”

Lin Ming softly said. Young girls of the jade bunny race were docile and gentle, with a timid personality. As Lin Ming spoke to them, they were a bit nervous. What sort of character was Lin Ming? The difference between them was like the heavens and earth!

They simply weren’t able to accept this thanks.

“S-senior-apprentice Brother Lin, please don’t say that, you will scare us to death.” A young jade bunny girl said, flustered, “Yes… yes, that’s right, Senior Divine Dream left you a message just now… you need to swallow this pill and… two hours from now… you must go to the arena stage and fight with Senior-apprentice Sister Frost Dream!”

“Fight with Frost Dream…”

Lin Ming rubbed his forehead. During that long dream, he felt as if he had lived a lifetime of tens of thousands of years. As he recalled it, even the First Martial Meeting seemed a bit distant in his mind.

“Mm… that’s right. I still haven’t fought with Frost Dream yet…”

Lin Ming clenched his fists together. He could feel that his own fists were wet with his sweat and blood, sticky and viscous. He could also feel that he had never been as strong as he was now!

…….

When Lin Ming woke up, a considerable amount of time had already passed since the conclusion of Frost Dream and Hang Chi’s battle. Over 90% of the audience was still there, not yet having left Vast Universe Heavenly Palace. However, just under 10% of the audience had begun to leave, either having ridden their spirit ships or were preparing to leave Vast Universe World.

And at this time, Vast Universe Heavenly Palace sent out news of Frost Dream’s upcoming match…

“What!? Frost Dream is coming on stage to compete once more?”

On a spirit ship that had taken off, some people heard this message passed down from Vast Universe Heavenly Palace.

“That’s too great! Let’s return and watch the match before we leave.”

Many of Frost Dream’s fans were crazily excited as they heard that Frost Dream was about to come back on stage. After Frost Dream and Hang Chi’s battle, she had entered the palace and had yet to emerge. This left many of her fans that were crowding around the contestant palaces disappointed. But now that they learned they had the chance to see her again, they were definitely delighted.

“Who is she fighting?” A middle-aged man lazily asked. He was the Elder leading these young disciples.

“She’s fighting against Lin Ming!” The young elite from before said.

“Lin Ming? He’s finally woken up? I heard that he’s been in a deep sleep for over a year. If he wakes up now, then it won’t be easy…” The middle-aged man said, a joking tone in his voice.

No one doubted Lin Ming’s talent. But in joining the First Martial Meeting, he had damaged his soul because he was trying to show off. He had been unconscious for over a year now and almost didn’t wake up. This caused everyone to feel that it was quite funny.

If one were to describe this behavior in a pleasant manner, then they would say he didn’t fear the strong and never gave up.

If one were to describe this behavior in a coarse manner, then that would be forced to the edge by their own behavior and lacking in foresight.

He had nearly died in a martial arts contest; was there any genius so stupid? Luckily he hadn’t died, otherwise that would really have been the greatest joke of all.

Although Lin Ming had woken up, many people guessed that there were still some hidden wounds left over. Even with all the precious soul recovery medicines available at an Empyrean Heavenly Palace, Lin Ming had still slept for over a year. How could his soul wounds be light?

“He’s just an impulsive little baby boy, and he also just started recovering from a severe injury. I think that Frost Dream should fight with someone from the older generation instead. If that happened… that might be worth watching.”

Hang Chi was much stronger than Lin Ming but he had still lost to Frost Dream. He hadn’t even been able to last until the end of Frost Dream’s Dreamsoul Immortal Melody before admitting defeat, let alone someone like Lin Ming. Lin Ming likely wouldn’t even be able to block a few moves from Frost Dream in his peak state, and he was wounded now too.

In the eyes of most people present, this battle would likely end before it started. This caused many of them to lose interest in seeing this fight. As for Frost Dream’s fans, they went to see her, not the fight itself.

The youth laughed, saying, “In any case, I’m going to look at Frost Dream, not her match. Then again, whoever Frost Dream competes with, it will still be the same. Who can possibly defeat her? I must say that I should thank Lin Ming. If he didn’t wake up on time then we wouldn’t be able to see her fight again!”

Chapter 1324 – Two Unrivalled Geniuses

When Lin Ming fought with the Monster Prince and Dragon Fang, his Fire Laws had reached large success of the fifth level Concept.

In terms of Laws, Lin Ming was inferior to Dragon Fang. In fact, if it weren’t for the existence of the Heretical God Tree, his Laws would be even worse than the Monster Prince’s. After all, what he comprehended were the strong Space and Time Laws.

Now, after just several days of time and a deep slumber of a year and a half, Lin Ming’s Laws had reached perfection of the fifth level and he had also traced upon the threshold of the sixth level Laws.

This was a simply inconceivable accomplishment. Moreover, he had been sleeping within a time enchantment where the Laws were all in chaos. In this situation, how could he even comprehend the Laws?

The large success of the fifth level Concept was only a single step away from reaching perfection, there were countless Divine Lord powerhouses who had failed to cross this step in their lifetimes.

“What happened to Lin Ming? Was he hiding his strength before?”

“He lost to Hang Chi so miserably, so how could he possibly have hidden his strength? He must have rapidly improved in this short period of time.”

“That’s impossible. His soul was injured before this and he had even fallen into a deep slumber, so how could he still cultivate?”

Many people found this hard to believe. Lin Ming’s talent had already aroused the envy of many heroic young elites. When Lin Ming had fought Hang Chi, many of these people believed that he was trying to show off, thus he received a deep injury which caused him to sleep for a year and a half and even possibly left behind hidden wounds. Because Lin Ming did something too stupid, these envious young elites all looked at him in a joking light.

After a year and a half, Lin Ming appeared on the arena stage and he had even made a breakthrough in the Laws. How could any of those who envied him accept this?

Someone suddenly said, “Lin Ming’s Laws might have been close to reaching perfection in the fifth level to begin with. With so many top tier geniuses in the First Martial Meeting, his comprehension of Laws was among the most disappointing. Now that he finally managed to catch up to everyone else, this isn’t strange at all.

Although these words were said with a sour taste, the facts were laid before them all. Lin Ming had indeed been weak in the aspect of Laws, but now his Laws were comparable to Dragon Fang’s.

“Just wait and see. His Laws have improved but it won’t change the result of this battle. Lin Ming’s disparity with Frost Dream is too great! Let alone perfection of the fifth level Laws, even if he reached perfection of the sixth level Laws he still wouldn’t be able to make up for their difference.”

Besides a few Empyreans of the highest levels, no one else knew of Frost Dream’s identity. But of those people that came to watch the First Martial Meeting, there were always those old fellows with an immeasurably deep vision and judgment. Although they didn’t know that Frost Dream was the reincarnated half of Divine Dream’s primordial spirit, they could confirm that Frost Dream had some unique secret. She was an invincible enigma.

In this battle, no one believed in Lin Ming. Even Jun Bluemoon’s master Old Sword, Vast Universe, or even Lin Ming himself, didn’t have full faith that he could win.

On the arena stage, Frost Dream’s eyes flashed with slight surprise. Although she knew that Lin Ming’s recent deep sleep was not as simple as it seemed, she never imagined that his strength would suddenly rise to such a degree.

“You have been cultivating for this last year and a half?”

An ephemeral true essence sound transmission spread to Lin Ming’s ears, like a clarion hosanna sung from an immortal paradise.

“Yes.” Lin Ming confidently replied.

“Cultivating in a 1:100 time flow time enchantment?”

Frost Dream was thoughtful for a moment. If one cultivated in a time enchantment, there wouldn’t be a problem if they gathered true essence to make a breakthrough. However, there would be distortions in the Laws they comprehended. This was the difference from cultivating outside. Moreover, one’s age would increase all the same within the time enchantment and the person would use up their life. Unless there was a unique circumstance, geniuses would not cultivate in a time enchantment.

“Junior-apprentice Brother Lin is truly special. Allow me to experience the achievements of your cultivation.” Frost Dream said. Then, she lifted her hand. From her palm, a rippling wave surged out, changing the world. Countless ice lotuses seemed to bloom all around Frost Dream.

The arena vanished. Lin Ming and Frost Dream arrived above a beautiful paradise.

This was the divine dream space.

After her first probing move, Frost Dream displayed her signature domain – the divine dream space!

Within the divine dream space, who could fight with her?

Within this space, Frost Dream held absolute control!

“Frost Dream is finally being serious!”

Everyone looked at Lin Ming. They didn’t think Frost Dream would use this move so early but would hold back for the first several moves against Lin Ming. But now, after just a single probing attack, Frost Dream had released the divine dream space.

Perhaps this even signaled that the match would end soon.

“This is the divine dream space… I see, so the feeling of standing within the divine dream space is like this.”

Although Lin Ming had seen the divine dream space in action before, this was his first time experiencing it himself.

After standing in the divine dream space, Lin Ming felt illusions grow thick in his mind. With just the slightest thought, what he feared the most or what he longed for the most could appear at any moment.

If a sexual deviant were to stand here, they would fall into an incomparably romantic dream, unable to ever escape.

If a miser were to stand here, they would see endless mountains of treasure, all of it belonging to them.

If a person with an unsteady will was to face Frost Dream here, Frost Dream wouldn’t even need to form anything in the divine dream space – they would simply be directly defeated.

Roar! Roar! Roar!

With a loud growling roar, that empty dreamland energy condensed together, forming into nightmare beasts within the divine dream space that barreled towards Lin Ming.

At the same time, Frost Dream gathered her hands together, forming a purple cage around Lin Ming that completely trapped him within. This cage was also formed from divine dream energy; it would not be torn apart easily.

Frost Dream caged Lin Ming in with divine dream energy so that he wouldn’t be able to dodge the attack of these nightmare beasts! These nightmare beasts were incomparably fierce. Even someone on the level of Ram Saber would have trouble dealing with several of these nightmare beasts, much less dozens of them.

Facing this attack of the divine dream space, Lin Ming poured all of his energy into his inner world. At that moment, an enchanting blood red lotus slowly bloomed behind him.

This was the Prime Emperor Lotus Flower!

The Prime Emperor Lotus Flower released the vast and boundless breath of the Great Dao that recklessly struck the divine dream space. In that instant, for a radius of 100 feet around Lin Ming, all of those blooming ice lotuses rapidly shattered, turning into countless shards. Even the cage around Lin Ming wildly trembled as if it would break apart at any moment.

With his strength, Lin Ming had shoved open a space within the divine dream space!

Puff! Puff! Puff!

Dozens of nightmare beasts broke into the grandmist space. Within the domain of the all-annihilating Grandmist Laws they began to rapidly weaken. Some smaller nightmare beasts even let out miserable cries.

Nightmare beasts were strong, and even Lin Ming would find it hard to deal with dozens of them. But, as long as these nightmare beasts left the divine dream space and entered the grandmist space, they were weakened to a near negligible level to Lin Ming.

At this time, Lin Ming took a step forwards. The Phoenix Blood Spear in his hands swept out. In that moment, the Phoenix Blood Spear was like a red dragon wildly raging around. Spear light shot out, and with several popping sounds, dozens of nightmare beasts were all killed by Lin Ming, their blood splashing all around!

After killing all of these nightmare beasts, Lin Ming’s long spear returned.

Chi-la!

The divine dream energy cage around Lin Ming was also torn apart by him!

The grandmist space constantly radiated outwards, forcibly pushing away all of the Divine Dream Laws within 100 feet of him. Although this was only a radius of 100 feet, this was still amazing enough.

The audience was shocked as they saw this. With his own domain, Lin Ming had stiffly opened up his own dominion within the divine dream space.

From start until end, the divine dream space had been the top domain of the First Martial Meeting. No one had been able to contend with it, not even Hang Chi.

Now, Lin Ming was using the grandmist space to resist the divine dream space. Although the grandmist space was clearly suppressed, this was still an exceedingly rare event! At least before now, this situation had never appeared.

“How is this happening?”

“Why did Lin Ming’s strength increase so much?”

At this time, no one thought that the reason Lin Ming and Frost Dream’s battle had reached this stage was because of his luck. Perhaps his strength truly had rapidly risen!

“Wasn’t he unconscious in a deep sleep? Who was the one who said his soul was injured? If his soul was injured, causing him to fall unconscious for a year and a half, how could his strength have grown so much?”

When Lin Ming was ‘wounded’ and in a deep sleep, many people had laughed at him and called him a fool who only knew how to show off and didn’t know just how deep he could go. But now, everything indicated that what happened to Lin Ming wasn’t some simple soul wound. Rather, he had experienced some unimaginable transformation.

He might have even experienced a sudden enlightenment or made a breakthrough!

Those people that called Lin Ming a fool were the ones who felt like fools now.

And in the honored seating section, some Holy Lord and World King level old men had already realized that a change had occurred within Lin Ming’s body. From the moment he appeared, his aura had been different.

“This Lin Ming isn’t simple at all. There were some people before this who said that if it weren’t for Frost Dream, his talent would only be inferior to Xiao Moxian’s and even comparable to Hang Chi’s. But now it seems that they all underestimated him!”

“Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian, those are truly the two unrivalled geniuses of this generation!”

“Yes, but what a pity… Frost Dream is simply too strong. She may have displayed the divine dream space, but this isn’t her true strength. Frost Dream isn’t someone that you can apply common sense to.”

Even if Lin Ming displayed an even greater strength, it would be nothing but an illusion in front of Frost Dream!

On the arena stage, Frost Dream looked towards Lin Ming. No matter how much she pushed the divine dream space, she was only able to suppress Lin Ming’s grandmist space; she wasn’t able to fully crush it.

Frost Dream slowly raised her right hand. Beneath her, more and more ice lotuses condensed, blooming in full glory. They spread out, covering the entire arena stage with endless flowers of ice, just like some fantastical dream.

These ice lotuses were difficult to destroy and even slowly permeated Lin Ming’s grandmist space. Lin Ming’s eyebrows show up. He could feel that in this instant, Frost Dream’s aura had risen once again.

She was truly worthy of being called the number one genius amongst the junior generation. She was an unfathomable existence!

In that moment, mystical dreamland energy gathered in front of Frost Dream, condensing together into a thick tome.

As she gently opened this tome, Frost Dream clearly said, “Dream Interpretation Scripture!”

Dreams represented a person’s desires. The power of divine dream was in truth a type of the power of faith. When the power of faith of all living beings came together, this power would be terrifying.

Chapter 1327 – Final Chapter of the Dreamsoul

The final chapter of the Dreamsoul Immortal Melody!

After hearing Frost Dream’s words, all of the heroic young elites present held their breaths. When Frost Dream fought with Hang Chi, she had said that once she completed the Dreamsoul Immortal Melody, he would lose without a doubt. That meant that the final chapter of the Dreamsoul Immortal Melody must contain some indescribably powerful force!

“The final chapter of the Dreamsoul can eliminate all Laws of this world and wash away even the Great Dao. Try your best to withstand this.”

Frost Dream was unable to fully grasp the might of the Dreamsoul’s final chapter. Lin Ming might be able to defend against this move, but he might even be severely wounded. Perhaps he could even die here. With the fighting having reached this stage, it was impossible for Frost Dream to tell Lin Ming to give up. They could only fight this out.

At this time, deep within Vast Universe Heavenly Palace, Empyrean Divine Dream’s expression stirred. She seemed as if she wanted to stop Frost Dream, but after hesitating for several breaths of time, she finally shook her head. No matter how Frost Dream and Lin Ming’s battle went, she believed that Lin Ming’s destiny was so great and dreadful that he wouldn’t die here in such a simple manner. And as her reincarnation, Frost Dream was also the same.

The zither melody changed once more. That Buddha-killing harmony with its profound killing intent once more returned to a peaceful tune. No one imagined that the final chapter of the Dreamsoul, with its vast and boundless momentum that seemed to look down at the world with disdain, would actually return to such a gentle quietness. For a time, within the Immortal Melody Pure Lands, countless crystal clear flower petals fell from the air, lightly landing on Frost Dream’s long hair, shoulders, and even her icy blue dress. As she sat down in the Immortal Melody Pure Lands, her image seemed carved into eternity.

At this time, a mysterious black crystal began to emerge behind Frost Dream, becoming larger and larger. Within the Dreamsoul Immortal Melody’s final chapter, a black crystal finally gathered. This black crystal was shaped like a cube with six even sides. It looked common, and even slightly plain, but as Lin Ming saw it his mind violently shook!

This was… the Magic Cube!

In this final moment, Frost Dream had summoned the phantom of the Magic Cube!

On this black cube was carved countless dark inscriptions. Lin Ming had seen these markings before; he had a profound impression of them!

In the past when he first obtained the Magic Cube, the Magic Cube had these black traces carved on it, each one different and unique. Even now, Lin Ming still didn’t know what they meant.

Lin Ming never thought that in Frost Dream’s final chapter of the Dreamsoul Immortal Melody, she would actually use her own energy to condense a phantom of the Magic Cube!

“Is the Magic Cube not in my body?”

Lin Ming’s thoughts stirred. His thoughts immediately touched upon the Magic Cube space within his body; he found that Mo Eversnow and Fishy were both safely dwelling there.

The Magic Cube was still in his body – he could not be wrong about this.

“I understand. Frost Dream’s Magic Cube phantom has the aura of the Magic Cube, but it is still far from being able to compare to the true Magic Cube!”

The Magic Cube was a divine tool of the soul; it complemented Divine Dream Heavenly Palace’s Divine Dream Law perfectly. If so, then Divine Dream Heavenly Palace must have some inheritance related to the Magic Cube!

“Could they… possess a replica of the Magic Cube?”

This thought immediately flashed through Lin Ming’s mind. Although the Magic Cube phantom that Frost Dream summoned had a completely similar appearance to the true Magic Cube, its aura was far lacking. If it was said that Divine Dream Heavenly Palace had a replica of the Magic Cube, that was highly possible.

For a time, Lin Ming felt the Magic Cube within his body restlessly stirring, as if it wanted to swallow the black cube above Frost Dream.

Lin Ming wasn’t able to summon the Magic Cube on his own initiative yet, but if the Magic Cube began to move by itself, Lin Ming could use his own energy to move it and have it launch an attack. If this happened then the Magic Cube would undoubtedly attack Frost Dream!

Once the Magic Cube attacked her, that would be the true Magic Cube against the phantom Magic Cube formed by Frost Dream’s own energy. The result of that match up could be imagined.

The Magic Cube was a divine tool. Or, to better put it, it was a supreme spiritual object that surpassed the limits of a divine tool. From the universe’s essence, energy, and divine, this was a spiritual object produced by the ‘divine’ of the universe.

The Magic Cube was deeply sleeping within Lin Ming and no one was able to discover its existence. Even when Lin Ming traveled deep underneath Immemorial Imperial City and met the artifact spirit of the Ancient Elysium Seal with its 3.6 billion years of experience, even that artifact spirit didn’t know of the Magic Cube’s existence. Only when Lin Ming summoned it did it find out.

As long as the Magic Cube was within Lin Ming’s body then he would be safe.

But, once he took out the Magic Cube to launch an attack, its existence would be revealed to the hundreds of millions of people present!

Most people didn’t know what the Magic Cube was, but it was impossible for Empyrean Divine Dream to not know. Moreover, the hidden Tian Mingzi would inevitably recognize the Magic Cube. If he were to reveal the existence of the Magic Cube then he would be locked down and hunted by Tian Mingzi.

This was something that Lin Ming couldn’t help but consider.

Even if it was Empyrean Divine Dream, Lin Ming still didn’t fully trust her.

Empyrean Divine Dream was someone that dual cultivated energy and soul. She also possessed a replica of the Magic Cube. If he exposed Empyrean Primordius’s inheritance in front of her then she wouldn’t care. Empyrean Divine Dream and Empyrean Primordius were both characters at similar levels. There was no way she would give up her own Laws to inherit Empyrean Primordius’s legacy.

But the Magic Cube was different!

It was an extremely precious treasure, especially to someone like Empyrean Divine Dream!

The Ancient Elysium Seal’s artifact spirit was not a human. It also had a mission to fulfill and its eventual death was arriving soon. If it obtained the Magic Cube then it wouldn’t find it of much use. But Empyrean Divine Dream was different. If she obtained the Magic Cube, she might even have methods to use it to directly become a True Divinity.

Lin Ming didn’t dare to risk such a danger.

At the very least, using the Magic Cube to attack Frost Dream wasn’t his own true strength.

Frost Dream had played the Dreamsoul’s final chapter and condensed the Magic Cube replica phantom with her own energy, displaying the absolute limits of her strength. But, if Lin Ming were to counterattack with the Magic Cube, this simply wouldn’t be meaningful to him.

Jun Bluemoon was also in a similar situation with the Yin Yang Soul Sword. When Jun Bluemoon fought Lin Ming, because he had used the power of the Yin Yang Soul Sword instead of his own, he had admitted defeat on his own initiative. Otherwise, both Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian wouldn’t have been his match.

Jun Bluemoon didn’t do so, and Lin Ming also made the same choice.

Lin Ming took a deep breath and poured all of his energy into the black hole seed.

By exceeding the limits of his body to revolve the Divine Seal Art to the limit, the blood vessels on Lin Ming’s arms seemed ready to burst open.

Lin Ming was well aware of just how strong Frost Dream’s final attack was. Even after he used Eternal Darkness, she had still begun playing the final chapter of the Dreamsoul. This proved that Frost Dream was confident she could break through the Eternal Darkness.

“Heretical God Tree!”

Lin Ming shouted out loud. Behind him, the phantom of the Heretical God Tree appeared.

In that instant, the power of thunder and fire heavenly tribulation contained within the Heretical God Tree completely erupted forth, weaving together into a sea of red and purple energy around Lin Ming!

Heavenly Dao Judgment!

Lin Ming suddenly thrust out his spear. The power of thunder and fire heavenly tribulation gathered together, wrapping around the black hole seed in a nebula as it hurtled towards Frost Dream!

Puff puff puff!

The blood vessels on Lin Ming’s arms exploded, spilling forth blood. Many of his meridians tore apart and even his organs broke in multiple places. This was Lin Ming’s strongest attack, and also an attack that exceeded the bearing capacity of his body!

With this strike, Lin Ming’s attack violently collided with the Magic Cube phantom produced by Dreamsoul’s final chapter.

In that instant, the space within an area of several miles of the Divine Realm was completely torn apart. This was no longer shaking, but true tearing.

A blinding divine brilliance flooded the entire arena, causing everyone to shield their eyes.

A brutal and terrifying energy wildly surged outwards. Vast Cosmos personally took action and used his own domain to melt away the violent fluctuations of energy and avoid disaster in the spectator stands. Otherwise, those young elites with weaker cultivations simply wouldn’t be able to withstand this.

“This is too terrifying!”

“It’s unimaginable. I can’t believe Lin Ming is powerful to such a degree!”

“Just who won in the end?”

Everyone peered towards the center of the martial stage. But above the arena, the eruption of the dark black hole had formed a special dark void area that isolated everyone’s sight. It was impossible to know what the situation was like.

Within that void of darkness, Lin Ming knelt on the ground, supporting himself with the Phoenix Blood Spear. His clothes were already dyed red with blood and blood was dripping down both of his arms. His meridians and organs were broken in several places and he had lost nearly all of his combat strength.

And in front of Lin Ming, Frost Dream had already lost support of her body. Although she was still floating in the air and hadn’t yet fallen down, she was also severely wounded. From the start of the First Martial Meeting until now, this was Frost Dream’s first injury, and it was a heavy one too.

Because of her severe injuries, the mist that concealed her expression had dispersed, revealing an unrivalled appearance as beautiful as the moon.

Her snow white skin seemed like perfection formed by the heavens, like a newly budded ice lotus on top of a snow-capped mountain, without the slightest hint of the mortal world. But now, her enchanting complexion was slightly pale and her icy blue hair was also scattered down about her. Blood spilled out from the corners of her lips, giving her a point of pity and tenderness that moved the heart.

“You…”

Frost Dream wanted to use an illusion technique to conceal her appearance once more, but because the backlash from the Dreamsoul’s final chapter was too great, the energy movement within her caused her injuries to erupt again and the blood dripping from her lips to be an even deeper red.

Changing methods, Frost Dream covered up her face with a sheet of fine gauze.

Her eyebrows were furrowed. Her beauty was lovely and moving, even during her weakness.

Chapter 1329 – Secret of the Great Calamity

“Junior Lin Ming greets Senior Empyrean Divine Dream and Senior Empyrean Vast Universe.”

Lin Ming first respectfully bowed. Then, he said, “If seniors allow, this junior has some matters that he hopes two seniors can provide guidance with.”

“Speak.” Divine Dream casually waved her hand and the surroundings rapidly changed. The three of them immediately arrived in a charming spring prairie with fragrant flowers and trees all about. Springs trickled, beautiful to the eyes.

This was an enchantment that Empyrean Divine Dream laid down. Within this enchantment, it was impossible for anyone else to spy on their conversation.

“Seniors, this junior would like to ask about a previous matter first. As long as this junior has been able to enter the top three of the Earth Proclamation then I should have gained the rights to enter an Empyrean Heavenly Palace and study a transcendent divine might. This junior would like to inquire whether or not I have the option to choose.”

“Oh?” Empyrean Divine Dream faintly smiled, “What do you want to choose?”

“What this junior wishes to choose is the Divine Dream Law created by Senior!”

Empyrean Divine Dream was not surprised by Lin Ming’s honest words, but Empyrean Vast Universe smiled. He heartily laughed, “Young man, it seems that you don’t have a liking for my Vast Universe Heavenly Palace’s transcendent divine might!”

“Senior, this junior certainly does not mean that. The transcendent divine might that Senior Vast Universe established is wonderful, able to open multiple inner worlds and allow a martial artist to have an amount of true essence far surpassing all others of their level. This junior also wishes to study it, but it’s only that relatively speaking, the Divine Dream Law is more useful to this junior.”

“Hehe, according to what I can see, you have quite a few transcendent divine mights on you!” Empyrean Vast Universe suddenly said. Ignoring the elementary transcendent divine might that Lin Ming had created as well as the tiny bit of the Divine Dream Law that he had comprehended earlier, he had three different sets of transcendent divine mights. He possessed the Heretical God Force, Primordius martial intent, and also the extremely high level but very incomplete Divine Seal Art.

Lin Ming replied, “This junior’s luck has been good, thus I have been able to acquire the inheritances of some seniors thanks to some accidental opportunities.”

“Mm… you have a good number of transcendent divine mights. If you study too many then you won’t be able to bring them to a high enough level. Choosing to develop one or two of them is the wisest choice.”

Every transcendent divine might was enough for a genius to cultivate all the way to the Empyrean realm. If one studied too many, although one could comprehend more Laws and enhance their strength, they might lack too much time and energy.

For instance, Hang Chi had in fact only learnt a single transcendent divine might. From the time he stepped onto the road of martial arts he had been thoroughly studying the Wheel of Samsara all the way until now.

Although Lin Ming knew this, he would still walk the path he had chosen. This was just like how he chose to dual cultivate in body and energy, and then chose to triple cultivate in essence, energy, and divine.

“The Divine Dream Law… you may learn it, but I shall not accept you as a disciple.”

As Empyrean Divine Dream spoke, Empyrean Vast Universe was a bit surprised on the side. Lin Ming was such a good apprentice and he also delivered himself to their gates, so why wouldn’t she accept him?

“Divine Dream, are you not accepting Lin Ming because it is the custom of your Divine Dream Heavenly Palace to not accept male disciples? I don’t know when you decided on these rules, but isn’t Lin Ming worth breaking them for, at least once?”

Empyrean Vast Universe directly said. In his opinion, Lin Ming’s potential future achievements were limitless. If he joined Divine Dream Heavenly Palace, then with Frost Dream also there, who could still hope to compete with them?

The only thing worth considering would be the fact that Lin Ming and Frost Dream were two absolutely proud geniuses of heaven. If they were to stay together for a long time then they might form feelings between each other that would multiply. The resulting consequences might violate Divine Dream’s ultimate taboo.

The truth was that Empyrean Vast Universe also had a faint guess regarding Frost Dream’s status. If Frost Dream was truly the reincarnated half of Divine Dream’s primordial spirit then the previous matter would truly be a grave issue.

Of course, he couldn’t directly speak about this.

Empyrean Divine Dream shook her said, saying, “I have a different reason for not accepting Lin Ming as my disciple. In addition, there is another matter that I will be honest about. Lin Ming, you are not suited to study the Divine Dream Law because… you do not possess spirit source. Think about your decision carefully.”

“Spirit source?”

Lin Ming was startled. He had also heard this term before, but as for what spirit source truly was, he still wasn’t sure.

Empyrean Divine Dream said, “A human has essence, energy and divine, and the universe also possesses essence, energy and divine. The essence of the universe is all the matter that exists, the energy of the universe is all the myriad energies that exist, and the divine is represented by the Heavenly Dao Laws. All three of these aspects have a source which represents their very beginning. Do you know of grandmist energy?”

Lin Ming nodded. He was familiar with grandmist energy; it was the foundation of his grandmist space.

“Yes, a great part of the reason that Empyrean Primordius was able to wield the Grandmist Laws was because he possessed a tremendous amount of grandmist energy. Grandmist energy is the source of all matter.

“Besides grandmist energy, there are also two other kinds of sources in this world. They are genesis energy and spirit source. The two of them correspond to ‘energy’ and ‘divine’ respectively. The reason that I could create the Divine Dream Law was by relying on spirit source!

“My Divine Dream Heavenly Palace has a very small number of people, only several hundred disciples. As for the disciples I have personally accepted, for all these millions of years, there have only been 10. The reason is because of a limitation in my requirements. All of my disciples must possess spirit source. However, you do not, thus you are destined to make no progress in the Divine Dream Law.”

As Empyrean Divine Dream explained this, Lin Ming was suddenly enlightened. No wonder there were so few people in Divine Dream Heavenly Palace.

Grandmist energy, genesis energy, spirit source, these were the three foundations that represented the essence, energy, and divine of the universe. This was the first time Lin Ming had heard of this.

“Now, are you still determined to study the Divine Dream Law?” Empyrean Divine Dream slowly said as she looked at Lin Ming.

“I am.” Lin Ming replied without hesitation. The triple cultivation of essence, energy, and divine was related to the Laws of the 33 Layered Heavens, he certainly couldn’t give up on it.

“Very well…” Empyrean Divine Dream no longer opposed. “Since you insist, I will not refuse you. I only hope that you do not waste your time.”

As the one who founded the Divine Dream Law, Empyrean Divine Dream could confirm that it was impossible to cultivate it without spirit source. However, she also didn’t wish to meddle in Lin Ming’s growth. She believed that Lin Ming had his own wonderful destiny to follow, and if he were subject to the intervention of others, he would never have reached this step.

“I thank Senior Divine Dream for the help.” Lin Ming happily said. He only wished to learn the Divine Dream Law; he didn’t care whether or not he formed any good relations with Divine Dream’s disciples.

“Senior Divine Dream, this junior has a question concerning the great calamity 3.6 billion years ago. This junior would like to ask – just what is the great calamity?”

On the Divine Seal Altar, Lin Ming had seen some remnant scenes of the great calamity.

Empyrean Divine Seal had stood atop the Divine Seal Altar. With Empyreans as generals and Holy Lords as soldiers, the God Beasts that soared through the universe had blocked out the heavens like massive celestial bodies. This scene had left a tremendous impact on him!

“The great calamity…” Upon mentioning this term, there was an ethereal tone to Empyrean Divine Dream’s tone.

“Countless years have passed since the birth of the universe; no one knows just how old this world is. It could be a trillion years or even a quadrillion years or more. And during this time, martial arts civilization has been destroyed many, many times, with countless worlds being destroyed and reborn. If this universe was truly destroyed then even a True Divinity would not be able to escape. If one looks back through the trillion plus years of the universe’s history, there have been many instances of this so-called ‘great calamity’. Facing the vast universe, even Empyreans are nothing more than ants.”

Empyrean Divine Dream suddenly emitted a deep feeling. Lin Ming was silent, respectfully listening to her.

“Now, the great calamity of 3.6 billion years ago should be referring to the fading of the barriers of the 33 Layered Heavens.” Empyrean Divine Dream softly said. But as Lin Ming heard this, he felt a chill run up his spine. “Barriers of the 33 Layered Heavens? What is that?”

The Concept of the 33 Layered Heavens was part of the Laws that Lin Ming cultivated. But as to what the 33 Layered Heavens truly were, he had no idea even now.

Empyrean Divine Dream said, “You should know that there are countless divergent mystic realms in the Divine Realm, right?”

Lin Ming nodded. He had gone to two divergent mystic realms before. One was the God Beast Mystic Realm governed by the four God Beast Clans, and the other was the Red Desolate Mystic Realm governed by Carefree Island.

In these two mystic realms, Lin Ming had harvested a supreme dragon bone one time and obtained a massive wealth the second time.

“The barriers that Senior refers to, are these the barriers that separate the divergent mystic realms?” Lin Ming suddenly asked as he recalled something.

Within the Divine Realm there were countless divergent mystic realms, each with tremendous amounts of wealth. However, wanting to enter them was difficult. This was because there existed barriers between the Divine Realm and these divergent mystic realms.

In order to pass through this barrier, one had to go through specialized transmission arrays and also consume a massive amount of violet sun stones. Also, the person transmitted couldn’t have too high a cultivation. The higher the cultivation, the more energy was required to transmit that person.

It was also because of this reason that no matter if it were the four God Beast Clans entering the God Beast Mystic Realm or Carefree Island entering the Red Desolate Mystic Realm, they had to consume a considerable amount of resources each time.

“Yes, the barriers of these divergent mystic realms are in truth the barriers that divide the 33 Layered Heavens. The Divine Realm’s endless divergent mystic realms are in truth the gaps between the Divine Realm and these other realms. There are 33 Layered Heavens and the Divine Realm is only one of them; its name is the Divine Shifting Heavens.

Empyrean Divine Dream’s words were slow and calm, but when she spoke them they struck Lin Ming’s mind like a titanic steel ball!

The heavens had 33 layers, and the Divine Realm was only one of them!?

This was…!?

Lin Ming was completely mind-boggled. He had already felt that the Divine Realm was vast to the point of being incomparably terrifying, but now he learned that the Divine Realm was only one realm of these 33 realms?

He never knew just what the legends of the 33 Layered Heavens meant. But now he knew just what the 33 Layered Heavens were. The ‘heavens’ meant other realms altogether, not the skies above.

Empyrean Divine Dream continued, “There are barrier walls that separate the 33 Layered Heavens. These barrier walls can separate all existences. The more powerful an existence is, the more difficult it is to cross. However, periodically, like the tide, these barrier walls will weaken to the point that they vanish altogether. The great calamity of 3.6 billion years ago was also because these barrier walls vanished.

“Beyond the Divine Realm there are alien races that are the mortal enemies of humanity. Moreover, they covet the resources of the Divine Realm beyond all reasoning. This leads to great wars between the different races. In the past, a bloody war swept through the entire Divine Realm, and nearly all martial arts masters died because of it! The leader of the martial arts world at that time – Empyrean Divine Seal, also perished because of this…”

As Empyrean Divine Dream spoke, Lin Ming could feel various emotions surging within him. “Alien races?”

“Yes, these alien races possess different Laws and cultivation methods from humanity. In truth, the Concept of the 33 Layered Heavens that you practice is said to be amongst the highest of Concepts because it is suitable for all worlds within the 33 Layered Heavens; this means that it is also suitable for the alien races.”

Empyrean Divine Dream’s words were astonishing. As Lin Ming heard this he was incomparably shocked. So that’s how it was! This was the true face of the 33 Layered Heavens Laws, and what Empyrean Divine Seal cultivated in the past were these 33 Layered Heavens Laws.

Chapter 1337 – Eavesdropping

“We still haven’t found it but that is also reasonable. The primordial epoch spirit root possesses its own wisdom. If we want to find it, it won’t be easy. But, that is unimportant. Our Skydark Holy Lands have sent out a million disciples as well as countless other wandering cultivators. Finding the primordial epoch spirit root is something that will happen sooner or later. Still, there is another matter that I’m afraid won’t be so easy to complete…”

The bald youth thoughtfully said. Many of those present simply didn’t know what this other matter was.

“It’s fine, you can all go now.”

The bald youth waved his hand, sending the outer court disciples of the Skydark Holy Lands as well as the outer court disciples to rest. “Wait. You right there, what was your name?”

The bald youth pointed at Lin Ming.

“Reporting to Senior-apprentice Brother, my surname is Duanmu, Duanmu Qun.”

Lin Ming casually gave out Duanmu Qun’s name. Duanmu Qun was a fey from the Holy Demon Continent.

“Duanmu Qun, mm, your performance was good today. Although your cultivation methods are rough and your foundation isn’t too solid, you can be considered quite good for a wandering cultivator. Tomorrow you can join our group!”

In the process of searching for the primordial epoch spirit root, they had inevitably experienced bitter battles with some roaming packs of demon beasts. The bald youth had originally planned to use Lin Ming as cannon fodder and sacrifice him, but they never thought that Lin Ming would live by relying on his own ability. Not just that, but he even possessed the strength to kill several strong demon beasts. This surprised the bald youth a little. Out of all the wandering cultivators he had met in these past days, Lin Ming was definitely the strongest one.

Thus, the bald youth dispelled any notion of sending Lin Ming to his death. Instead, he decided to bring Lin Ming into his squad. At a critical moment, Lin Ming could be a decent help, and in dangerous situations, he could even be used as a shield to save the strength of his team as much as possible.

“Well done. After all this is over, I will petition the sect to accept you as a caretaker disciple.”

The bald youth patted Lin Ming’s shoulder, once again putting forth this sweet enticement.

Lin Ming faked an overjoyed expression. He cupped his hands across his chest and said, “Thank you very much for recognizing me Senior-apprentice Brother. I only hope I can live up to your expectations.”

“Haha, well said.” The bald youth said, his face full of smiles. But, in his heart he was actually thinking, “These wandering cultivators are far too easy to trick. They are nothing but ant-like characters that struggle on the edge of death every day. Just a tiny advantage can lure them to cross seas of fire or water. This fellow wants to become a disciple of my Skydark Holy Lands? He needs to live through this first!”

As Lin Ming and the others went to rest, the bald youth and the several other core disciples gathered in the main hall of the camp.

These people were all secret disciples of Tian Mingzi. Although they were secret disciples, it was extremely difficult for them to see Tian Mingzi, much less receive his guidance. But, compared to ordinary disciples, their status was much higher!

In the Skydark Holy Lands, Tian Mingzi was the one and only king. This was like a mortal nation where all power and authority was controlled by the emperor. Even a distant relative was still a royal relative; who would dare to offend them?

As the several of them gathered in the main hall, one of them took out an array disc from their spatial ring. Then, they took out a violet crystal and inserted it into the array disc, creating an enchantment in the space above.

The enchantment of this array disc was able to isolate the senses of outsiders to avoid spies; it was extremely secure. Even a Divine Lord realm martial artist would find it hard to break through. Moreover, once the enchantment was broken, the array disc would react and alert everyone. This was an essential item for the disciples of the Skydark Holy Lands to discuss important matters.

The space enchantment flickered. Within it, the disciples of the Skydark Holy Lands never imagined that a faint strand of divine dream energy would infiltrate their security, clearly observing their conversation.

After cultivating the Divine Dream Law to now, Lin Ming’s soul force had become incomparably powerful. Although his senses couldn’t cut through space, it wasn’t difficult to break through this sort of enchantment.

Lin Ming could see that these young disciples were at least at the core level of the Skydark Holy Lands. There were many things that they must be privy too, especially about the primordial epoch spirit root. They might even know why Tian Mingzi was collecting so many body transformation medicines.

“The primordial epoch spirit root is truly difficult to find!” After the enchantment spread out, a disciple began to complain.

“That is normal. The primordial epoch spirit root isn’t easy to deal with to begin with. Even if we find it we cannot act rashly. Luckily, the sect has sent out many disciples and we can form a giant sealing array to lock it in. There is also a massive number of wandering cultivators that we can use as cannon fodder. If we can obtain the primordial epoch spirit root, that will absolutely be a great contribution. We will obtain endless rewards from the sect. There might even be a small chance for us to study the transcendent divine might of our Skydark Holy Lands.”

As the disciples heard the term transcendent divine might, all of them were extremely excited. Although the Skydark Holy Land’s transcendent divine might was incomplete to an extreme degree, it was still an inheritance that would cause one’s blood to boil with desire.

“I wonder just what Honorable Master has been planning recently. Not only does he want us to find precious body transformation medicines, but he even wants us to search for Lin Ming’s whereabouts… this Lin Ming came in second place at the Divine Realm First Martial Meeting. But even though he came second, the truth is that he is more or less on the same level as the first place Frost Dream. It could even be said that within the Divine Sea realm, he is the number one young elite of the entire Divine Realm. Compared to him, Elder Senior-apprentice Brother just can’t compare at all.

As they discussed the plan to search for the primordial epoch spirit root, one of them suddenly changed topics to Lin Ming.

Lin Ming was startled. “Looking for me?”

Lin Ming didn’t believe that Tian Mingzi was searching for him because he wanted to drink some tea and ask him if he wanted to join the Skydark Holy Lands.

As Lin Ming thought of this, he realized that there was a possibility that Tian Mingzi had discovered his relation with Mo Eversnow. He might have even guessed that the Magic Cube was in his body!

That was undoubtedly dangerous to him. Once news of the Magic Cube was revealed, there might be no place for him to take shelter beneath the heavens.

Lin Ming took a deep breath, calming himself down. He rapidly recalled every moment where he might have revealed his identity. “Miss Mo, could Tian Mingzi have seen some clue from the Celestial Tyrant Manual?”

Lin Ming had used the Celestial Tyrant Manual’s Hundred Layered Waves in the First Martial Meeting. And, the Celestial Tyrant Manual was an inheritance of the Verdant Feather Holy Lands.

“No.”

Mo Eversnow shook her head. “The Celestial Tyrant Manual was originally an inheritance stored away by the Verdant Feather Holy Lands. In the entire Verdant Feather Holy Lands, there was no one besides me who cultivated it. Even Tian Mingzi was no exception. He simply doesn’t know just what it is like to cultivate the Celestial Tyrant Manual. Moreover, the Celestial Tyrant Manual is an ancient body transformation cultivation method passed down from ancient times 3.6 billion years ago. In the Divine Realm, it might not have been uniquely possessed by the Verdant Feather Holy Lands. However, I cannot confirm this.”

Lin Ming nodded. He calmed his thoughts and continued to listen on.

“Do you think that Honorable Master might have realized the secrets on Lin Ming’s body?” A disciple suddenly asked. The bald youth frowned, coldly saying, “Stop carelessly making assumptions! I do not know the reason that Honorable Master is looking for Lin Ming; it might not be to deal with him to begin with. In any case, we only have to follow orders. Above all, this matter must be kept absolutely secret. Lin Ming’s current status is too sensitive. We can only inform other core disciples of this. As for those wandering disciples, we cannot divulge this information otherwise this secret will spread out.”

“Understood!”

“Good. Then we will continue like this. Tomorrow we will look for the primordial epoch spirit root again.”

After the several disciples finished speaking, Lin Ming was lost in his thoughts.

Tian Mingzi was searching for materials to refine body transformation pills and also searching for his own whereabouts – just what was he plotting?

“Lin Ming, Tian Mingzi’s thoughts are extremely deep and hidden. Even though he was part of the Verdant Feather Holy Lands for so many years, I have never completely understood him. His talent and his strength have always been a mystery, even up until now. He is a highly ambitious character that doesn’t move according to common sense. Although I don’t know what he wants with you, you cannot allow him to find you.”

“I understand. Before I have the strength to truly struggle with a Great World King, I cannot come into contact with Tian Mingzi at all. Otherwise that is simply allowing others to play with my life.”

Even though he said this, Lin Ming still didn’t want to miss out on the primordial epoch spirit root. The appearance changing technique that Lin Ming learnt from Divine Dream Heavenly Palace, when used by a Divine Lord realm powerhouse, could even fool a Great World King. Lin Ming could rely on the Magic Cube to use this technique. Moreover, it would be difficult for him to encounter Tian Mingzi here.

Thinking like this, Lin Ming sat down and began to meditate. He was always cultivating; diligence and hard work was one of the required talents of a genius.

Night passed without words. Early next morning, the sun shined through the canopy of Demondawn Jungle, illuminating the endless canopy of trees. The disciples of the Skydark Holy Lands began their missions for the day.

Lin Ming went with the bald youth’s squad, shuttling back and forth all over the jungle. They encountered packs of vicious demon beasts, but Lin Ming performed well during all of these battles. This surprised the bald youth more and more. Lin Ming’s strength was far greater than that of other wandering cultivators.

As the squad ventured deeper into Demondawn Jungle, the surrounding miasma became increasingly thick. In front of them, thick mud began to appear, just like they were wandering into a swamp.

“This black swamp…” The bald youth frowned. According to what he knew, this sort of terrain in Demondawn Jungle was often infested with ambushing demon beasts. As for the miasma and black swamp, that could block their senses. Thus, walking through this area made one particularly susceptible to sneak attacks. One needed a guide to lead one through this area. With a guide, once a danger appeared, everyone else could quickly react and leave.

The bald youth looked at Lin Ming, “We’re going to explore this area. Duanmu Qun, you walk first. An hour from now we’ll have Zhong Feng replace you.”

The Zhong Feng that the bald youth referred to was a very large fellow with a peak late Divine Sea cultivation.

As Lin Ming heard this bald youth’s words, his expression stiffened. Without a doubt, leading the way here was the most dangerous position.

The bald youth coldly said, “What are you so afraid of? With us behind you, are you scared we’ll let you suffer a loss? Moreover, we’ll even replace you after a while.”

“Then… alright. Several senior-apprentice brothers, your reactions must be faster this time. If danger truly appears then I might not be able to withstand it.” Lin Ming said, a bit weakly.

“Haha, don’t worry!” The bald youth agreed, smiling. He certainly wanted to preserve Lin Ming’s life as far as possible, but this was because Lin Ming was still useful. If there truly was some kind of danger then he could only abandon Lin Ming.

Like this, Lin Ming walked in front of the squad. With his senses, he could sense every single movement in the surrounding 1000 miles. Not even miasma or the black swamp could hope to stop him!

After entering 100 feet into this black swamp, Lin Ming discovered that 100 feet away, there was a powerful python laying in ambushF, its large black eyes greedily staring at him.

Chapter 1340 – Murdering Others and Stealing Blood

Woosh! Woosh! Woosh!

Countless root hairs shot up like lances. Two lower Skydark Holy Land disciples had their protective true essence directly pierced through. With a light shattering sound, these root hairs were like vipers as they drilled into the two disciples’ chests. All of their flesh and blood essence was sucked out by these roots hairs. Before long, the two of them had become dried up corpses.

Hu – !

A rich blood energy enveloped the surrounded world. Within this world, everything had turned a light red. The thick smell of blood swirled about, emitting a vast and boundless strength. This was the atmosphere of chaos.

“Domain!”

Lin Ming was startled. This primordial epoch spirit root was actually able to cultivate its own domain! It was almost the same as a human martial artist!

Within this domain, there were the auras of the Blood Laws, Grandmist Laws, and Wood Laws. Although these Laws didn’t seem exquisite to Lin Ming and there were also numerous loopholes within them, by relying on its own profound foundation, the primordial epoch spirit root was able to cover a hundred miles in its domain, covering everyone within!

“Line up!”

The blue-clothed Hall Master Luo suddenly threw down a flag. The flag fluttered in the air, completely scattering the bloody atmosphere. The five Divine Lord Hall Masters flew around Hall Master Luo, each one bringing out their own magic tools. For a time, the six of them fused their strength together, forming the phantom of a six-armed demon king behind them. This was the demon art of the Skydark Holy Lands – The Six-Armed Halcyon Lord. Although this wasn’t a transcendent divine might, these six Divine Lord powerhouses had already practiced this cultivation method for 10,000 years. Now that they joined forces, countless demon king phantoms shot out from the flag. Ghosts cried and demons roared, the sound ringing through the ears.

The phantom of the Six-armed Halcyon Lord battled with the primordial epoch spirit root’s domain!

“Darklight, the Myriad Blood Demon Fading Array!”

Hall Master Luo shouted towards Nether Darklight.

“Yes!”

For Nether Darklight to become a Hall Master before the Divine Lord realm, he could be considered as an outstanding individual. He had seen many magnificent scenes and also gone through many dangerous life or death situations. At the beginning he had panicked for a brief moment because of the primordial epoch spirit’s sneak attack, but now he had calmed down.

“My comrades, offer a sacrifice of your blood, Myriad Blood Demon Fading Array!”

As Nether Darklight spoke he bit down on the tip of his tongue and spat out a mouthful of blood. This blood was mixed together with a trace of blood essence, turning into a dreadful blood demon in the skies.

And after Nether Darklight did this, the other disciples of the Skydark Holy Lands followed suit. They bit down on the tip of their tongue, spraying blood out into the air. Each mist of blood turned into a crimson blood demon!

The basis of the Myriad Blood Demon Fading Array was to use the blood essence of the casters to form an offensive array formation that attacked with blood demon kings. Once this sort of array formation was used, it would inevitably damage the life source of the user. Unless one was going all-out, they wouldn’t use this array.

Some disciples of the Skydark Holy Lands hesitated at the start. After all, this was something that involved  their own source blood essence; no one wanted to casually throw it away. But at this time they could only steel themselves and follow orders.

Nether Darklight shouted out, “Disciples of the Skydark Holy Lands, heed my orders! Use your everything to kill this primordial epoch spirit root! The more it swallows the flesh and blood essence of martial artists, the stronger it becomes! But once it is captured, that will be a great merit for all involved! The primordial epoch spirit root is something that Master Ancestor Tian Mingzi needs, and he will be generous with rewards. You are all inner court disciples, and in the Skydark Holy Lands there are hundreds of millions of you! Do you want to remain an inner court disciple for the rest of your life? Do you never wish to see Master Ancestor for the rest of your life? Do you never wish to study a transcendent divine might for the rest of your life?

“Riches and dangers come hand in hand; this is your chance! Everyone who participates in this battle, I guarantee that you will obtain rich rewards beyond your imagination! The value of this is far beyond the blood essence that you will pay! Fellow sect members, let us put forth our full effort and capture this spirit root!”

Nether Darklight’s words were filled with passion, containing a stirring strength.

Those Skydark Holy Land disciples who originally had problems with giving up their blood essence were suddenly roused by Nether Darklight’s words.

Indeed, this was their lucky chance. If they could find this medicine that Tian Mingzi was specifically looking for, just what kind of merit would that be!

If it weren’t for the special terrain of Demondawn Jungle that required a massive number of disciples to carry out a full-on carpet search, they never would have had the chance to complete a mission for Tian Mingzi.

The 200-300 Skydark Holy Land disciples spat out their blood essence. This blood essence turned into blood-red demon kings, all of them rushing towards the root hairs of the primordial epoch spirit root.

Rumble rumble rumble!

Energy surged and blood flew out. Some blood demons were shattered and broken up but there was also a massive number of spirit roots that were burned and cut in half!

These blood demons possessed extreme corrosive properties. The primordial epoch spirit root was also burnt!

The disciples and Elders of the Skydark Holy Lands were not some random nobodies. If they dared to come and try to capture the primordial epoch spirit root, they naturally had certain abilities they could rely on.

“Continue! All the way until the end!”

Nether Darklight shouted out once more as he spat out more blood essence.

Although each time he was just spitting out a tiny bit of blood essence, how could he continue like this?

Some disciples of the Skydark Holy Lands turned to the loose cultivators.

“You lot! All of you offer your blood essence! Hurry!”

Even the disciples around the bald youth began to shout out loud.

“What’re you all standing around for? Do you want to die!?”

As they spoke, several disciples of the Skydark Holy Lands took out their weapons, a thick killing intent overflowing from their bodies as if they were about to attack these loose cultivators at any moment.

If they really fought, then there would be no need for the six Divine Lord powerhouses or the Divine Transformation realm Nether Darklight to do anything. Just the bald youth and his group alone could kill off the dozens of loose cultivators!

The difference in strength was far too great!

Lin Ming frowned. These disciples were offering their blood essence, and now they also wanted the loose cultivators to do the same?

As long as the disciples of the Skydark Holy Lands were able to catch the primordial epoch spirit root, they would be able to enjoy countless rewards. But what about the loose cultivators present? If they also spent their blood essence would they receive the same generous rewards?

The bald youth loudly said, “Today, I can promise all of you loose cultivators that as long as you offer your blood essence and fight with everything you have, after this battle is over, you will be allowed into the Skydark Holy Lands as official disciples! Isn’t entering the Skydark Holy Lands something that you wish for even in your dreams?”

To enter the Skydark Holy Lands was indeed the wish of many loose cultivators. However, they also knew that the so-called official disciple was in truth a caretaker disciple. To put it more bluntly, that was to be a servant to others.

To burn their blood essence and also participate in a battle in which they would likely die, all in order to become a caretaker disciple – wasn’t that thinking too cheaply of their lives?

Many loose cultivators didn’t want this.

The bald youth’s complexion turned cold. “Burn your blood essence or die, make your choice!”

Within the primordial epoch spirit root’s domain, it was impossible for these loose cultivators to escape. And at this time, the disciples of the Skydark Holy Lands were purposefully pushing the scattered domain energy towards the edges where the loose cultivators were.

For a time, at the position where the loose cultivators were, the power of the domain became increasingly strong and the smell of blood soared to the heavens. The chaos aura here became increasingly rich. Even if the primordial epoch spirit root’s chaos aura wasn’t yet able to transform into elementary grandmist energy, it was still as heavy as a mountain. With so much chaos aura pushing down on these loose cultivators, it was making it hard for them to breathe!

Some loose cultivators turned pale because they couldn’t resist this pressure. Some of them even let out miserable screams as explosive sounds emitted from their joints and parts of their meridians broke apart. As loose cultivators, it was simply impossible for them to be like the disciples of the Skydark Holy Lands and set down a great array formation to resist the power of this domain.

“Humph! You all would rather do things the hard way! You only have yourselves to blame.”

The bald youth maniacally grinned. At this time, Nether Darklight coldly coughed, “What are you dawdling about for? For the loose cultivators that won’t offer their blood essence, just kill them and extract their blood essence instead!”

As the one who was managing the Myriad Blood Demon Fading Array, Nether Darklight was eager to defeat the primordial epoch spirit root. This was an important accomplishment to add onto his record of merits!

Even with Nether Darklight’s status, he was still rarely given the chance to perform tasks for Tian Mingzi. This was an unbelievably great opportunity for him. If he completed this task perfectly, he would obtain unimaginable rewards. Moreover, his status in the future would rise to new heights and he would be able to travel even farther down his road of martial arts.

With such a chance presented before him, how could he allow these loose cultivators, who were nothing more than a group of ants, to drag him down?

“Yes, kill them all!”

The bald youth smacked his forehead. Wasn’t killing these loose cultivators and taking their blood essence even simpler?

“H-hold on!”

As a loose cultivator that was struggling vigorously in the scattered domain energy saw the bald youth about to attack, he shouted out, “Forgive me! I’m willing to offer my blood essence!”

“Too late! Killing you is much simpler. I want all of your blood essence! Only like that will the might of the Myriad Blood Demon Fading Array be even stronger!”

The bald youth laughed and thrust his saber into the loose cultivator’s chest. The difference in strength was extremely high to begin with, and these loose cultivators were also being pushed down by the suppressive domain all around them. They simply didn’t possess any ability to resist.

“Ahhh!”

The loose cultivator that had been begging for mercy cried out in pain, his entire body twitching. All of his blood essence was sucked out by the bald youth, turning into a crimson blood demon that hurtled towards the primordial epoch spirit root!

The Myriad Blood Demon Fading Array’s might was beyond doubt. In addition, there were also the combined attacks of six Divine Lord masters constantly raining down, cutting away the root hairs of the primordial epoch spirit root!

Every time a root hair was cut off, a massive amount of blood shot into the air.

This extremely evil plant was actually able to bleed.

Woosh! Woosh! Woosh!

The primordial epoch spirit root violently struggled. Thick branches smashed into the black swamp, causing millions of jins of blood to rush into the sky like a tsunami.

Bang!

Several hundred branches simultaneously struck the six Divine Lord realm masters. But, with the six masters having formed an array formation and also being under the protection of the six-armed demon king, they blocked all the attacks of the primordial epoch spirit root!

However, underneath the attack of the primordial epoch spirit root, the six Divine Lord masters weren’t feeling much better. They were desperately persisting through this onslaught of attacks. In this war of attrition, the one to last to the end would win!

“This isn’t the end yet. If I knew things would be like this I would have killed all those loose cultivators earlier. Although they are weak, their blood essence can still be used. If all their blood essence is taken out it, it will still be stronger than the blood essence we can put forth.”

Although the disciples of the Skydark Holy Lands had a vibrant blood vitality, how many drops of blood essence could they burn? How could it compare to taking out all of the blood essence from these loose cultivators?

Chapter 1341 – Drastic Measures

As the bald youth was about to continue killing the other loose cultivators, the black swamp beneath them began to wildly rumble. With a loud explosive sound, endless amounts of black mud scattered in all directions. Then, a root hair 10 times thicker than the previous ones suddenly shot out.

This root hair was like a black dragon, releasing an incomparably terrifying aura. This was the primordial epoch spirit’s main body!

The primordial epoch spirit root had intellect and was also aware that this was a critical moment in its survival. It had to go all-out!

“Rahhh – !”

The primordial epoch spirit root roared. This plant was actually able to roar. The following sharp sound wave transmitted several hundred miles outwards, piercing through the ears.

“Stop it!”

“Demon Massacring Great Array!”

The six Divine Lord masters attacked together. The joints in their bodies burst out with crackling sounds, their muscles expanding as their blood vessels popped out. Their skin began to turn a dark red. Without a doubt, this was a secret technique of the demonic path.

Although this sort of secret technique didn’t involve burning their blood essence, the truth was that this harmed their source of life even more than that. This was a move that required them to burn their very life. Just using it once would cause one’s fires of life to weaken by a great deal, a style of bringing down the opponent while bringing great harm upon oneself. This was their final finishing move saved for all-out events. If they couldn’t kill their enemy then they would all die one after another, because this move greatly overdrew their true essence and blood vitality.

The bodies of the six masters burst out with layers of black light that wrapped around them. Behind these six people, a black scroll and a white scroll began to slowly unravel. Atop these scrolls were images of pain and suffering, people being tortured and demons being executed. Just glancing at these scrolls made one’s entire body feel restrained!

Hah – !

The black and white scrolls suddenly came falling down, covering the primordial epoch spirit root.

The primordial epoch spirit root wildly struggled, wanting to tear those painting scrolls to pieces. As for the six masters, their faces began to pale as sweat streamed down their faces.

“Darklight, hurry! Use the strongest state of the Myriad Blood Demon Fading Array so we can defeat this creature in one fell swoop!”

Hall Master Luo roared out. When he used the Demon Massacring Great Array, every breath of time cost a thousand years of life. They simply couldn’t continue like this.

“I know!”

Nether Darklight’s eyes turned to those several hundred loose cultivators, his vision filled with a thick and brutal killing intent.

“Hurry and kill them all!”

“Great!” The bald youth laughed. If he used the blood essence of these loose cultivators, he could earn merits and not damage his own life source; that was something he truly wished for!

“Skydark Holy Lands! You damned dogs can go die!” Many loose cultivators angrily cursed. They began to take out their weapons, preparing themselves to struggle to the death.

“Let’s fight with them and then run away!”

“I don’t want to die here.”

In the face of imminent death, no one was able to maintain their calm. Although these loose cultivators could also fight, they knew that there was a high probability they would all die here today.

“Big Brother, what do we do?” The blue-clothed girl who spoke to Lin Ming before was pale with an expression filled with fear. Beside her, her brother’s forehead was also dripping with sweat.

And at this time, Lin Ming looked at the battlefield in front of him. This primordial epoch spirit root’s strength had surpassed his imaginations. Even so, if this battle continued, the primordial epoch spirit root would be captured sooner or later. This was not something he wished to see.

What he hoped for was an outcome in which both sides were severely wounded.

“Hey, brat! We brought you all the way here, now it’s time to make use of you. We’ll start with you first! Now die!”

The bald youth decided to start with Lin Ming.

In his eyes, although Lin Ming was strong, he was still a loose cultivator in the end. In other words, he was nothing worth caring about.

Hu – !

The bald youth’s saber slashed through the void, cutting down at Lin Ming!

Lin Ming sneered. Without even using the Phoenix Blood Spear, he stretched out his hand and grasped the bald youth’s saber.

Omm!

With the sound of shivering metal, the bald youth’s saber was easily gripped between two of Lin Ming’s fingers. The saber seemed as if it was stuck in a block of iron, unable to be pulled out.

“What!?”

The bald youth couldn’t believe his own eyes. This feeling was the same as if he were to step on an ant, but then found that the ant was lifting him instead!

At this moment, he felt a thunderous blast echo in his mind. Illusions began to grow thick in his spiritual sea. In the confusion, all he saw was Lin Ming’s coldly indifferent face.

Puff!

With a light sound, Lin Ming flicked out a true essence energy arrow that pierced through the bald youth’s throat.

A severe pain spread through the bald youth’s body. The bald youth grasped his throat, desperately trying to stem the flow of blood, his eyes as round as plates and his vision filled with incredulity. Like this, he fell straight down from the skies.

“Senior-apprentice Brother Luo!”

“What happened!?”

The sudden change in Lin Ming immediately attacked the eyes of all the disciples from the Skydark Holy Lands.

Everyone saw Lin Ming easily kill that bald youth. Even the loose cultivators were shocked.

The bald youth himself had a late Divine Sea realm cultivation. As for Lin Ming’s cultivation, he was only at the peak of the middle Divine Sea realm. Even so… this was simply impossible.

“He killed Senior-apprentice Brother Luo?”

“How is this possible? He is only a middle Divine Sea realm martial artist!”

“He must have been hiding his cultivation! He isn’t a loose cultivator!”

The bald youth was not some ordinary nobody. Those people that Tian Mingzi were willing to accept as secret disciples were all amazing geniuses to begin with. Even so, he had been instantly killed by Lin Ming. The only explanation was that Lin Ming was hiding his cultivation or perhaps had even altered his appearance.

“Work together! Kill him!”

The disciples of the Skydark Holy Lands all rushed towards Lin Ming.

Lin Ming’s complexion was calm and indifferent. An ancient and boundless aura surged out from his body, recklessly washing over everyone. He had opened the grandmist space. However, this grandmist space was different from before. This time, Lin Ming’s grandmist space was filled with a wisp of divine dream energy, making this space seem as if it were isolated from the world and located in a completely different space and time.

This was the domain created by Lin Ming combining the Divine Dream Law with the grandmist space. With Lin Ming’s current understandings into the Divine Dream Law, it was impossible for him to form the divine dream space. And it was even more impossible for him to completely fuse the divine dream space and grandmist space together. But, to integrate the Divine Dream Law into the grandmist space and allow it to take on certain characteristics of the Divine Dream Law was something he could do.

For a time, all of the martial artists were covered in the grandmist space. Illusions grew thick in their minds and the real world seemed to fall away from them.

Lin Ming grasped the Phoenix Blood Spear and stepped forwards. A deadly spear light flashed out and several disciples were instantly cut down by Lin Ming!

“What have you done?!” As Nether Darklight saw this, his eyes filled with red rage.

Catching the primordial epoch spirit root was a golden opportunity for Nether Darklight to earn great merits; it would relate to how far he would be able to walk down the road of martial arts in the future. And yet, all of his efforts were being sabotaged by Lin Ming. By killing a massive number of Skydark Holy Land disciples, that would cause the great array to be destroyed. How could he not be angry?

He grasped his black heavy sword and cut down at Lin Ming, “Die for me!”

Facing Nether Darklight, Lin Ming’s complexion was indifferent. In that instant, essence, energy, and divine fused within his body as his strength began to rapidly rise.

Three Essences as One!

Nether Darklight was an early Divine Transformation powerhouse, but to Lin Ming, he was the same as everyone else.

Divine Seal Art – God Forbidding Seal!

Lin Ming’s fingers linked together, instantly forming thousands upon thousands of seals. These seals were all complex and ancient; besides Lin Ming, no one was able to understand them.

Lin Ming shouted out loud. Then, all of these seals flew towards the approaching Nether Darklight!

Ka ka ka!

Nether Darklight’s sword light was covered in these seals. In that moment, these seals all turned into energy black holes, rapidly swallowing Nether Darklight’s strength.

Nether Darklight felt his strength rapidly fading away. His complexion suddenly changed. He wanted to cut off his connection to his sword light and attack again, but Lin Ming had already appeared like ghosts and gods in front of him.

One spear shot out!

Nether Darklight was frightened out of his mind. A protective black fog covered his entire body. Ghostly energy grew thick around him as black light flashed. At the same time, he traced his spatial ring as if he wanted to pull out some life-saving magic tool.

But at this time, Lin Ming’s spear light thrust into the black fog surrounding Nether Darklight. With a blur, space trembled and the black fog around Nether Darklight remained for just a brief moment before completely dissipating.

The Phoenix Blood Spear ruthlessly pierced into Nether Darklight’s chest.

With this strike, the massive amount of energy contained within the Phoenix Blood Spear erupted. Nether Darklight cried out as most of his organs were torn to shreds. In his right hand, there was no time for him to use the magic life-saving tool he was taking out; he had already been killed by Lin Ming.

The disparity was too great!

Chapter 1345 – Receiving the Spirit Root

Lin Ming grasped the Phoenix Blood Spear. Within his body, essence, energy, and divine fused together. He aimed his spear at the 12 root hairs and slashed outwards!

The power of thunder and fire intertwined upon the Phoenix Blood Spear. This was the power of thunder and fire tribulation that flowed out from the Heretical God Tree.

Heavenly Dao Judgment!

Bang!

With a terrifying explosive sound, those 12 root hairs were blown apart by Lin Ming. Lin Ming calmly retreated, but the primordial epoch spirit root’s main body actually staggered backwards, slowing down. Tens of thousands of God Forbidding Seals formed energy black holes in its body, swallowing up a massive amount of its strength.

The transformed woman’s face of the primordial epoch spirit root constantly twisted, becoming increasingly blurry. Because its energy was becoming too chaotic it was finding it hard to maintain its manifested shape.

With Lin Ming in front of it, it simply didn’t have the opportunity to force out these God Forbidding Seals. If this continued, then it wouldn’t be too long before Lin Ming would capture it.

But if it wanted to run away, that was also difficult. The primordial epoch spirit root’s entire body was riddled with these divine seal marks, these marks were personally formed by Lin Ming. The primordial epoch spirit root suspected that Lin Ming would absolutely be able to use these marks to sense its presence and chase after it.

If it ran away, it would continue to weaken until it was overtaken by Lin Ming.

“This damned boy!”

The primordial epoch spirit root’s voice became increasingly shrill and harsh. The woman’s face it manifested became increasingly fierce, turning into that of a horrifying demon. “Boy, you have forced my hand!”

At that moment, a gray, boundless aura surged out from the primordial epoch spirit root’s body, becoming increasingly intense. It roared towards Lin Ming like a gray inferno. This was the life aura of the primordial epoch spirit root, the primal chaos spirit energy from the forming of the universe that it had absorbed.

The primordial epoch spirit root didn’t hesitate at all to consume its life aura in order to attack Lin Ming.

As Lin Ming saw these gray flames rushing towards him, he grinned, “You’ve finally used your last resort. But, your final ultimate move uses the power of the Primal Chaos Laws; it is useless against me!”

At that moment, behind Lin Ming, a blood red lotus flower slowly bloomed. This lotus flower was ancient and profound, red to the point that it seemed as if it were dyed in the blood of a demon god.

Grandmist space!

Hu – !

A powerful grandmist strength surged out. The Law-annihilating grandmist space spread out, covering an area of a hundred miles.

As the primordial epoch spirit root’s gray flames entered this grandmist space, they actually seemed as if they were about to be absorbed. This was the power of primal chaos, but Lin Ming’s attainments in these Laws were much higher. The grandmist space was a transcendent divine might established by an Empyrean level master.

“This… this is!? How is this possible!?” The primordial epoch spirit root was greatly shocked. “You can actually comprehend the Primal Chaos Laws!?”

At that moment, a deep feeling of unease swelled up within the primordial epoch spirit root’s heart. It ignored all else and exploded those gray flames before turning around and fleeing!

Although it knew that escaping from here would be difficult, if it remained here it would die without a doubt.

Bang!

The gray flames exploded within the grandmist space. At the same time, the main body of the primordial epoch spirit root tried to sink underground. But at this moment, it sensed that all the light around it had disappeared, everything turning to darkness. A powerful traction force locked onto its body, making it impossible for it to dive underground.

Lin Ming’s voice began to echo in the primordial epoch spirit root’s ears like the whispers of a cackling demon.

“By the power of a black hole, swallow all power, swallow all matter, fall into an infinite abyss of time, within this cage of space you shall never emerge, sink forever, perish through the sands of history! Divine Seal Art, swallow all of existence – Eternal Darkness!”

At this time, a dark sphere floated out in front of Lin Ming. All of the origin energy within this world began to go crazy, wildly gathering towards the sphere and forming a giant black vortex. All of the mud in the swamp, all of the broken trees, all of the vicious beast skeletons, everything was being sucked up by this vortex, vanishing into that dark sphere where it would be sealed for all eternity!

This dark sphere was Lin Ming’s black hole seed. With it, he could simulate the final darkness of a black hole singularity.

A year ago when Lin Ming used this move, all of his meridians and blood vessels had bulged upwards, tearing apart as they were unable to withstand this pressure. But now, Lin Ming’s understandings into the soul forging Dream Laws were far more profound. Moreover, his fused essence, energy, and divine strength was being increasingly coordinated and his comprehension of the Concept of the 33 Layered Heavens was also much deeper.

Currently, he could freely use Eternal Darkness as he wished.

“What is this!?”

The primordial epoch spirit root furiously cried out as it began to lose its mind. It crazily struggled, but at this time, underneath the compulsion of the 10,000 God Forbidding Seals, all of them broke out. A terrifying strength swept out like a mat, recklessly enveloping everything nearby. The primordial epoch spirit root suddenly stiffened; it was impossible to break free from this strength!

“Ahhhh!”

The primordial epoch spirit root roared out; it was actually lifted up by this terrifying suction force!

The main form of the primordial epoch spirit root was over a thousand feet long and looked like a massive black python. It crazily struggled in the skies, but no matter what it did, it could not escape the shackles of Eternal Darkness.

“Die!”

As Lin Ming released the black hole seed, he also thrust out his spear.

Heavenly Dao Judgment!

The savage power of thunder and fire tribulation crashed into the primordial epoch spirit root, spurring those over 10,000 God Forbidden Seals to explode!

Energy shockwaves surged outwards. The primordial epoch spirit root was blown apart by Lin Ming’s attack!

A massive deluge of bright red juice showered down like a waterfall. All of this blood-like juice was sucked in by Lin Ming.

“Brat, I curse you to a miserable death for the next 10,000 lives! I hope you die horribly!”

The primordial epoch spirit root viciously roared. As a plant lifeform, it truly did have a far more formidable ability to resist attacks than humans did. Even now, it still hadn’t died, and if it were allowed to swallow up enough flesh and blood essence it could even restore itself.

“Seal!”

Lin Ming’s fingers flashed. In just several breaths of time, over 10,000 more God Forbidding Seals sank into the primordial epoch spirit root’s main body, sealing away all of its strength. Even its basic life functions were sealed away.

The Divine Seal Art could seal away even gods, much less a tiny spirit plant.

Hi – !

After the primordial epoch spirit lost all ability to resist, it was directly brought into the Magic Cube space.

After completing all of this, Lin Ming let out a long breath. After using Heavenly Dao Judgment twice, forming tens of thousands of God Forbidden Seals, and even displaying Eternal Darkness, he had consumed a considerable amount of energy.

As he turned his head, he could see that those six Divine Lord powerhouses still hadn’t completely died off. Almost half of their flesh and blood essence had been swallowed up by the primordial epoch spirit root and their bodies were as thin as sticks, like corpses that had been withering away for thousands of years. Their appearances couldn’t be called humans or ghosts.

“You… you…”

Old Man Luo looked at Lin Ming with horror. His hair was stringy and white, his eyes had receded deep into their sockets, his chest was caved in, and he had lost all semblance of life. He would die soon.

“Hahahaha! Hahahha!”

Old Man Luo seemed to suddenly come alive. He wryly smiled, “I never thought that even though the six of us joined forces to capture the primordial epoch spirit root, all of our efforts would be gifted to someone else. Finally, victory fell into the lap of a little brat like you! Even the primordial epoch spirit root was tricked by you! You are vicious and cunning enough, a wonderful plan indeed!”

Old Man Luo grit his teeth, his body constantly trembling.

“Are those your final dying words? How boring.”

Lin Ming coldly glanced around, taking stock of the surroundings. After the six Divine Lord powerhouses had been caged in with the primordial epoch spirit root, the other disciples of the Skydark Holy Lands had either died or run away. Now, there were only six people left over.

The loose cultivators were still there, but Lin Ming didn’t worry that they would recognize his identity from his moves. This was because Lin Ming had fought the primordial epoch spirit root in its domain, and added to the fact that he had used some concealing techniques, it was impossible for them to witness the scene of fighting.

“You… just who are you?”

Old Man Luo hadn’t watched the finals of the Divine Realm First Martial Meeting, but he could feel that this youth in front of him was not some nobody. No matter how he looked, this youth in front of him was still at the middle Divine Sea realm and didn’t seem to be hiding his cultivation at all…

Lin Ming grinned. His squatted down in front of Old Man Luo and said, “I am the Lin Ming you have been looking for. Surprised?”

Lin Ming’s words caused Old Man Luo’s heart to shake!

He felt that Lin Ming’s smile was the smirk of a devil. This was Lin Ming? He was actually Lin Ming. He knew that everyone was searching for him but he deliberately walked into their midst? This youth was too terrifying!

In that moment, Old Man Luo’s divine soul fell into illusion. He felt a powerful strength invade his spiritual sea. Ghosts and phantoms grew thick in his mind as he lost himself.

Lin Ming pressed his hand onto Old Man Luo’s forehead. Divine Dream Law – soul searching technique!

By using the Divine Dream Law to display the soul searching technique, this was countless times superior to using the common soul searching technique of the demonic path. The information that could be recovered was far more complete. Besides things like cultivation methods, array formation techniques, alchemy techniques, refiner techniques, and other such extremely complex memories, everything else could be obtained.

However, Old Man Luo was a Divine Lord powerhouse and his divine soul was incomparably powerful. If Lin Ming rashly used the soul searching technique, it was likely he would suffer a backlash. Thus, he informed Old Man Luo of his status to make his enemy’s mind fall into despair. This gave him the perfect opportunity to strike.

A tremendous amount of information emerged within Lin Ming’s mind.

This included Tian Mingzi’s recent movements, and possible reasons why he was searching for body transformation medicines and Lin Ming’s whereabouts.

However, Lin Ming didn’t find anything of value in this old man’s memories. All of this information had only been speculation.

All sorts of clues indicated that there seemed to be some unknown force that had appeared within the Skydark Holy Lands. This influence was of an extremely high status and only received orders from Tian Mingzi himself. It seemed that the reasons there were people searching for body transformation medicines was all because of this influence…

“Tian Mingzi is looking for my whereabouts, could it be related to my body transformation technique?”

This thought inevitably appeared in Lin Ming’s mind.

Lin Ming wasn’t able to confirm anything without further information. He thrust his spear into Old Man Luo’s throat. The dying old man struggled for several more breaths of time before finally laying motionless.

As for the other five people, they were all killed off one by one. Their spatial rings were also taken by him. After searching through them, he found that they mostly contained cultivation methods and pills of the Skydark Holy Lands as well as some weapons and other treasures. It was impossible for Lin Ming to take a liking to any of this.

After casually putting it all away, Lin Ming’s thoughts moved and he entered the Magic Cube space. He wanted to completely subdue and refine the primordial epoch spirit root.

Chapter 1348 – Hunt of the Saint Race

Lin Ming felt as if his own mortal body had perished, with nothing but an incomparably clear spiritual sense. He swam through an endless void, and this vast void was filled with countless hollows, each one leading to infinite dimensions. If he was not careful then he would lose his soul and would be unable to pull himself out.

For the consciousness to wander about in such a space was extremely dangerous. But, Lin Ming could faintly feel that in some distant space behind him, there was a black sphere that continuously emitted some invisible gravitational force. Because of this force, Lin Ming was able to clearly recognize the direction he needed to go in without fear of becoming lost.

“This sort of attraction is the… black hole seed!”

Lin Ming’s mind immediately flashed back to his black hole seed. As a manifestation of the Laws from the Concept of the 33 Layered Heavens, it actually had a function of guiding the process of the body transformation technique. This was because the body transformation technique was also one of the Concepts of the 33 Layered Heavens.

With the black hole seed, it was like a beacon signaling to him in a black and boundless sea. As he ran forwards, he searched about, passing through countless wild space flows before faintly making out a gate in the depths of time and space.

On top this gate were two white skeletons. The hands of these skeletons each grasped a handle of this gate, keeping it locked tight.

“This is the Gate of Death!”

Lin Ming’s eyebrows shot up. The Gate of Death was the final of the Eight Inner Hidden Gates, a gate that was located in the spiritual sea.

In order to open the Gate of Death, one had to bring the mortal body to the edge of death until there was only the spiritual consciousness remaining. Then, through taking a swim in one’s spiritual world, they could feel where the Gate of Death was.

This was the so-called nirvana rebirth after annihilation.

Lin Ming was well aware that as long as he could open the Gate of Death, he could reach perfection of the Eight Inner Hidden Gates and obtain endless benefits in the future. This would allow him to establish a solid foundation for opening the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace.

Lin Ming stretched out his hand, his thoughts forming a spear in his grip. As he held this spear, he smashed it atop that gate.

Bang!

The great gate shook. From a tiny gap in the gate, a vast amount of energy poured forth. Lin Ming knew that this energy was called astral essence.

This was also the energy that a body transformation martial artist used. It was one of the three main origin energies of the universe.

Lin Ming took a deep breath and allowed all the astral essence leaking out from the Gate of Death to be sucked into his body. In that moment, the phantom of an Azure Dragon appeared behind him.

Lin Ming simultaneously opened the first seven of the Eight Inner Hidden Gates. The Heretical God Force erupted as he transferred all of his strength into a barrage of attacks. Spear after spear came crashing down, with 100 spear strikes coming in an instant. Then, these 100 spear strikes fused together, gathering into the strongest strength.

Celestial Tyrant Manual – Hundred Layered Waves!

Bang!

To use the pure power from body transformation to attack the Gate of Death, at this time, the Gate of Death violently trembled. An increasingly powerful force flowed outwards along with an immeasurably vast amount of astral essence, forming a raging river that poured onto Lin Ming.

More and more energy gushed out, becoming increasingly rich. Lin Ming swam within this energy and felt his mortal body that had been filled with the power of death begin to glow once more with the vitality of life.

His withered skin and flesh began to burst apart, falling off, revealing newborn flesh. His skeleton also regrew. Although Lin Ming’s skeleton had been integrated with the power of a dragon bone and the power of a dragon bone was indeed wonderful, in the end it wasn’t his original strength at all and would cause minor conflicts within his own strength. But now, this strength was also being refined and cast into his new body.

At that moment, Lin Ming could feel his mortal body reach unprecedented levels of strength. His entire body began to emit crackling noises, as if a God Beast were sealed within him and was trying to burst outwards.

“Ha – !”

Lin Ming shouted out loud and waved his spear, smashing it once more at the mystical gate in front of him.

This time, with a loud explosive sound, the gate completely broke apart.

Lin Ming had finally broken through the Gate of Death.

Astral essence continued to flood into Lin Ming’s body like an endless river. Lin Ming’s strength also rapidly rose. In just several breaths of time, his strength broke through 100 million jins and still continued to climb.

110 million!

120 million!

150 million!

180 million!

200 million!

…….

With the Eight Inner Hidden Gates having reached perfection, the strength of Lin Ming’s body had taken a qualitative leap upwards.

200 million jins was still not his limit.

230 million jins, 250 million jins, all the way to 260 million jins.

If Lin Ming were to erupt astral essence from his body, his strength would rise even more.

“The amount of astral essence within my body has increased by over a hundredfold. Although I cultivated the body transformation technique, the astral essence I had was pitifully low. Now that I’ve opened the Gate of Death, it actually increased so much. This is simply incredible!”

Lin Ming muttered. Mo Eversnow continued to explain, “Lin Ming, the current Divine Realm’s Heavenly Dao Laws do not allow the body transformation technique to be cultivated to a high level, and thus astral essence has also been imprisoned. Before now, the cultivation of your body transformation technique was low, but with you having opened the Gate of Death and reaching perfection of the Eight Inner Hidden Gates, your strength has risen to new heights. At the minimum, you have touched upon the Divine Realm Laws. But, the Eight Inner Hidden Gates is only the start. The truly heaven-defying difficulty will now begin as you try to break into the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace. This step is simply far, far too difficult.”

Mo Eversnow shook her head as she spoke of the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace. She didn’t know whether or not  Lin Ming would be able to take this step in the future.

“I can slowly approach the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace. Now that I have opened the eight gates to perfection, in terms of body transformation technique I should be at the peak in the Divine Realm.”

Lin Ming was confident in himself. Before now, the person with the highest boundary in body transformation was Shiku, who had also opened seven gates. He was the same as Lin Ming’s previous state.

“Miss Mo, let’s not delay. Let us leave for the Sky Spill Planet as soon as possible. In my current state, I have some grasp of being able to enter the Eternal Demon Abyss.”

“Okay.”

Mo Eversnow turned into a wisp of spiritual energy that fused back into the world within Lin Ming’s Magic Cube.

Lin Ming left the cave dwelling he opened and began to fly towards the lower realms transmission array.

In the blink of an eye he crossed several dozen miles. At this time, a sense of absolute crisis surged in Lin Ming’s mind! He could feel that in that instant, his entire body was being seen through by an invisible eye!

Lin Ming’s entire body turned ice cold. He nervously stopped where he was, carefully looking all around as he took out the Phoenix Blood Spear.

“Who is it!?”

“Hehe, you’re quite vigilant. But what a pity, the difference in strength is too great. You are destined to die here today.”

A thousand feet in front of Lin Ming, the void was ripped apart as a black-robed man shrouded in dark fog stepped out.

He stretched out his long tongue, licking the air as if he were tasting Lin Ming’s aura.

“Truly incredible. It was already a surprise that you killed so many disciples of the Skydark Holy Lands and even obtained the primordial epoch spirit root, but to think you used this to open the Gate of Death. As for your cultivation… mm? You are at the middle Divine Sea realm?”

At this time, Lin Ming was still concealing his appearance. With the cleverness and versatility of the Divine Dream Law, no one could see through Lin Ming’s appearance changing technique unless they were a Great World King.

“Middle Divine Sea realm? Are you hiding your cultivation? What sort of cultivation disguising technique is this, that even I can’t see through?”

The black-robed man said, greatly interested in Lin Ming.

“Who are you?”

Lin Ming’s voice was gloomy and dire. Facing this black-robed man, he could feel an enormous sense of danger pressing down on him, making all of his hairs stand on end.

This person’s cultivation was shrouded in a thick fog. Lin Ming couldn’t see what this person’s cultivation was or what Laws they practiced. He wasn’t even able to confirm whether this person was truly a man or a woman. All he felt was an extremely dangerous aura.

Lin Ming had never encountered such an unpredictable and elusive enemy before.

And, most importantly, just how did this person find him?

Before Lin Ming caught the primordial epoch spirit root he had changed his appearance and even changed his appearance several times after. Moreover, he had escaped extremely far. In this situation, this person had found him?

And such a mysterious enemy came from the Skydark Holy Lands? All sorts of ideas raced through Lin Ming’s mind. He suddenly realized that the situation in the Skydark Holy Lands wasn’t as simple as he first thought.

“Miss Mo, what is going on here? Did I make a mistake somewhere?”

“I am not sure. If he can find you, it seems as if he’s using the mythical karmic techniques. It is said that those supreme elders who cultivated the Time Laws to an extremely high boundary could calculate the past and predict the future. Predicting the future is just a bedtime story; the future is far too ethereal and winding and no one can accurately say what will happen. But, the past has already occurred, and that is something which is eternally unchanging. In this world, there are indeed some people that can see the past…”

“Mm? There is a secret technique like that?”

“Yes, but this person before us might not have used such a technique. There are countless roads to the Great Dao, and innumerable secret techniques that we are not aware of. This person is far too strange, and he even feels… like he isn’t a human!”

As Mo Eversnow stated this stunning declaration, Lin Ming’s eyebrows shot up. This person wasn’t a human? Were they a monster? Or a demon?

Or, was it possible they were an unknown alien race?

But, what was without a doubt was that this person in front of him was extremely strong, and much, much stronger than he was.

Just by looking at him being able to tear apart space to appear, that was something far from what Lin Ming could accomplish. That was the void shifting technique.

“Let’s not bother with some nonsensical banter. I will finish you. Since you ate my primordial epoch spirit root, I will use you to make my medicine instead. The effects shouldn’t be much worse!

As this black-robed figure spoke, Lin Ming felt all of the space around him suddenly shrink and be isolated. Along with the black-robed figure, he arrived in a separate world devoid of everything but shadows.

This was a domain, and also a very powerful domain. Lin Ming and the black-robed man were both completely isolated from the outside world.

In this domain, not only would Lin Ming be suppressed but he wouldn’t even be able to escape.

“This is my Eternal Demon Domain. Once you enter it you will fall under my control. You can forget ever escaping!”

The shadowy figure spoke with supreme confidence. He took out a black scroll and slowly unraveled it. On top of this scroll was a drawing of a black and white landscape. A simple stone bridge was in the center of this drawing, appearing extremely mystical.

Lin Ming’s pupils shrank. He didn’t wait for this shadowy figure to make his move, instead taking the initiative to attack first!

He opened the Heretical God Force to the limit and also revolved the complete Eight Inner Hidden Gates. The astral essence he just obtained suddenly erupted from his body as he thrust his spear towards that black-robed man.

Rumble rumble rumble!

Thunder and flame crazily twisted together.

Heavenly Dao Judgment!

Chapter 1351 – Forcing Through the Void

The sudden voice startled the Skybreak Sect Elder. He simply didn’t know where this voice was coming from, “Who is it?”

“I am the Great World King of the Demondawn Great World. Immediately stop the revolution of the transmission array!” Tian Mingzi’s voice seemed as if it passed through layers and layers of the void, directly entering the spiritual sea of the Skybreak Sect Elder.

“This is… I…”

The Skybreak Sect Elder was dumbfounded. The Demondawn Great World’s Great World King!?

To him, that was an utterly legendary character!

Although he didn’t know whether this was true or false, from just this terrifying pressure alone, it was absolutely a top master. How could he dare to ignore the order of such a master?

The Skybreak Sect Elder immediately stopped the activation of the transmission array.

As Lin Ming saw this, his complexion changed.

The Skybreak Sect Elder glared at Lin Ming, simply not bothering to explain anything to him.

If he told others that he had stopped just because someone ordered him to, that would be a tremendous loss of face. In any case, he simply didn’t care about a junior like Lin Ming.

Lin Ming grimaced. He was aware that Tian Mingzi’s long distance sound transmission had reached this Skybreak Sect Elder!

With Tian Mingzi’s methods, from where he was to here, he might need just 10 breaths of time to cross the void and arrive. It might even be less than that!

In other words, he had less than 10 breaths of time to escape here!

With so little time, Lin Ming wouldn’t waste his time trying to persuade this old man to open the transmission array. And even if he tried, this old man definitely wouldn’t listen to him.

One didn’t need to be a genius to know whether someone would listen to the words of a Great World King or a middle Divine Sea realm boy.

Woosh!

The Phoenix Blood Spear leapt into Lin Ming’s hand. In an instant, Lin Ming opened the complete Eight Inner Hidden Gates and released the Heretical God Force to the limit.

Behind Lin Ming, the phantom of the Heretical God Tree began to appear. He only had 10 breaths of time. In 10 breaths of time, he had to defeat this Skybreak Sect Elder and forcefully activate the transmission array.

As for this Skybreak Sect Elder, although his foundation was a mess beyond wobbly, for better or worse he was still a Divine Lord realm master. Lin Ming had to invest his all-out strength in this attack!

The sudden change caused all the nearby martial artists to be surprised. This young man, just what sort of mental illness did he have?

“Brat, what are you doing?”

“Shit, you’re crazy, stop scaring us all…”

A Divine Transformation realm martial artist cursed. However, his voice slowly faded away. Was this terrifying aura really something that a Divine Sea realm martial artist could release? And this solid foundation, this deep and vast true essence… this was definitely an unrivalled genius amongst Divine Sea realm martial artists!

Everyone looked at Lin Ming; even the Skybreak Sect Divine Lord Elder was shocked. This brat, could he actually be attacking him and thinking of forcefully opening the transmission array?

A middle Divine Sea boy actually dared to attack him? Was he crazy?

“Hah!”

Lin Ming roared, not holding anything back. His spear suddenly thrust forwards. From within his inner world, the black hole seed was shot out directly.

Eternal Darkness!

A black hole dark star of the universe was able to attract all matter and was heavy to an incredible degree. If a sun were struck by a black hole, that sun would be completely destroyed!

Destroying a planet was something an Empyrean could achieve. But as for destroying a sun, that was something only a True Divinity could accomplish. Moreover, that was only a possibility.

Lin Ming’s black hole seed hurtled towards the Skybreak Sect Elder.

“Since you want to die so badly, let me help you along!”

The Skybreak Sect Elder wasn’t an idiot. Tian Mingzi had sent him a long distance sound transmission and ordered him to stop this transmission array, and then this youth had attacked him, wanting to forcefully activate the array. It was clear that Tian Mingzi was coming for this youth, to capture or even kill him.

The Skybreak Sect Elder didn’t know why Lin Ming was being chased by Tian Mingzi, nor did he know how Lin Ming had escaped Tian Mingzi’s grasp and was just a step away from fleeing to the lower realms. But, what he was absolutely clear on was that if he weren’t attending this transmission array today, then this boy really might have run away.

This was a golden opportunity for him to perform a valuable service!

Just what sort of character was Tian Mingzi? Within the entire Demondawn Great World, besides Demondawn Heavenly Palace, he was the sovereign king of this world! A normal Holy Lord of a Holy Land wouldn’t have the chance to see Tian Mingzi. If he could help him with something, then that would definitely be a great benefit to him!

He didn’t think that he would be able to rely on this favor to break through into the Holy Lord realm, but he would at least be able to live for several thousand years longer. How could he refuse such a wonderful thing?

Moreover, Lin Ming was extremely young. Although his aura was powerful and he seemed to be an unrivalled genius, the difference in cultivation was simply too great. To block him was a piece of cake. This was nothing but a giant meat pie that had fallen from the skies.

He wildly laughed, “Hahahaha! A little bead like you actually dares to struggle with the splendor of the sun and moon! Seven Star Battle Revolution!”

Behind the Skybreak Sect Elder, seven stars immediately appeared. These seven stars arranged themselves into the shape of the compass. With the seven stars shining, the old man’s aura began to quietly rise, as if he were absorbing power from the starlight of the highest heavens.

A cyan sword leapt into the Skybreak Sect Elder’s hand. All of the starlight completely gathered onto the blade of the sword.

“This sword is called Seven Stars. With a cut of this sword, stars revolve and seasons change!”

The cyan sword swung out, gathering the power of the seven stars and brightly shining atop Lin Ming’s black hole seed.

But in that moment, a brutal and crazy vortex of energy appeared around the black hole seed. That power of starlight was twisted to pieces by this strength before being swallowed!

The black hole seed tore through the endless starlight before crashing into the Skybreak Sect Elder!

“What!?”

The Skybreak Elder was shocked. One of his greatest finishing moves was broken so easily. How could this be!?

He rapidly drew backwards, a curtain of blazing blue starlight appearing around him. This was clearly his protective technique. However, underneath Lin Ming’s attack, this defense simply had no ability to resist. It was helplessly twisted apart and swallowed up by the black hole seed!

All energy, all matter, nothing could stop the swallowing of the black hole seed.

Ka ka ka!

As the curtain of starlight was twisted apart, the Skybreak Elder put forth his final strength and slashed his sword down on the black hole seed. A powerful backlash rolled upwards, causing the Skybreak Elder to spit out a mouthful of blood and fly backwards!

As the other martial artists in the transmission array saw this, all of their eyes went as wide as goggles, none of them able to speak.

Was this young man really just a Divine Sea realm martial artist?

Some people even suspected that Lin Ming was hiding his cultivation. But as they looked at his attacks and the aura he used, he truly seemed like a middle Divine Sea realm martial artist!

Without enough time to respond, Lin Ming’s figure had already flashed and appeared near the transmission array. He pulled out three nine sun jades from his spatial ring, stimulating their energy to the limit, hastily pouring all of it into the transmission array.

Hu – hu – hu – !

Underneath the massive influx of energy, the transmission array wildly revolved, seeming as if it would explode soon!

As the martial artists on the altar saw this, their hearts went cold. In order to speed up the transmission array, this young man had overloaded it past its limits. This was simply a death wish!

To descend from the Divine Realm to the lower realms through a transmission array was filled with incomparable dangers. Even in a well-ordered and meticulous transmission array, there was already a chance that an accident would occur, much less with a transmission array that was going haywire like this. Not only would the space storms be more violent and turbulent, but if the transmission array was destroyed, the person still inside would truly die without a grave!

“He’s insane!”

“Let’s leave. I don’t want to get caught up in this mess and die with him!”

The other martial artists weren’t sure what was happening. They simply didn’t even know why Lin Ming had fought the Skybreak Sect Elder and why he was going so crazy. None of them wanted to mess with this rabid dog.

Then, the seven or eight martial artists all flew down from the transmission array. This was even better for Lin Ming. Like this, he could save more time.

Lin Ming stepped onto the transmission array and a boundless energy erupted. A divine light shot into the sky, piercing through the void. Lin Ming shot upwards, entering the infinitely turbulent space flows!

Just five breaths of time after Lin Ming escaped into the transmission array, a long black sword stabbed through the void, forming a door in space. The black-clothed Tian Mingzi appeared, like the arrival of a death reaper.

As Tian Mingzi appeared, all of those martial artists that planned to go to the lower realms were shocked silly. Who was this? Why was his aura so formidable?

Facing Tian Mingzi, they even found it difficult to breathe. The pressure he gave off was simply too great.

Tian Mingzi didn’t bother with these people. He looked towards the transmission array that was still shining with light, and then his face turned colder than absolute zero.

“You think you can escape me by entering the transmission array?”

Tian Mingzi subconsciously clenched his fists as if he wanted to crush Lin Ming’s bones within them, “If you ran away in such a hurry, then the incarnation that expert gave you must only be able to be used once… if so, then there’s nothing for me to be cautious about.”

Tian Mingzi closed his eyes, his sense sweeping through the runes that were still swirling around the transmission array. These runes were solved by Tian Mingzi, one at a time.

The Skydark Holy Lands’ inheritances in the Space and Time Laws were extremely profound. Just Nether Limitless himself was able to form four spatial mirror image avatars. And as Nether Limitless’s teacher, Tian Mingzi’s comprehension of the Space Laws had reached an unbelievable level.

He thrust out his palms, grasping the void above the transmission array. A deep and vast energy surged out from his body and raced into the turbulent space flows.

This energy formed a massive hand in the turbulent space flows before coming hurtling forwards!

Tian Mingzi’s actions weren’t conventional by any standard. If he were to forcefully tear apart the void to enter and not open a proper spatial channel through a transmission array, he would inevitably encounter the sweeping strength of the space storm. This power of space was something that not even a Great World King could live through.

Rumble rumble rumble.

The crazy and brutal space storm tore into that black hand, constantly wearing it down and weakening it.

A spatial transmission from the Divine Realm to the lower realms reached unimaginable speeds In just five breaths of time, Lin Ming had already flown out to the far off distance.

“Lin Ming! Tian Mingzi is reaching across the void to attack you!”

Mo Eversnow’s voice boomed in Lin Ming’s mind.

“What?!”

Lin Ming’s mind shook. Tian Mingzi had already reached such a degree? He actually possessed the ability to attack him while he was in a transmission array?

Lin Ming turned around to see a massive black hand chasing straight after him from a distant part of the spatial channel. This black hand broke through the barriers of countless space storms, but its strength was also constantly being weakened.

Chapter 1352 – Identity Exposed

Tian Mingzi was already a Great World King powerhouse, and a peak Great World King master at that. He was very close to becoming a half-step Empyrean.

Such a character had an immeasurable disparity with Lin Ming. His attack could instantly turn Lin Ming into smoke and ash!

“Lin Ming, be careful!”

Mo Eversnow anxiously said. At this time, behind Lin Ming, that great hand was roiling forwards with the sound of rumbling thunder, rapidly rushing ahead. Facing this massive hand, Lin Ming was like a tiny bird flying away from an avalanche; he was simply nothing at all.

He absolutely could not contend with this!

Lin Ming was crystal clear that trying to block this attack with his own strength was impossible!

That meant that the only path he had left was to allow the surrounding space storms destroy it. Even the strength of a Great World King didn’t reach the level of ignoring the rules of space.

Lin Ming took a deep breath as energy erupted from his body once more. He suddenly changed directions, flushing towards an area of incomparably chaotic space turbulence!

In that moment, even the usually calm Mo Eversnow paled. In the chaos of the vast space channel, an endless power of space formed massive violent space currents that were trillions of miles long. These tremendous currents lay far in the distance, like the swirling arms of a galaxy. Once one entered these unimaginable space currents, they would encounter the endless crazy power of infinite space storms cutting upon them like unlimited blades. This force could even cut a planet to pieces!

Just how dangerous was it to break into these turbulent space flows? With Lin Ming’s strength, a single misstep would leave him beyond redemption!

Mo Eversnow’s eyes sharpened. Without the slightest sound, she fused her divine soul with Lin Ming’s body, using her comprehension of Space Laws to help Lin Ming avoid any mistakes to the best of her ability.

To pass through this turbulent space flow was like a mortal walking across a steel wire suspended high in the air. They could have successfully passed it a thousand times, but they weren’t even allowed to make a single mistake!

Rumble rumble rumble!

A terrifying current fell on top of Lin Ming. The speed of this turbulence reached unimaginable degrees, its impact causing space to violently shake. This sort of shaking could easily shatter a mountain range!

At that moment, Lin Ming felt a powerful force attacking his insides, as if it wanted to rip his body to pieces! This was not a frontal attack, but only a slight scratch. Even so, this sort of impact could even exterminate an ordinary Divine Lord powerhouse!

Peng!

Lin Ming’s protective true essence shattered like a glass wall being struck by a giant steel ball!

Gate of Death – open!

Lin Ming fiercely grit his teeth and directly opened the Gate of Death. The Gate of Death was located in Lin Ming’s spiritual sea and was like a valve. Once the Gate of Death opened, all of Lin Ming’s astral essence would flood out, erupting with an amount a hundred times greater!

Lin Ming currently only had true essence. But with true essence and astral essence fusing into his body now, the intensity and strength of his body instantly rose to incredible heights. By relying on his formidable mortal body, he forcefully withstood the impact from the power of space.

Roar – !

With the resonant cry of a dragon, the phantom of a True Dragon appeared behind Lin Ming. Lin Ming was like an Azure Dragon swimming through the wild seas, rapidly soaring through the world.

Putting aside Mo Eversnow, just Lin Ming himself had an incredibly high understanding into the Space Laws.

Empyrean Divine Seal was someone who reached large success in the Space and Time Laws. The essence of his primal chaos black hole was to seal away even gods into a singularity of space and time, reaching the boundary of an eternal seal.

During Lin Ming’s year and a half deep sleep in the Divine Realm First Martial Meeting, his Space and Time Laws had reached perfection of the fifth level Concept.

Cross the void!

Seeing a giant space current fall onto him like an endless river, Lin Ming forcefully twisted his body and abruptly passed through a gap in this space current. The massive backlash caused Lin Ming’s body to shake as he spat out a mouthful of blood.

And after that was the giant hand Tian Mingzi had sent out. At this time, this hand was already trillions upon trillions of miles away from Tian Mingzi. No matter how powerful or skilled Tian Mingzi was, or how high his comprehension of the Space Laws was, it was impossible for him to manipulate this hand to nimbly avoid the space storms.

Bang!

A space storm collided with the giant hand. Against this force that could instantly smash apart a million mountain ranges, even a Great World King wasn’t able to withstand this!

Luckily, Tian Mingzi already had some response. However, there was not enough time. With a terrifying explosive sound, this hand was torn in half!

Energy crazily vented outwards. The massive hand violently shook before suddenly dimming down.

Immeasurably far away, Tian Mingzi shook and his complexion paled. His right hand trembled as if a snake had bitten it and a trace of blood flowed down from his fingertips.

All of this fell into the eyes of the surrounding people.

They looked at Tian Mingzi, disbelief thick in their eyes. Such a great person was actually injured?

How had he been injured?

Although these people didn’t know what his status was, they knew that he was undoubtedly a World King level powerhouse; this pressure they felt could not be wrong.

If such a person were to rush here all in order to capture a junior who fled through a transmission array, by all reasoning that should be easy, so how could he have been injured?

Before they could react, Tian Mingzi’s body shook once more. At that moment, blood vessels burst open on his hand as blood spewed out.

The true essence hand he sent out had struck a space current a second time. That half remaining energy was also completely torn apart!

At this time, within the space channel, Lin Ming had completely rid himself of Tian Mingzi’s giant hand. The terrifying explosion of energy was like endless fireworks that detonated behind Lin Ming. Lin Ming’s entire body was covered in thunder and flame, like a meteor in the deep night. Wrapped in this fiery flame and lightning, he rushed out from the space storm!

He had escaped!

Lin Ming’s entire body was covered in blood and he didn’t relax in the slightest. Although he had escaped Tian Mingzi’s chase so far, he had penetrated into a space storm to do so. If he wanted to return to his original space tunnel, he would have to pay a considerable price.

At this time, because Lin Ming had repeatedly passed through gaps in the space storm and was also affected by the exploding energies, his organs had been tremendously injured. If it weren’t for the support of his body transformation technique, he would have been grievously wounded and vomiting blood. If he lost his combat strength in this space storm, his fate could be imagined!

“In crossing the void this time, you still have to continue onwards for several hours!”

Within Lin Ming’s spiritual sea, Mo Eversnow spoke out. She had experience going to the lower realms from the Divine Realm.

“That’s a long time…” Lin Ming clenched his teeth and swallowed down a pill. Even if Tian Mingzi wasn’t chasing him, this would still be a difficult struggle.

…………………..

On Skybreak Planet, Tian Mingzi looked at his injured hand. His hand had been as beautiful and clear as the finest jade, but now many blood vessels had ruptured, causing blood to leak out. His hand now seemed a bit disturbing and gloomy.

At this time, Tian Mingzi coldly sneered. He coldly spat out a single word, “Good.” This caused everyone to be even more confused. All of them fell into a silent panic, too afraid to say a single word.

“What a young hero. You risk the dangers of the violent space turbulence to avoid me chasing you. Your actions are truly bold and courageous, but this makes me even more unable to let you go…”

Tian Mingzi lifted his hand. Without knowing whether this was happiness or anger, everyone in the surroundings began to retreat backwards. They could feel Tian Mingzi emitting a faint killing intent.

“You…”

Tian Mingzi darkly said. With a wave of his right hand, the body of the severely wounded Skybreak Sect Elder flew into Tian Mingzi’s grasp, held by the throat.

In that instant, the Skybreak Sect Elder’s face turned ashen. “F-forgive me, Senior Skydark World King, please calm your anger. This lowly fool is useless and was unable to stop him, I contributed as much as I could…”

The old man quickly explained. He could also feel the killing intent rolling off from Tian Mingzi. With Tian Mingzi’s status, killing him was the same as killing an ant.

“Sky… Skydark World King!?”

Everyone in the surroundings was shocked as they heard the old man speak this name.

They had originally guessed that Tian Mingzi was a World King level character, but they never thought he would turn out to be the Great World King of the Demondawn Great World!

Looking at the entire Divine Realm, Tian Mingzi was a peak World King existence!

Such a character was absolutely not a figure that people of their status could ever come into contact with.

Looking at the Skybreak Sect Elder, Tian Mingzi smiled, happily saying. “I know you made a contribution, but… I want you to make one more. I want information on that youth.”

“Yes… yes… I will tell you…”

The Skybreak Sect Elder hastily nodded, his voice trembling. But before he could continue speaking, he felt Tian Mingzi’s hand tighten on his neck. With a severe pain transmitting through his body, there was a light cracking sound as his spine was shattered by Tian Mingzi!

“There is no need for you to speak. I will examine you myself.”

Still smiling, Tian Mingzi’s soul force broke into the Skybreak Sect Elder’s spiritual sea, brutally scanning through the old man’s memories.

Soul searching technique!

The information that could be described with words was limited in the end; it naturally couldn’t compare to the nuanced detail from a soul search.

But as Tian Mingzi saw Lin Ming’s fight with the old man from before he forcefully entered the void, he was suddenly shocked.

The move that Lin Ming used, Eternal Darkness, how could Tian Mingzi not know what that was? He had watched the entire Divine Realm First Martial Meeting finals with his own eyes.

“Middle Divine Sea realm cultivation, that strange energy black hole, a spear-using martial artist, how could this be…”

Tian Mingzi’s blood red pupils flashed with a brilliant light. “He is Lin Ming!”

Lin Ming…

Tian Mingzi’s eyebrows shot up. Lin Ming’s status was special. If he wanted to kill Lin Ming, he would definitely arouse a great deal of trouble. Once his role in that was revealed, that too was something he wouldn’t be able to shoulder.

Moreover, because of the saint race’s orders, he had planned to make his move in secret. But now, the entire situation had become a chaotic mess. The saint race spy had actually been killed by Lin Ming!

Tian Mingzi didn’t know whether or not Lin Ming realized the status of the saint race spy he killed, but what he was absolutely sure of was that the corpse of that spy was taken away by Lin Ming!

Once Lin Ming gave this corpse to Empyrean Divine Dream or Empyrean Vast Universe, the consequences would be dire!

“I have to… I have to kill Lin Ming!”

This thought flashed through Tian Mingzi’s mind. And, the moment that Lin Ming reached the lower realms was the best chance for Tian Mingzi to attack!

Chapter 1353 – Sky Spill Planet

“Sky… Skydark World King, you… you…”

Near Skybreak Sect’s transmission array, there were several Skybreak Sect disciples as well as the seven or eight martial artists waiting for the transmission array. They had all borne witness to Tian Mingzi killing the Skybreak Sect Elder and then searching his soul!

At this time, they were all horrified. In their eyes, Tian Mingzi was nothing but a cruel and malicious demon, someone who killed without batting an eye, and doing so without rhyme or reason.

Tian Mingzi looked at everyone around him, his complexion indifferent as he said, “I’m sorry. You have all seen something you shouldn’t have.”

Tian Mingzi chasing after Lin Ming was an extremely important matter. If this was revealed, he would definitely be embroiled in a great deal of trouble. If they investigated into this, they would likely uncover his collusion with the saints. If this happened, then he would die without a doubt!

Tian Mingzi naturally wouldn’t allow something like this to happen. Even if these people around him didn’t know of Lin Ming’s status, he still wouldn’t allow any of them to remain alive.

“You… you…!”

Hearing Tian Mingzi’s words, everyone turned pale.

Although martial artists were strong, that didn’t necessarily mean they were brave. When facing death, they were even more afraid, because compared to a mortal, their lives were much more wonderful and long.

“Run!”

Several martial artists cried out in panic, immediately turning tail to escape!

They all used their ultimate trump cards. Some use mystical escape talismans and some even burnt their blood essence. Without regard to the cost, they desperately tried to flee!

All of them escaped in different directions. But in the face of a Great World King, there was simply no chance for any of them to escape.

“If you wish to blame something, blame your luck for being bad.”

In that moment, Tian Mingzi’s aura erupted as he shot out hundreds of black energy swords. The speed of these energy swords was fast beyond belief. The dozen plus people around the transmission array were all instantly pierced through by these energy swords, cut into countless pieces of meat.

These dozen plus people all died on the spot!

Blood rained down along with bits and pieces of flesh. Tian Mingzi stood in this rain of blood, his body emitting an invisible force field. As these drops of blood and flesh approached him, they were automatically pushed aside.

At this time, Tian Mingzi was wearing a voluminous black robe. His face was pale white and his eyes were a deep scarlet red. When looking upon him in this hail of blood, he resembled a demon amongst demons!

“This is truly a shameful matter. I want to kill Lin Ming, but I can’t even sense him when he knocks on my gate. Not just that, but he stole the primordial epoch spirit root, and even my alliance with the saint race was discovered by him.”

Tian Mingzi mumbled to himself. At this time, some people on the planet noticed something unusual occurring.

“What’s going on? Are people fighting?”

Tian Mingzi’s vision turned icy and he coldly snorted. A monstrous demonic energy surged forth from his body, soaring into the skies and causing dark billowing clouds to appear. These dark clouds were heavy and gloomy, as if infinite demons were gathered within them.

Heaven and earth origin energy roared. Strong winds recklessly surged, like an apocalyptic scene.

“What!?”

“Heaven and earth origin energy is being stirred up?”

Skybreak Sect’s martial artists were startled; this wasn’t a natural occurrence.

As they were about to fly out and investigate, at this time, an invisible space covered all of them, enveloping the entirety of Skybreak Sect.

The world outside was completely isolated!

“How is this…!?”

The martial artists that flew into the sky all fell down, an indescribably bleak feeling drowning them.

“Is an unrivalled powerhouse planning to exterminate our sect?”

This thought flashed through the hearts of many people. And then, they knew nothing at all.

Tian Mingzi had used his own domain, a domain completely similar to the black-robed saint spy’s – the Eternal Demon Domain.

Beneath this domain, everyone was isolated.

Tian Mingzi deprived everyone of consciousness but he didn’t kill them. This wasn’t because of some kind-hearted benevolence, but because he didn’t want to make this matter too big. If a peak eighth-grade sect was instantly exterminated like this, that would arouse far too much attention.

“Lin Ming, if he flew to the lower realms, he should have returned to his homeland of the Sky Spill Planet.”

Lin Ming’s information appeared in Tian Mingzi’s mind. The Sky Spill Planet was a tiny insignificant world of the lower realms, a planet that was slightly larger than average. If it weren’t for the saint race’s orders to assassinate Lin Ming, making him research all the available information on Lin Ming, he simply wouldn’t know about such a tiny world of the lower realms like the Sky Spill Planet.

“If Lin Ming returned to the lower realms then he should have gone to the Sky Spill Planet. With his cultivation, then underneath the suppression of the Heavenly Dao Laws, returning to his home world is his limit. It is impossible for him to pass through the infinite space storms to go to other worlds. It is impossible for him to escape my grasp.”

Tian Mingzi gently smiled as he pulled out a golden jade slip. This jade slip was as large as a book. As he sunk his thoughts into it, a celestial starmap of the 3000 great worlds of the Divine Realm and innumerable worlds of the lower realms appeared in his mind. As long as he knew the coordinates of the Sky Spill Planet, then with his strength he would be able to pass through the transmission array and arrive at the Sky Spill Planet in two to four hours.

Tian Mingzi’s lips slowly curved up in a dreadful smile. With his strength and with Lin Ming contained on a single planet, wanting to find him would be as easy as catching a turtle in a jar.

“You have simply chosen the best tomb for yourself. The land of your home world is indeed a suitable place for you to be buried…”

Tian Mingzi’s words were like the whispers of a cackling demon. With a wave of his sleeves, a nine sun jade flew into the energy core of the transmission array. In the next instant, a divine light radiated outwards and Tian Mingzi vanished into the transmission array.

………..

At this time, a hundred quintillion miles away, separated by the vast and infinite void of space, there was a blood red plain. The ends of this plain extended outwards into a thousand mile long mountain range.

This mountain range had a name, Tragic Death Mountain. It constantly exuded demonic energy all year round.

With the loud whinnies of vicious beasts, a team of winged flood dragons landed at the ends of this plain. These winged flood dragons appeared extraordinary, and there was a crowd of heroic and dashingly spirited martial artists on their backs!

Of these people, the one leading them was a tall middle-aged man. In addition, the most standout among them was a man and a woman.

This pair was tall with extraordinary makings. The man was handsome and graceful and the woman was beautiful like an ethereal fairy. They were the Prince and Princess of a Divine Kingdom from the Holy Demon Continent. They could both be called proud children of the heavens!

“Tragic Death Mountain, we’ve finally arrived for our training. We must kill to our heart’s’ content this time!”

The handsome youth excitedly said. He grasped the long sword in his hand, a confident expression on his face.

Every year there were many martial artists that entered this mountain range, but over 90% of them never returned; they wouldn’t even have their corpses or bones remaining. Because they died in such a tragic manner, this mountain range was called Tragic Death Mountain. This was a graveyard for masters but also a treasure trove of great lucky chances. Many martial artists came here to adventure in hopes of being able to gain enough insights and experience to break through to the next boundary and walk even further down their road of martial arts.

It was also because of this reason that even though this mountain range had endlessly great risks, there were still many extreme characters that came every year in order to temper themselves.

“Big Brother, we must be careful. Tragic Death Mountain is unfathomable. Sovereign Father has already advised us to listen to General Wei’s heeding, and the most we can enter into Tragic Death Mountain is about 400 miles.” The Divine Kingdom Princess riding the winged flood dragon said. She wore a military uniform and seemed extremely stern and martial, but this did not diminish her gentleness and stunning looks. She was a rare beauty. With her appearance and her background, she was the ideal woman that many young elites in the Divine Kingdom yearned for.

“What the Princess says is right. The depths of Tragic Death Mountain are far too horrifying. Even if His Majesty were to personally arrive, he still wouldn’t dare to go into the deepest parts of Tragic Death Mountain. That area is a true absolute life-forbidden zone; no one is an exception.”

Behind the beautiful Princess, the tall and burly middle-aged man spoke. He wore a helmet and a suit of armor; he was clearly the General Wei that the Princess was referring to.

The young Prince obviously didn’t seem willing to listen to this advice. He curled his lips, wanting to say several words refuting him and describing just how strong he had grown.

But before he could open his mouth, there was a terrifying rumble that came crashing down from the skies.

Everyone was shocked. They all looked up to see a brilliant meteorite come crashing down with unbelievable speed, tearing through the upper atmosphere as it came smashing down!

In addition to the thunder and flames wrapped around this meteorite, there was also a gray power surrounding it. No one had seen this gray power before. But, if someone skilled in the Space Laws were to see this, they would know that this was the power of the space storm that leaked out from the crack in space. Moreover, this space storm originated from the spatial void that existed between the Divine Realm and the lower realms; it was a terrifying force that could annihilate all of existence!

“What a fast meteorite!” The young Prince cried out in alarm.

And beside him, General Wei was also looking out far into the distance. Then, his mind shook. “No, that’s not right, it doesn’t seem like a meteorite at all. How come I think it looks like… a… a person?”

General Wei put forth a speculation that even he couldn’t believe he said. However, with his eyesight that far surpassed that of normal martial artists, he could see that this was indeed a person.

Everyone that heard him was shocked. This was a person?

At this time, that ‘meteorite’ finally crashed to the earth. And, the point it landed at was that mountain range filled with demonic energy and also known as a life-forbidden zone – Tragic Death Mountain!

Bang!

In that instant, an incomparably terrifying explosion rolled up the earth for a thousand miles. The mountain range of Tragic Death Mountain was directly lifted up into the air and even the world was pierced through. The magma roiling beneath the ground shot into the skies, flooding forth like massive tsunamis. The horrifying shockwaves crushed the entirety of Tragic Death Mountain, rolling outwards with an unstoppable momentum.

“Shit! Danger!”

General Wei was shocked. He immediately set down an enchantment of energy, protecting those people near him.

A titanic shockwave crashed into General Wei’s energy enchantment. His face paled as his insides tumbled about, nearly causing him to vomit blood.

Even from such a distance, he had withstood less than a ten-thousandth of the impact force from just the aftermath shockwaves, and yet that had caused him to be injured. General Wei found it hard to imagine the might of the crash just now.

The storm quickly passed. Everyone opened their eyes wide to see the place where that ‘meteorite’ had landed. As they did, everyone was dumbfounded, their mouths falling open. Even the normally calm General Wei was unable to regain his calm for a long time.

Tragic Death Mountain, the legendary life-forbidden zone filled with endless demons, the legendary mountain range where countless masters had perished, had actually been over 70% destroyed!

Let alone those demons, not even the mountain range was left intact!

Just what kind of horrifying strength was this?

Everyone felt as if they were in a dream. But, that bubbling magma that was still surging upwards from deep underground told everyone that what they were seeing was not an illusion at all.

“Ge-general Wei, you said that meteorite just now was a person?”

The Divine Kingdom Princess shivered as she recalled this.

Everyone else also looked towards General Wei.

General Wei was still bewildered. He opened his mouth with some difficulty, saying, “I… I might have been mistaken.”

Chapter 1359 – Burn

In the moment that the spear light and sword light crossed, the world changed colors and all light seemed to disappear. A wild and violent energy erupted outwards and the earth was blown apart as if a titanic hammer struck it. The world hollowed, forming a massive crater in the ground that was dozens of miles wide. Magma sprayed into the air, and even nearby mountains were flattened like collapsing sand dunes.

This was a battle between extreme Divine Sea powerhouses, or, it was more accurate to say Divine Lord level powerhouses. This was the terrifying battlefield they created on a world of the lower realms!

Although this strength wasn’t able to destroy a planet, wiping out all life here would simply be a matter of time!

The energy shockwaves swept out for a thousand miles before fading away. The earth was sundered and bubbling magma gushed out as if the world was bleeding. This was a ghastly sight.

Strong winds howled through the air. Tian Mingzi’s clothes fluttered in the wind. There was a trace of blood on Tian Mingzi’s eight foot long sword; this blood belonged to Lin Ming.

Stretching out his finger, Tian Mingzi stroked the sword edge and wiped away that trace of blood before gently licking it. At that time, Tian Mingzi’s face, coupled with that scarlet blood, appeared increasingly monstrous.

Lin Ming grasped the Phoenix Blood Spear, his body floating dozens of miles away from Tian Mingzi. In that horrifying impact just now, his right arm had shattered and his left shoulder had also been pierced through by sword light. His collar bones were visible through his flesh, blood leaking down his arm and flowing over the Phoenix Blood Spear like a wandering red snake.

Tian Mingzi had severed his hand to form a flesh and blood avatar, and even added in a wisp of his soul to shape it. The strength of Tian Mingzi’s avatar far surpassed Lin Ming’s imagination! If it weren’t for Lin Ming practicing the body transformation technique, that strike just now would have turned him to mush!

If this battle continued then Lin Ming would undoubtedly die!

“Lin Ming!”

In Lin Ming’s mind, Mo Eversnow’s concerned and anxious voice echoed outwards. Currently, she wasn’t able to help Lin Ming in any way. This made her feel extremely uncomfortable.

Tian Mingzi was her absolute mortal enemy, someone whom she could not stand to live under the same skies with. After all sorts of strange circumstances and meandering paths, she had once again been forced into a desperate situation by him. Mo Eversnow had already died once, so she no longer cared about herself, but, how could she look on as Lin Ming died here?

Mo Eversnow took a deep shuddering breath, unable to remain calm. Even her fingers faintly shivered. She rarely lost her composure like this. This wasn’t because of fear, but because of hate!

She hated Tian Mingzi to the extreme!

“Lin Ming, do you have a plan?”

Mo Eversnow said, forcefully suppressing the rage in her voice.

“I have no good method, I can only fight!”

After being locked down by Tian Mingzi and also covered in his 10,000 Demon Domain, Lin Ming was truly forced into a dead end. A moment ago, because Tian Mingzi had attacked with his all-out strength, the 10,000 Demon Domain had weakened for a brief moment, to the point that it could have been torn apart. However, Lin Ming had no way of diverting any attention to do that.

As soon as the collision finished, that domain had vaguely floated back around Lin Ming, locking him back in a cage.

In terms of domain ranks, whether it was the grandmist space or the divine dream space, both of them blew past the 10,000 Demon Domain. But, the essential difference was the disparity in cultivation and comprehension of Laws. This caused Lin Ming to be unable to pressure Tian Mingzi.

Tian Mingzi was someone who had lived for at least 50,000 years and Lin Ming was just over 30 years old. Lin Ming was only a fraction of Tian Mingzi’s age, so how could there be any comparison between the heights in Laws that they both reached?

Separated by a distance of several dozen miles, Tian Mingzi began to casually walk through the void towards Lin Ming.

Although his steps were slow, every step he took crossed one or two miles. In another 20-30 steps, he would reach Lin Ming.

There was silence, only a terrible silence. The only sound that broke through the gloomy silence was the sound of Tian Mingzi’s steps crossing through the void, as if the god of death were slowly approaching.

In one more strike, Lin Ming would absolutely suffer a life-threatening wound.

In the third strike, he might die!

Mo Eversnow looked at Tian Mingzi slowly approaching, and her eyes flashed with a cold light. Then, she suddenly said, “Lin Ming, in these past years my soul force has been restored a great deal, and as for you, through your training in Divine Dream Heavenly Palace, your connection with the Magic Cube has become increasingly close. We can make an attempt together, to join our strength and stimulate the movement of the Magic Cube. If we can do that then it will give us the opening we need to defeat Tian Mingzi!”

Mo Eversnow suddenly suggested. She actually wanted to galvanize the power of the Magic Cube to deal with Tian Mingzi!

The Magic Cube had always been passively defending. Was it possible to activate it so that it could attack on its own?

Lin Ming’s mind stirred. At this time, he could only desperately struggle. The Magic Cube was a divine tool of soul attacks. If he could stimulate the movement of the Magic Cube and destroy the wisp of soul that Tian Mingzi left in his avatar, then his avatar would only have its spirit body remaining. Without Tian Mingzi’s comprehensions of Laws, the avatar would be nothing to fear.

Lin Ming wanted to immediately agree and bet on this final tactic.

But just as he was about to speak, he seemed to suddenly wake up.

Did Mo Eversnow really think this was possible?

In Divine Dream Heavenly Palace, Lin Ming had indeed become closer to the Magic Cube. But, he also knew that he still fell far short of being able to stir its movements to kill an enemy.

When Mo Eversnow had suggested that the two of them join their strength together to stimulate the Magic Cube, the truth was that this was only an excuse.

In the end, Mo Eversnow wanted to rely on her own strength to activate the Magic Cube.

In the past, when the Verdant Feather Holy Lands was destroyed, Mo Eversnow had stimulated the movement of the Magic Cube by using the entirety of her strength. Because of that, she had paid a deep price, even losing her body in the process. And that had been at her peak state. Now, with her current condition, there was only a single way for her to possibly arouse the Magic Cube… and that was to completely burn up her divine soul.

With the price of her death, she would trade that for one final attack!

This was absolutely not what Lin Ming wanted. He would rather fall beyond redemption and perish than allow Mo Eversnow to die like this!

“Lin Ming, what are you still thinking about? This is our only chance. If Tian Mingzi attacks one more time, your injuries will be much heavier. At that time, even if we killed Tian Mingzi, we would be nothing but lamps without oil. At that point, even Nether Limitless and the others would be able to kill us.”

Mo Eversnow’s voice was hurried.

Lin Ming solemnly said, “Miss Mo, in I, Lin Ming’s life, whether it is now or in the future, I will not have your sacrifice yourself for me. I will not use your death to exchange for my own life. To step onto the peak of martial arts is the goal that I have been chasing through in my life, but even that peak of martial arts is far inferior to Miss Mo’s life!”

As Lin Ming said these words, Mo Eversnow was stunned. She didn’t think that Lin Ming would see through her intentions. Indeed, from the very start she had never planned to rely on Lin Ming’s strength. Rather, she wanted to burn away her divine soul and stimulate the Magic Cube, perishing together with Tian Mingzi’s avatar. And now, as Lin Ming said these words, Mo Eversnow felt her heart inexplicably touched in the softest, most defenseless parts of her soul. She didn’t know why, but she felt a twisting pain as a crystal clear teardrop quietly fell down her cheek.

“Big Sister, why are you crying?”

Within the Magic Cube space, the sleeping Fishy seemed to sense something happening. She opened her eyes and saw that a tear had fallen down from the corner of Mo Eversnow’s eye.

Without knowing what happened, Fishy haplessly looked at Mo Eversnow. Then, she reached out her little hand and gently wiped away this single drop of ‘soul tears’.

Eyes could cry. This could be sadness, but it could also be a lie, deceit, an act…

But if a soul form were to cry, that would only be because they were sad to the extreme, grieving to the extreme, or perhaps… their heart was touched.

Mo Eversnow softly patted Fishy’s head. She said in a gentle voice, “Big Sister is alright. From now on, you must be a good girl and listen to your Big Brother Lin Ming’s words…”

As she spoke, Mo Eversnow’s body gradually floated upwards. In that instant, her soul form began to slowly flash. Beautiful and enchanting blue and white rays of light radiated from Mo Eversnow’s body, dazzling to the eyes…

She was burning her divine soul!

“Miss Mo, you – !”

Lin Ming urgently cried out, alarmed.

“…Lin Ming, do you know? 50,000 years ago, I had to watch with my own eyes as the Verdant Father Holy Lands was destroyed in front of me. I lacked the strength, and was unable to stop Tian Mingzi. At that time, the Verdant Feather Holy Lands was the most important thing to me! My family and my foundation, my everything was there. Now, 50,000 years later, I must watch once more as Tian Mingzi destroys you, and right now, you are the most important person in my life. I, I will not allow this cycle to repeat itself once more, I will not! I won’t!”

As Mo Eversnow spoke, her strength constantly flowed into the Magic Cube. Lin Ming could even feel the Magic Cube beating within his body, as if it were about to fly out from within him!

“You have your determination, but I have my oath. If you die, there is no reason for me to continue living on!” Mo Eversnow’s voice was incomparably firm and resolute.

The palpitations of the Magic Cube became increasingly intense! The truth was that the Magic Cube had no master. As the crystallized form of the universe’s ‘divine’, there was no mortal that was able to completely control it. And, in terms of being able to control the power of the Magic Cube, Mo Eversnow far surpassed Lin Ming.

At the moment that Mo Eversnow started to burn her own soul, Lin Ming felt an indescribably heart-rending pain tear through his body, as if there were something exploding within his inner world!

He could not allow Mo Eversnow to continue. He could not allow her to burn her divine soul. Right now, Mo Eversnow only had her divine soul remaining. Once she burnt that, she would truly perish! Not even a True Divinity would be able to save her!

In this moment, an indescribably wild and brutal strength ignited within Lin Ming’s body, exploding outwards!

The implacable black hole seed came to a grinding halt before it rapidly began to spin in reverse. From that black hole seed which originally nothing could escape, a torrential amount of energy began gushing forth!

“Tian Mingzi! I’LL KILL YOU!”

Lin Ming roared out. A gargantuan amount of energy began to swell forth from his body. If he didn’t release this energy, his body would explode!

Peng peng peng!

Lin Ming’s blood vessels ruptured and blood rained down. All of his strength was poured into the Phoenix Blood Spear. The Phoenix Blood Spear began to keen in excitement, as if a True Dragon was awakening within it!

In the past, you were the one to protect me…

And now, I should be the one to protect you…

No matter what, whether in the past, in the present, or in the future, I will not watch you burn your soul and die for me.

Even if I must overdraw my life, even if I must fall here, I will defeat Tian Mingzi!

In that moment, all sounds faded away from Lin Ming’s mind. All he could hear was the clarion cry of his own mind.

“My life’s blood essence, burn for me!”

Lin Ming roared. In that moment, he began to burn his blood essence without reservation!

A full 50% of his blood essence began to combust!

Even if Lin Ming had perfectly opened the Gates of Life and Death, he absolutely could not withstand such a consumption of blood essence!

“Lin Ming… you!”

Mo Eversnow froze. Burning 50% of his blood essence, what sort of concept was that? Did he not think of the ramifications!?!?

Lin Ming truly didn’t care about any consequences right now. If he couldn’t stop the Magic Cube from activating, then he could only defeat Tian Mingzi!

With half his blood essence as the price, this was Lin Ming’s last stand!

The sky trembled and the earth began to moan in grief. The power of thunder, the power of fire, the power of space, the power of time, all strengths gathered within Lin Ming’s spear light. At this moment, any technique had lost meaning. This was Lin Ming’s ultimate attack that came at the price of burning his own life!

“What? You actually…!”

With a superiority in all aspects and controlling the entire situation so far, Tian Mingzi had held utter confidence. But now, as he saw Lin Ming suddenly erupt with such a terrifying striking power, even his complexion paled.

“Samsara of the heavens and earth, the myriad Laws shall die out, only my demonic path shall remain immortal and forever!”

Tian Mingzi’s hands formed dao patterns in the air. In front of him, a gray wheel appeared. This wheel had tens of thousands of seal, each seal seeming to contain its own world. With tens of thousands of charms, it was like facing tens of thousands of worlds.

“Heaven Absorbing Demon Art – Counterforce!”

Tian Mingzi had used the transcendent divine might belonging to Empyrean Demondawn!

In the past, Tian Mingzi had entered Demondawn Heavenly Palace and studied the Heaven Absorbing Demon Art from Empyrean Demondawn. Although this transcendent divine might was the same one that Xiao Moxian used, it was actually far more formidable.

The Heaven Absorbing Demon Art could suck in others’ abilities and then dissolve these abilities with demonic strength before using them to strike back at the enemy.

Heaven Absorbing Demon Art Counterforce was one of the attack states of the Heaven Absorbing Demon Art.

Underneath the hands of Xiao Moxian, the energy gushing forth from the Heaven Absorbing Demon Art was able to form a vortex of energy. But in Tian Mingzi’s control, it was actually able to form a demon god disc.

In that moment, Lin Ming’s long spear smashed into the demon god disc. A terrifying divine light shot out, piercing through the heavens, sundering the earth!

In that horrifying explosion, Tian Mingzi’s 10,000 Demon Domain was completely destroyed!

Puff!

The moment that the 10,000 Demon Domain was destroyed, Tian Mingzi suffered a tremendous backlash that caused him to vomit blood.

As Tian Mingzi spat out a mouthful of blood in the air, he couldn’t believe his own eyes. Lin Ming, with his middle Divine Sea cultivation, had actually wounded his avatar, who possessed the Law comprehensions of a Great World King as well as the spirit body of a Great World King?

Ka ka ka!

Underneath Lin Ming’s attack, a final strike that cost half his blood essence, this demon god disc also began to crack!

“What!?”

Tian Mingzi was shocked. He began to withdraw but it was far too late.

The Phoenix Blood Spear rushed forth like a raging Azure Dragon, shattering that demon god disc and hurtling past its broken pieces, thrusting straight towards Tian Mingzi’s heart.

“Do you really think this strike can kill me!?”

Tian Mingzi shouted out loud as he brought his sword slashing down on Lin Ming’s spear light.

Bang!

Spear light and sword light collided. All sounds faded away. Tian Mingzi only felt a powerful force wash through him, sending his sword flying away. The meridians in his body had broken apart in countless places and blood poured out from his mouth, gushing into the skies.

In this strike, he had truly been grievously wounded by Lin Ming. A middle Divine Sea realm junior had broken his own domain and even severely wounded his avatar at the same time?

Tian Mingzi found this impossible to believe!

And several hundred miles away, this final strike had been seen by Nether Limitless and the others. All of them were incomparably shocked. They would never have dreamed that Lin Ming was powerful to such a degree that even their Honorable Master would be wounded to such an extent!

As Nether Limitless looked lost and dazed, there was a flash in front of his eyes. A figure seemed to teleport right in front of him.

This person’s body was bathed in blood. He was like an asura demon that had crawled up from the blood ponds of hell!

“Lin… Lin Ming…”

Nether Limitless’s body stiffened. At this moment, there was an excruciating pain in his chest. As he looked down, he saw Lin Ming’s right hand had penetrated into his chest and grabbed onto his beating heart.

Chapter 1361 – Once More Into the Blood Slaughter Steppes

When pushed into a corner, even a bunny would bite back. With a disciple taking the lead, some people immediately risked their lives to attack Tian Mingzi!

Tian Mingzi sneered. Right now he was indeed seriously wounded, but even if he only had 40% of his original strength left, he was still on the same level of strength as Lin Ming in his peak state. How could these young disciples of the Skydark Holy Lands possibly hope to contend with him?

Bang!

The power of the domain erupted. The two disciples in the lead suddenly felt the energy within their bodies be completely suppressed by Tian Mingzi’s domain!

Tian Mingzi grasped both of their foreheads.

“Heaven Absorbing Demon Art!”

A black line shined forth. The two young elites had all of their blood vitality and energy directly drained dry by Tian Mingzi!

“Honorable Master, please forgive us!”

These young disciples didn’t have the courage to face Tian Mingzi to begin with, and now that they saw just how great the disparity of strength was between them, that tiny bit of confidence they had left completely crumbled. They all knelt to the floor and began to beg for mercy.

Tian Mingzi’s complexion was coldly indifferent. “You already know far too much. Although I can make a heart demon oath to restrain you, you will inevitably be captured by others and have your souls searched. If that were to happen, my affairs would naturally be exposed. If you can kindly and quietly die right now, I will treat your families well.

As Tian Mingzi spoke, his hands formed a wheel in the air. This was the wheel disk evolved from the Heaven Absorbing Demon Art. As the young disciples saw this, their faces turned ash-gray with despair, their hearts and minds quaking.

No matter what they did, no matter what they said, it wouldn’t avert their inevitable deaths.

Every disciple of the Skydark Holy Lands was swallowed up by this wheel disk, turning into pure blood vitality and energy that was then absorbed by Tian Mingzi. Tian Mingzi felt his strength rapidly restoring itself.

Miserable wails and pained howls echoed through the skies. In just a moment, all 12 disciples that had been sent to the Sky Spill Planet had been sucked dry by Tian Mingzi!

12 geniuses of a Great World King influence had died a tragic and violent death!

Tian Mingzi didn’t care about these losses at all.

To most World King influences, the reason they raised the new generation and trained the elites was all for the future posterity of their family and their sect. They hoped that once the older generation declined, the new one would take their place and allow their sect to carry on into a brighter future.

But to Tian Mingzi, the reason he raised juniors was only to raise underlings and increase the number of chess pieces he had. He needed them for key moments in order to complete his plans.

And now was the time to use these juniors!

Even though they were also a World King Holy Land, there was such a difference. This was because Tian Mingzi’s ambitions were far too great. He wanted to become a True Divinity and seek the road to eternal life. The reason he founded the Skydark Holy Lands was all in order to create a tool to aid him in the future. If necessary, he was willing to discard the entire Skydark Holy Lands, and what did it matter to him if he did?

After absorbing these 12 disciples, Tian Mingzi’s strength returned. He wasn’t any weaker than he was when he first battled Lin Ming.

But in comparison, Lin Ming had already burnt half his blood essence and had received major wounds. Underneath these completely distortional physical states, the disparity between them was even more obvious!

………

Woosh!

The dazzling shuttle flashed through the void. In every blink of the eye, Lin Ming crossed 300-400 miles.

The shuttle passed through the void again and again. After innumerable times, when Lin Ming pierced through the void once more, vast and boundless blood red plains were presented before him!

Gloomy red clouds hung low above the plains, as if they were about to drop blood. All of the surroundings seemed constrained and depressed. These plains were called the Blood Slaughter Steppes!

After so many years away, Lin Ming had finally reappeared!

As Lin Ming entered the Blood Slaughter Steppes, his body violently shook. He nearly fell down from the space shuttle!

At this time, his nose and ears were dripping blood. His face was whiter than paper and his body was shivering.

“Lin Ming…”

In the Magic Cube space, the corners of Mo Eversnow’s eyes were wet with tears.

When Mo Eversnow had first begun combusting her soul, Lin Ming had felt a heart-piercing and gut-wrenching pain, both physical and emotional. But when Lin Ming had burnt half his blood essence, Mo Eversnow was also heartbroken.

To burn half his blood essence at once, that was something that would greatly affect Lin Ming’s future accomplishments. This loss was far too great!

“Lin Ming… why would you do that… in that battle, you burned half your blood essence. Do you know how bright your future is? But because of this…”

Lin Ming’s desperate gamble had indeed won them a slim chance of survival. But in Mo Eversnow’s eyes, this slim chance might not be able to be sustained.

For this unknown chance to save her and him, he had paid such a deep and painful price. Mo Eversnow felt a deep sadness in her heart because of this.

She transformed into a soul form in front of Lin Ming, gently stroking his cheeks. In her eyes, brilliant crystalline tears shined light diamonds.

“If I burn my blood essence, I can still find ways to make up for it. But Miss Mo, if you truly burnt your soul, you would have perished there. Even if I stepped into the realm of True Divinity in the future, there would still be nothing I could do!”

At this time, Lin Ming was bleeding from every orifice and his face was as pale as paper. But even so, he was still gently smiling. This smiling face was just like the honest expression of a neighborhood boy, as bright and warm as the rays of the sun. It was a rarely seen emotion on Lin Ming’s face.

As Mo Eversnow saw this smile, her heart was touched once more. “Lin Ming, from now on, please call me senior-apprentice sister…”

Lin Ming had already joined the Verdant Feather Holy Lands, and in the future, when the Verdant Feather Holy Lands was reconstructed, he and Mo Eversnow would come from the same sect. It was right for him to call her senior-apprentice sister.

“Of course, Senior-apprentice Sister.”

Lin Ming suddenly said. He didn’t like to call her Miss Mo because he felt that this name was too distant, like a stranger. Even so, if he didn’t call her Miss Mo, he didn’t know what else to call her. He naturally couldn’t call by her name, Eversnow. Throughout all these years, Mo Eversnow had the status of a half-master to him, and in Lin Ming’s mind, he held nothing but the greatest respect for her.

As Lin Ming saw Mo Eversnow still anxious, he said, “Senior-apprentice Sister, rest assured that even if I burnt 50% of my blood essence, or even burnt 70% of my blood essence, as long as I don’t die, I can still become an Empyrean in the future and become a True Divinity. Although it is difficult to restore my blood essence after burning so much, it isn’t an impossible feat.”

Although Lin Ming said this, Mo Eversnow felt a heaviness in her heart.

Restoring his blood essence; wasn’t that easier said than done?

The stronger a martial artist was, the more vivid and vibrant their blood vitality was, the more difficult it was to restore their blood essence.

If one was a lower realms Life Destruction martial artist with an extremely sloppy foundation, then they could restore their blood essence in the lower realms by finding some heavenly materials. Of course, these so-called ‘heavenly materials’ would be nothing but scraps to the geniuses of a Great World King Holy Land, something that they wouldn’t bother picking up if they saw it on the side of the road.

This was also reasonable. For a lower realms Life Destruction martial artist, even if they burnt all of their blood essence without a single drop remaining, how much strength could they possibly display?

But for someone like Lin Ming, not only was his foundation incomparably solid and deep, but his blood vitality, his fires of life, were like raging flames that would never subside. Wanting to restore his blood essence would be extremely difficult. Even if Lin Ming opened the Gate of Life and gained the ability to restore his blood essence, the most he could restore was 10-20%.

Mo Eversnow seemed to want to say something, but Lin Ming first said, “Senior-apprentice Sister, there is no need to speak. I have already considered everything, it’s just that there are many matters that even I am unsure of what will happen…”

As Lin Ming spoke, his complexion immediately changed.

Just now, he felt a strong sense lock onto him. This sense was just like a leech latching onto his body; it was impossible for him to shield against it!

This sense was gloomy, dreadful, and powerful. There was no need to consider who it came from… there could only be one person – Tian Mingzi!

Lin Ming never expected that his attack that cost half his blood essence would be able to destroy Tian Mingzi’s avatar. But, he never imagined that Tian Mingzi would recover so quickly, and would even be chasing after him right now!

At this time, Lin Ming’s situation was extremely poor. If he was overtaken, there would be nothing awaiting him but death!

“Tian Mingzi?”

Mo Eversnow saw Lin Ming’s changing expression and correctly guessed that Tian Mingzi had locked onto him.

Tian Mingzi was simply far too formidable and he had studied countless different arcane abilities. After remembering a person’s aura, no matter if they ascended to heaven or hell, he could still track them down!

The only possibility for Lin Ming to prevent this was if he cultivated the Divine Dream Law’s appearance changing technique to the point of shifting his bones and even changing the aura of his soul. But now, his proficiency in this skill was far too lacking.

“Go!” Lin Ming activated the space shuttle to tear through the void once more!

In just an incense stick of time after Lin Ming disappeared, at the point where he had been standing, the void was torn open. A black-robed Tian Mingzi slowly walked out.

Although his avatar only had a Divine Sea realm cultivation, he didn’t need a magic tool to shift through the void of the lower realms and chase Lin Ming. This wasn’t because Lin Ming’s space shuttle was slow, but because Tian Mingzi’s Space Laws were far too fierce. Although the cultivation of his avatar was lacking, it had actually inherited the Laws of Tian Mingzi’s true body.

“These plains…”

Tian Mingzi stopped where he was, not immediately entering.

He could make out the strangeness of the Blood Slaughter Steppes with a single glance. By all reasoning, this was a place that shouldn’t exist in the worlds of the lower realms. However, as he thought of the ash-gray light barrier that surrounded the entirety of the Sky Spill Planet, he could accept this.

“Could it be that the unknown master who laid down the barrier to protect the Sky Spill Continent did so because of these red plains? These plains have the aura of a curse… could this be left behind by the transcendent divine might, the God Curse Art…?”

Tian Mingzi thought to himself. His intuition was not wrong; the Blood Slaughter Steppes was indeed cursed.

In the Holy Demon Continent, the Blood Slaughter Steppes was known as a forbidden land for all high stage Life Destruction martial artists and above. If a high stage Life Destruction martial artist were to enter, they would be fine at the start, but afterwards they would eventually suffer a tragic and miserable death in the future. This was the result of a curse!

Once or twice couldn’t be considered anything at all. But, in the past, many Divine Sea masters of the Holy Demon Continent, Demon Emperors, Fey Emperors, and countless others, had been killed off by the curse of the Blood Slaughter Steppes. After that, there was no high stage Life Destruction martial artist that dared to enter the Blood Slaughter Steppes.

Thus, the Blood Slaughter Steppes and the Skysplit Towers here were all considered a great arena for martial artists below the Life Destruction realm.

For high stage Life Destruction martial artists and Divine Sea martial artists, unless they became twelve-winged Heavenly Demons beforehand in the Skysplit Towers, they would be cursed by the Blood Slaughter Steppes.

“God Curse Art… this shouldn’t have been deliberately used. Rather, two extreme masters once battled here, and one of them used the God Curse Art. The aftermath of that battle covered this entire region, cursing this land. What a terrifying transcendent divine might. Even after tens of thousands of years or even hundreds of thousands of years, this land still remains affected as before, without the curse dissipating.”

Tian Mingzi’s avatar had inherited the experiences of his true self. He quickly realized the reason for this cursed land.

In the past, those characters that fought were likely Empyreans. But even if they were Empyreans and the aftermath of their battle was spread out here, it should still have faded away with time…

Chapter 1362 – Into the Eternal Demon Abyss Once More

It was for a full half hour that Tian Mingzi stood quietly in front of the Blood Slaughter Steppes. Only then did he start to slowly fly in.

The remaining curse of an Empyrean master, even if it wasn’t done on purpose, and even if it was just the aftermath from a great battle 100,000 years ago, still had to be dealt with carefully.

Of course, it was Tian Mingzi’s avatar that was entering the Blood Slaughter Steppes and it would be his avatar that withstood the curse. Even if his avatar wasn’t able to avoid the power of the curse, it wouldn’t instantly kill him upon entering. The power of this kind of curse would often take days, weeks, or even months before it manifested into a visible role.

“If Lin Ming flew in here, does that mean there is something special about this place? Could these blood red plains possibly be the reason why Lin Ming was able to become the number one genius of the Divine Realm, even though he originated from the lower realms?”

Tian Mingzi couldn’t help but think of this. He felt increasingly sure that this trip to the Sky Spill Planet was the right choice. Who would have thought that a world of the lower realms would actually possess such a heaven-shaking secret?

“Lin Ming, I thought you were a dark star, but I never imagined you would be my lucky star too. Without you, how would I know about the lucky chances here? But what a pity, no matter what secrets you possess, all of them will be mine! Hahaha!”

Tian Mingzi laughed out loud. As he flew into the Blood Slaughter Steppes, his speed increased.

………..

At this time, at one of the Blood Slaughter Steppes’ 12 Skysplit Towers, Polaris Tower –

On Polaris Tower’s fourth floor, in an extravagant grand hall, seven or eight old men in long robes were sitting around a circular table, discussing the candidacy of a new High Lord.

The supreme master of a Skysplit Tower was the Tower Master, but beneath the Tower Master were the High Lords. These High Lords were all previous geniuses of the Skysplit Towers. After passing through countless life or death massacres, they slowly climbed to the position of a High Lord.

These seven or eight High Lords hadn’t been in their position for very long. If one had to think of a reason, it was because of the great catastrophe that occurred at the Blood Slaughter Steppes 10 years ago. Because of the catastrophe, several Tower Masters, even more High Lords, and the previous Steppes Master himself had died. The Steppes Master had been replaced by a human, causing the leadership of the 12 Skysplit Towers to be reshuffled.

That sort of terrifying earthquake had never happened even in the last 10,000 years of the Blood Slaughter Steppes!

And the current Steppes Master was incomparably mysterious. Since becoming the Steppes Master he had yet to be seen.

Some rumors said that he had closed up deep in seclusion, and some rumors said that he had entered the Eternal Demon Abyss. There were even some people that said he had broken through the void with his martial arts and ascended.

But, no matter which view it was, there was one thing that everyone agreed upon, and that was that the current Steppes Master was one of the most terrifying existences in the entirety of the Holy Demon Continent!

The current Tower Master of Polaris Tower was someone who had climbed up the chaos left behind by that disaster. His strength was decent to begin with and it was said that he had the support of the current Steppes Master. Thus, his prestige had soared to the heavens, and even the several supervisory Elders of the Blood Slaughter Steppes treated him as an equal.

Facing this Tower Master that held true power, the High Lords present were all cautious and in awe. They were afraid to meet the eyes of the Polaris Tower Master.

The candidacy of a new High Lord was an important matter for any Skysplit Tower. The other High Lords were all slowly waiting for the final decision of the Polaris Tower Master.

As the Polaris Tower Master was about to say something, the entire meeting hall shook. The power of space suddenly violently shook! There were High Lords that understood the Space Laws, but even they couldn’t understand just why such a terrifying aura had covered the entire meeting hall!

“What is happening!?”

Everyone was shocked. There was a giant protective array formation that surrounded the periphery of Polaris Tower, and the inside was also covered with layers upon layers of array formations with countless protections. Numerous array formations protected the meeting hall in a giant sphere. They just couldn’t understand why a dreadful aura suddenly shrouded the entire area.

“Who is it!?”

The Polaris Tower Master immediately stood up, his hand tracing his spatial ring. At this time, in front of everyone, the void was torn apart and a young man with a pale face and black robes fell down from a space shuttle, appearing in the meeting hall like a ghost.

As the people present saw this, their eyes widened like dishes.

There were no transmission arrays in the meeting hall. If this black-robed man hadn’t gone through a transmission array, then could he have actually torn through the void with his bare hands and directly teleported here!?

Not just that, but the meeting hall and Skysplit Tower itself was filled with layers of array formations!

Could a late Divine Sea realm master really be so terrifying?

As the leader of the people here, the Polaris Tower Master had a nervous expression. In facing such an uninvited visitor, they were all in a critical situation!

However, as he saw Lin Ming’s face, he was completely startled. The horror and fear on his face immediately changed into shock and incredulous disbelief.

At once, a deep sense of awe and reverence swelled up within him. He knelt upon the ground.

“Subordinate greets the Steppes Master!”

The Polaris Tower Master recognized Lin Ming. When Lin Ming killed the last Steppes Master, he had appointed new supervisory Elders and Tower Masters. The Polaris Tower Master had been one of these people.

As for the so-called ‘support’ of the Steppes Master, that was the spell that Lin Ming had implanted within their bodies. If they had the thought of ever betraying Lin Ming, the spell would activate and they would be reduced to ash.

But it was because of this relationship that they were able to be thought of as trusted subordinates of Lin Ming. This was because of the spell in their bodies. If someone dared to kill them, Lin Ming would also know of this, and nobody in the entire Blood Slaughter Steppes had the courage to move against Lin Ming. Lin Ming’s fame and prestige was far too great. Initially, he had broken through the traps of his enemies and slaughtered them like chickens. Even under the onslaught of two Divine Sea masters, Lin Ming had still killed them. As for the others, all he had to do was open his domain and they all died!

Against such a terrifying character, how could anyone dare to revolt?

“Steppes Master? This black-clothed youth is the mythical Steppes Master? One of the peak existences of the entire Holy Demon Continent?”

As the other High Lords heard the Polaris Tower Master call out Lin Ming’s name, they were all stunned speechless. This sort of feeling was the same as an ordinary Holy Lord of the Divine Realm suddenly encountering a peak Empyrean.

Several of them immediately kneeled on the ground, but some others were frozen solid.

“Open the transmission array, I must go to the Eternal Demon Abyss!”

Lin Ming succinctly said, not bothering with how the other people here responded. Time was of the essence; he could feel Tian Mingzi approaching him faster and faster!

“Eternal Demon Abyss?” The Polaris Tower Master asked in a daze, “The Eternal Demon Abyss is currently undergoing a period of eruption. If you go there now…”

Every dozen years or so, or even several dozen years, the Eternal Demon Abyss would erupt. These eruptions did not come at a fixed time, and once the Eternal Demon Abyss erupted, everything inside would perish!

At the same time, after every eruption, a massive number of demon god bones and other treasures would spew forth from deep within the Eternal Demon Abyss. These were treasures that people from the Blood Slaughter Steppes would risk their lives to obtain.

Lin Ming frowned. The Eternal Demon Abyss was extremely mystical. Although his strength wasn’t comparable at all to that of the weak martial artists of the lower realms, in his current state, it was hard to predict what would happen when he ventured into the Eternal Demon Abyss!

“Open it!”

Lin Ming said without hesitation. Although there was danger when the Eternal Demon Abyss erupted, there was still a slim ray of hope. But if he were to be overtaken by Tian Mingzi, that was certain death!

“Yes… yes…”

The Polaris Tower Master quickly nodded as he rushed to the Eternal Demon Abyss transmission array.

After putting blood demon crystals in the sockets, the transmission array began to start.

As the transmission array activated, a faint voice resounded near the ear of the Polaris Tower Master, “There will be a powerhouse soon catching up. If you don’t want to be caught up in the chaos and die then hurry up and leave!”

The Polaris Tower Master was stunned. A powerhouse? He didn’t know who Lin Ming was speaking of, but it was clear from his meaning that this person could easily annihilate everyone here.

Lin Ming believed that Tian Mingzi would appear directly at this transmission array. If there was no one here, then Tian Mingzi naturally wouldn’t kill everyone on the other levels of Skysplit Tower; he would be chasing Lin Ming at full speed.

The moment before Lin Ming’s figure vanished, he flicked a seal from his fingers. This seal was formed from the power of thunder and fire heavenly tribulation. After it fell onto the transmission array, it exploded upon impact, completely ruining the transmission array.

The Eternal Demon Abyss was buried deep underneath the 12 Skysplit Towers. If one didn’t use a transmission array, then although there were still ways to enter, it would be very troublesome. Lin Ming didn’t believe that destroying this transmission array would be enough to stop Tian Mingzi. Tian Mingzi was skilled in the Space Laws. Even if he had to tunnel tens of thousands of miles downwards, it would still take only a brief period of time.

Lin Ming destroying the transmission array left the Polaris Tower Master frightened. He didn’t know what was happening, but he immediately did as Lin Ming said and quickly left this level.

After half an hour passed, a black light flashed in the area where Lin Ming and the Polaris Tower Master had been standing. Space was torn apart and a black-clothed Tian Mingzi appeared.

He glanced at the destroyed transmission array, a demonic smile splitting his face.

Chapter 1363 – Eruption of the Demon Abyss

“So the secret is down here?”

After tracking the aura of the transmission array, Tian Mingzi was sure that Lin Ming had escaped deep underground.

In other words, deep beneath these blood red plains, there was a separate world with ancient ruins of the past. And, these ancient ruins clearly had some heaven-shaking secret. It was highly possible that these secrets concerned the extreme Empyrean master who had set down the enchantment around the Sky Spill Planet.

After chasing Lin Ming all the way here, Tian Mingzi had almost accurately deduced the reasoning behind the enchantment that protected the Sky Spill Planet as well as the reason for the curse left behind on the Blood Slaughter Steppes.

“Lin Ming, whether you ascend to the heavens or descend to the hells, you cannot escape me. I want to see just what secrets the Sky Spill Planet has!”

Tian Mingzi’s sword sliced through the void. Using the energy fluctuations of the transmission array as a basis, he forcefully opened a transmission array and began descending deep underground.

………..

In the vast space underground, the infernal energy was so thick that it nearly condensed into bubbles.

The entire area was pitch black, with a faint gray haze floating about. The only light came from the tiny dots of starlight in the skies, but even this light was blocked out by the fog. If a mortal were to stand here, they would simply be blind.

This was the Eternal Demon Abyss. After so many years, Lin Ming had finally returned!

The so-called Eternal Demon Abyss was originally a massive tunnel that penetrated through the entire Sky Spill Planet, ending in the Sea of Miracles on the other side. This was caused by an Empyrean level powerhouse striking right through the center of the Sky Spill Planet.

And in truth, when people referred to the Eternal Demon Abyss, they often referred to the 10,000 mile surrounding area.

This was a very dangerous area, but if one was strong enough they could come here to seek their own lucky chances before safely leaving. As for the true central Eternal Demon Abyss, even if the highest under the heavens of the Holy Demon Continent were to enter, they would not be able to return!

Lin Ming had once seen a massive shape similar to a horned black dragon God Beast in the center of the Eternal Demon Abyss. Its body was thousands of miles long and its terrifying roar had blown away all the young elites that were still several hundred miles away.

This was an existence that even a Divine Realm World King would fear!

The last time Lin Ming entered the Eternal Demon Abyss, he had stumbled into the thousand mile forbidden zone. That was the thousand mile range around the true Eternal Demon Abyss. It was known as a true life forbidden zone, a place that no one could make it out of alive.

And this time, Lin Ming had returned to the Eternal Demon Abyss to go to the center. He wanted to venture deep into it and find the most core inheritances that Empyrean Primordius had left behind!

As for what he would meet along the way, Lin Ming wasn’t sure. And as for reaching there alive, he wasn’t confident in that either.

Lin Ming stepped on the space shuttle, wanting to teleport forwards once more. But, he suddenly discovered that the energy within the Eternal Demon Abyss was extremely chaotic. If he tried to teleport here, he might stir up some terrifying space storm. With Lin Ming’s current condition, stepping into this sort of space storm would needlessly add wounds onto his already serious injuries. There would even be a chance of death.

Lin Ming remembered that the Polaris Tower Master had said that the Eternal Demon Abyss was in a state of eruption, able to erupt at any time. This meant that the Eternal Demon Abyss was several times more dangerous.

“Che!”

Lin Ming frowned. He put away the space shuttle and began flying towards the center of the Eternal Demon Abyss. At this point, there was no time to delay. His injuries were great and now that he couldn’t use the space shuttle, he would have to fly through the Eternal Demon Abyss at high speeds in its most dangerous period. This was a tremendous pressure on him!

Strong winds howled. Lin Ming’s face was pale.

To fly so crazily in the Eternal Demon Abyss was naturally extremely conspicuous.

“Roar!”

With a bass and shrill roar, seven or eight evil beings shot up from the ground, rushing towards Lin Ming!

These evil beings were formed from infernal energy. With the Eternal Demon Abyss in an erupting state, the infernal energy here was becoming increasingly thick and terrifying. This caused these evil beings to be that much stronger.

If these were ordinary times, a Life Destruction powerhouse would be more than enough to deal with these evil beings. But now, even a Divine Sea powerhouse would find it difficult.

The erupting state of the Eternal Demon Abyss made it an absolute land of death for the martial artists of the Holy Demon Continent.

The Phoenix Blood Spear swept out. These evil beings were instantly slain by Lin Ming.

Lin Ming didn’t even slow down. He turned into a beam of light, breaking into the thick fog!

In this dense fog, there were even more evil beings!

After Lin Ming hurtled into the fog, these evil beings awoke like a pack of disturbed flies. They began to rabidly plunge towards Lin Ming.

Lin Ming’s complexion was cold and callous. The Phoenix Blood Spear in his hands stabbed out again and again, and the power of thunder and fire heavenly tribulation roared outwards.

Chi chi chi!

Thunder and fire rolled up like a wave. Whether it was the power of fire or thunder, both were nemeses of evil ghosts and spirits. These evil beings were all charred to ash!

Lin Ming continued to barrel forwards, not slowing down in the least.

However, as time passed, more and more evil beings rushed at Lin Ming, forcing him to cut down more and more. Slaying 80-90 evil beings was fine, but killing 800-900 evil beings was another matter altogether. Lin Ming was rapidly consuming his energy.

If Lin Ming was in his peak state, he could restore his strength with just the Gate of Healing, the Gate of Life, and the supreme dragon bone. But now, Lin Ming’s condition was extremely poor.

Blood slowly trickled down from Lin Ming’s ears and eyes.

As Mo Eversnow saw this, she felt her heart pained with grief.

Good fortune never came in pairs and misfortune never came alone. Even though they had escaped to the Eternal Demon Abyss, they had actually run into here during the erupting state!

These evil beings were a hundred times more formidable and numerous than they ordinarily were!

Mo Eversnow quietly poured her soul force into Lin Ming’s body, helping lighten the burden on him.

However, Mo Eversnow’s soul force was only usable in limited amounts. Once she used it, she would incur damage to her divine soul. It would be hard for her to restore herself.

The more powerful someone was, the more difficult it was to restore their soul force. In the past, when Mo Eversnow had gone into a deep slumber, she had only regained consciousness after absorbing a massive amount of blood essence as well as the dragon bone marrow. From this it could be seen just how many resources were required.

“Senior-apprentice Sister, don’t!”

Lin Ming stubbornly sealed away his inner world, refusing entry to Mo Eversnow’s energies.

“Lin Ming!” Mo Eversnow cried out anxiously. Her bright eyes were wet with tears. “Do you want to die here?”

“I know what I’m doing!”

Lin Ming no longer spoke. In absolute silence, he only madly and crazily fought!

Whether it was evil beings, corpses, demonic spirits, or ghosts that appeared in front of Lin Ming, he cut down everything in his path!

He simply didn’t care about them or about himself. At this time, Lin Ming was like a demon god that had lost his mind!

1000 miles, 2000 miles, 3000 miles…

Lin Ming pierced deeper and deeper into the Eternal Demon Abyss, endlessly slaughtering. Soon, he was 9000 miles in. Once he went another 1000 miles in, that would be the true Eternal Demon Abyss.

At this distance, the fog had already dispersed. As Lin Ming looked out in the distance, he could see brilliant black flames burning in the distant horizon, connecting the heavens and the earth. In the rivers of stars above the skies, a vast amount of star light sprinkled down, connected together with that black flame as if the galaxy were falling downwards!

This was the true Eternal Demon Abyss!

And at this time, Lin Ming suddenly felt a terrifying killing intent shroud over him. Compared to before, this sense was far more intense!

He knew that Tian Mingzi would arrive soon!

After so many twists and turns, Tian Mingzi had finally entered the Eternal Demon Abyss, and now both of them were in the same space!

With Tian Mingzi’s speed, even if the power of space was in chaos and he couldn’t teleport, he was still several times faster than Lin Ming!

The 1000 miles around the Eternal Demon Abyss was known as the thousand mile forbidden zone. To Revolving Core geniuses of the Eternal Demon Abyss, as well as many High Lords and even Tower Masters, this was a land of no return. Once one entered, that meant nearly guaranteed death!

Even in the past when Lin Ming entered this place, he still had to expend a great deal of effort and take many risks before escaping with the guidance of Demonshine.

Now, the Eternal Demon Abyss was in a period of eruption and the thousand mile forbidden zone was a hundred times more dangerous than usual. Lin Ming’s wounds were extremely heavy too; this would make it far more difficult for him to push forwards.

There was a possibility that Lin Ming would be overtaken by Tian Mingzi before he was able to enter the Eternal Demon Abyss.

“Lin Ming, you’ve been overdrawing your strength this entire way, adding wounds upon your previous wounds. You have even burnt half your blood essence. If this continues then you will die…”

As Mo Eversnow looked at Lin Ming in such a state, she felt as if someone had pulled out her heart. She hated herself and her inability to help Lin Ming.

As Lin Ming felt Tian Mingzi’s killing intent rapidly approaching, he didn’t immediately rush into the thousand mile forbidden zone. Rather, he stopped where he was.

He was rapidly calculating possible routes to take.

Lin Ming’s original idea was to enter the Eternal Demon Abyss and borrow the  strange and unknown power of the Eternal Demon Abyss to protect him. If he were lucky, then there was a chance that Tian Mingzi would perish inside.

But now, he had no idea whether or not Tian Mingzi had the possibility of perishing in the Eternal Demon Abyss.

The crux was that with Lin Ming’s current condition, if he were to enter the depths of the Eternal Demon Abyss, he might be the first one to perish.

At this moment, Lin Ming could only make one desperate gamble!

He didn’t plan on going deep into the Eternal Demon Abyss, but prepared to go somewhere else first.

After he resolutely made this decision, he adjusted his direction and rapidly flew somewhere else.

“Lin Ming, where are you going?”

Mo Eversnow was stunned. Lin Ming wasn’t taking a straight line to the Eternal Demon Abyss but was curving around. This would naturally take him longer.

“To the ancient grave of the goddess!”

Lin Ming suddenly said.

Over 10 years ago, when Lin Ming had entered the thousand mile forbidden zone for the first time, because he had been attacked by several corpse devils and then chased after them, he had managed to stumble upon the ancient grave of the goddess.

The ancient grave of the goddess held four coffins, each one carved from the darkest obsidian rock.

The first three coffins had held all sorts of heavenly materials produced in the Eternal Demon Abyss. Lin Ming guessed that these heavenly materials were once collected by the corpse devils who occupied this tomb.

But in the last coffin, there was actually the corpse of the goddess.

Because the body of this goddess exuded an infinite majesty and might, the corpse devils simply weren’t able to approach her. Thus, she retained her pure and untainted form.

Even though it was a corpse, the vitality of the goddess was more vibrant than that of a living person. Her entire being emitted a bright and exuberant aura; this was the vitality of life.

Even now, Lin Ming had no idea as to what the status of this goddess was.

At this time, because it was far too difficult to enter the Eternal Demon Abyss, Lin Ming decided to change directions and go to the grave of the goddess first.

Lin Ming’s memory was extremely good. He could remember the exact position of the goddess’ grave.

In the past, because Lin Ming didn’t understand the Space Laws, he had nearly become lost in the thousand mile forbidden zone. But now, that sort of situation wouldn’t occur. As long as he remembered the position of the goddess’ ancient grave, he could arrive there directly.

“The ancient grave of the goddess, are you thinking to…”

As Mo Eversnow spoke, Lin Ming had already broken into the thousand mile forbidden zone. As soon as he entered the thousand mile forbidden zone, many evil spirits threw themselves at Lin Ming. These evil beings were far more formidable than the ones before!

Lin Ming grit his teeth, opening the Eight Inner Hidden Gates as he fought with everything he had!

Chapter 1364 – The Phantom within the Ancient Grave

From the time that Lin Ming entered the thousand mile forbidden zone until he reached the tomb of the goddess, he had killed countless evil spirits.

These evil spirits were 10 times more dense than outside the thousand mile forbidden zone and they were also far stronger.

Rumble rumble rumble!

The power of thunder and fire heavenly tribulation howled in the air. Lin Ming rushed through groups of demonic beings, dozens upon dozens of them instantly being charred to ash that was scattered in the wind.

At this time, Lin Ming’s entire body was bathed in blood and the treasure armor he wore was nearly broken to pieces. He was a flickering fading flame in the deep dark.

But at this moment, Lin Ming saw a dark gray mountain appear in front of him.

This mountain was barren and desolate, without a single blade of grass growing upon it.

Around this mountain faint fluctuations of space were exuded. This also meant that there was some hidden cave dwelling within this mountain.

“It’s here.”

Lin Ming wouldn’t remember incorrectly; this was where the tomb of the goddess was. Although this mountain like plain and non-descript, the truth was that there was already an accessible channel leading to the tomb, otherwise it would have been impossible for those corpse devils to enter this ancient grave.

Lin Ming closed his eyes, spreading his senses and soon locating the entrance.

Looking at it, it seemed like a stone wall, but Lin Ming knew that this was merely an illusion.

He pressed his hands against that stone wall and pushed through. At that time, he felt as if he had passed through some gate made of mercury, entering a distorted space barrier before everything around him began to light up.

Lin Ming had finally returned to the tomb of the ancient goddess. This dark cave was filled thick with dust. The ancient passage, the weathered stone walls, everything had the taste of endless passing years.

In the cave there were four coffins. Three of them were already open. Only the fourth coffin was sealed. This coffin emitted a vast aura, as if there were some ancient monarch buried within it.

Lin Ming slowly walked to that coffin and respectfully bowed, “Deeply sleeping senior, today this junior has fallen into dire danger, thus I apologize for offending you.”

Lin Ming quietly said before he pushed open the coffin lid.

The goddess in the coffin was still lying down as she was all those years before.

Her skin, her body, everything seemed carved from the most perfect, exquisite jade in the world, as if it were formed from the essence of the stars and moon.

Her long black hair was thick and glossy as it lay pooled within the coffin, like waves in an ocean of ink. Her face glowed with an intangible light and one could even make out the faintest traces of blood vessels beneath her skin, seeming as if blood was flowing within them.

These fluctuations of life appeared all around the goddess. If one didn’t know otherwise, they might think that this goddess had simply fallen asleep here and was ready to wake up at any moment.

This was an extraordinary woman. She was a fairy of the night, a sublime goddess formed from the splendor and glory of the universe.

“An ancient ruler!”

After seeing the goddess once more, Lin Ming’s experience far surpassed what it was in the past. He could increasingly feel just how powerful the goddess was.

Lin Ming originally thought that the goddess was someone important to Empyrean Primordius but her strength was lacking, and that she had been relying on the protections of Empyrean Primordius to lay here filled with life vitality 100,000 years after her death.

But now, Lin Ming had completely changed his thoughts.

This goddess was likely amazingly powerful. Flowing all around her were the light fluctuations of the Life Laws. As heaven and earth origin energy gathered about her, it turned into spiritual beings that floated all around.

To die and still have Law fluctuations around them 100,000 years later, it was clear that this woman’s understandings into the Laws had reached a breathtaking degree.

“Miss Mo, do you think there is a chance you can possess her body?”

Lin Ming slowly said as he looked at the goddess in the coffin.

To have Mo Eversnow possess the mortal body of the goddess was one of Lin Ming’s ideas before he had entered the Eternal Demon Abyss. But, he also knew that wanting to do this was an enormous risk!

This was because the mortal body of the goddess was supported with the will of Empyrean Primordius. Empyrean Primordius might not be willing to see the goddess’ body taken possession of by Mo Eversnow, turning into someone else’s.

Mo Eversnow’s eyebrows jumped up. Take possession of the goddess’ body?

Mo Eversnow had once had this idea before, but she knew this goddess was no ordinary figure. Her power far surpassed Mo Eversnow even during her peak.

As for she herself, all she had left was her weakened soul. If she tried to possess this woman’s body, it was hard to imagine what would happen.

But now, with Tian Mingzi rapidly approaching, Mo Eversnow had no choice. She could only take this gamble!

Without a word, her soul flew out from the Magic Cube, turning into a soul form in the air. Mo Eversnow’s soul form wore a long blue dress, her body exuding a crystalline light, as if she were made from countless shattered crystals. It was an enchanting and dreamy sight, like a dream that was soon to fade.

Mo Eversnow clenched her teeth, wanting to rush into the coffin. But at this time, Lin Ming stepped in front of Mo Eversnow, blocking her way, “I’ll go first!”

With this, Lin Ming revolved the Divine Dream Law to the limit. His complete sense, his will, his divine soul, he focused everything on the coffin, taking the first step to submerge his consciousness into the goddess’ body before Mo Eversnow.

The area Lin Ming chose to enter was the chest of the goddess.

As soon as he entered, Lin Ming felt his mind tremble. Immediately, his soul and will arrived in a completely separate space.

This was a vast and starry world, as if it were the infinite universe itself.

Lin Ming took a deep breath. He wasn’t a stranger to this starry world. Many years ago when he was still at the Revolving Core, he had stumbled upon the tomb of the goddess and had also come to this starry world that was formed from a world of will.

Within these starry skies was a terrifying existence.

As this thought passed through Lin Ming’s mind, a massive amount of life origin energy gushed towards him like an endless tide.

This energy was pure and vibrant. It smashed into Lin Ming’s body like a tide against the shore.

Luckily, Lin Ming was already prepared. As his body was pushed back by this energy, he steadily fell in the void before coming to a stop high in the skies.

He looked up. In front of him, in the void, in the horizon, as if it were close at hand and also immeasurably far, was a powerfully beating blood red heart.

Boom! Boom! Boom!

This was a horrifying sound. Every beat seemed to strike upon Lin Ming’s fires of life, causing all of the blood vitality within his body to resonate and want to come gushing out.

This was the heart of a Great Emperor. This was the heart that Empyrean Primordius had left behind!

This heart had already been beating for 100,000 years, but its blood vitality was still as potent and boundless, and its life force remained like an endless ocean, unending. Every beat of this great heart caused the void to shake.

Even after leaving its body for 100,000 years, this heart continued to beat onwards. Moreover, it contained a terrifying vitality, as if it were destined to beat until the oceans dried and the world cracked, beating on until the end of all times.

This aura, as if all existence were beneath it, as if it alone ruled the vast cosmos, caused Lin Ming to recall Empyrean Primordius’ words that he had once left behind in the Road of Emperor – “The masterless river of stars in the endless cosmos, I shall rewrite the infinite history!”

“Senior Primordius!”

Lin Ming shouted out as loudly as he could, not caring whether or not Empyrean Primordius could hear him.

In those vast starry skies, Lin Ming’s voice seemed especially lonely. There was no response.

At this time, Lin Ming didn’t have any time to delay further. He grit his teeth and flew towards that Great Emperor’s heart!

In what seemed like an incomparably long time but also a mere instant, Lin Ming arrived in front of that great beating heart. In that moment, a wild and brutal wave of blood vitality swept up around Lin Ming, turning the entire starry world into a blur.

When Lin Ming saw his surroundings become clear once more, he saw that in the void, there was a massive planet in front of him. This planet was covered in dark and gloomy clouds. The land was endless and a great aura exuded from this planet; it was faintly familiar to Lin Ming.

This was… the Sky Spill Planet?

Lin Ming was startled as he thought this. This should be the Sky Spill Planet, but it was also different from the Sky Spill Planet in his memories.

At this time, the starry skies were ripped open and a giant portal appeared in the air. Countless powerhouses began emerging from this portal. These powerhouses each had a vague appearance and the ones in the lead all emitted a strange aura. This aura was similar to that of the mysterious black-robed person that Lin Ming had killed at the Demondawn Great World. In other words, there was a possibility these people were all from the saint race.

After these people appeared, they moved towards the Sky Spill Planet and immediately launched their attacks!

For a time, the void was shattered as terrifying fluctuations of energy wantonly bombarded the Sky Spill Planet. Lin Ming thought that the Sky Spill Planet would be destroyed, and every single life living on the planet would also perish in a miserable death.

But at this time, an energy barrier appeared around the skies of the Sky Spill Planet, blocking all the attacks.

Energy erupted in turbulent blasts and the energy barrier shook, but, it never broke.

Lin Ming’s eyes widened. He recognized that this barrier was the barrier that currently protected the Sky Spill Planet. It was the protection that Empyrean Primordius had laid down so long ago.

Empyrean Primordius had used the Sky Spill Planet as the foundation, and after many years of work, the protective array formation he laid down was incredibly firm. It was even able to resist the joint attacks of so many powerhouses without being destroyed.

And at this time, in the dark skies of the Sky Spill Planet, the thick clouds were torn apart and a Black Dragon thousands of miles long roared its way outwards.

This Black Dragon emitted a terrifying pressure as if it were a celestial body itself. On the back of this Black Dragon was a black-clothed man. He was tall and strong and he held a 10 foot long halberd in his hands. It was impossible to make out his face.

As Lin Ming saw this black-clothed man, his mind shook. This man was Empyrean Primordius!

He had the atmosphere of a Great Emperor, and that Black Dragon he was riding on was that horned black dragon that Lin Ming had seen in the Eternal Demon Abyss.

Without a doubt, the scene replaying in front of him was the great war from 100,000 years ago that played out on the Sky Spill Planet!

And among Empyrean Primordius’ opponents, there were powerhouses from the saint race!

100,000 years ago, besides Empyrean Thunder Punishment, there were also many saints that were involved in that tragedy. At that time, Empyrean Primordius had already been one of the few characters that stood upon the very peak of the Divine Realm. The reason that he had suffered severe wounds during this war and possibly even perished afterwards was all because of the saint race.

Chapter 1365 – Blood Vitality Entering the Body

The war was staged in the endless starry skies. Both sides had countless masters. Lin Ming saw a man holding a blue scepter that controlled lightning. During this battle, he was like the incarnation of the Heavenly Dao, wielding the power of thunder tribulation.

This person was Empyrean Thunder Punishment.

Besides Empyrean Thunder Punishment, Empyrean Primordius had to face two peak masters of the saint race!

By himself, Empyrean Primordius faced off against three dire enemies!

Even so, he didn’t seem as if he could be defeated.

“How could supreme masters of the saint race enter the Divine Realm?”

Lin Ming couldn’t understand this. According to Empyrean Divine Dream, the Divine Realm was only one of the 33 Layered Heavens, and there were massive barriers that separated these ‘heavens’. Because of this, the more powerful someone was, the more difficult it was for them to break through and enter.

So how could these saint race masters have come to the Sky Spill Planet?

As Lin Ming was thinking this, the great war vanished, leaving nothing but that blood red beating heart in the skies.

Boom! Boom! Boom!

That powerful sound was like the deafening beat of a divine drum!

Lin Ming knew that what he saw just now was only incomplete images preserved in the memories of that heart.

A heart was only a part of the physical body, thus it shouldn’t have any memories. Then, logically speaking, this heart should contain a wisp of a remnant soul!

This idea immediately cut through Lin Ming’s mind, “Senior Primordius!”

A loud voice echoed through the world. Lin Ming was extremely hurried. Tian Mingzi was quickly catching up to them. He couldn’t rely on the eruption of the Eternal Demon Abyss to delay Tian Mingzi for much longer.

“Senior Primordius!”

Lin Ming shouted out once more. However, he still received no reply.

“Was my guess wrong? Is there really no remnant soul here?”

Lin Ming’s mind raced. The wisp of Empyrean Primordius’ remnant soul might be very weak to begin with, and then it had also been sleeping here for 100,000 years. If he really wanted to awaken it, wasn’t that something easier said than done?

As Lin Ming was thinking this, his power suddenly concentrated in his inner world. A blood red lotus flower began to slowly bloom behind him.

This was the Prime Emperor Lotus Flower.

A vast and boundless aura began to emit from Lin Ming’s body. He had opened the grandmist space!

The grandmist space covered that great heart. The elementary grandmist energy constantly struck against that beating heart like a surging tide.

“Senior Primordius!”

Lin Ming exhausted all of his strength as he roared out. His voice echoed like roiling thunder, shaking the void for thousands of miles around!

At this time, the beating heart suddenly shook. Its beating frequency slowed down as an invisible energy covered Lin Ming and began to absorb the divine dream energy within him.

Lin Ming was shocked but he didn’t prevent this, instead letting this force absorb as it wished. For Lin Ming to do this in his current state wasn’t easy on him at all.

A moment later, Lin Ming’s complexion turned much paler and there was even a trace of fading ash in his complexion. Then, a gray shadow poured out from the heart, finally transforming into a black-robed man.

This man’s figure was extremely vague, constantly trembling in the currents of heaven and earth origin energy as if he could disappear at any moment.

The phantom opened his eyes with great difficulty, staring at Lin Ming with confusion.

Lin Ming also looked at this black-clothed man in front of him.

Was this the remnant soul that had been attached to Empyrean Primordius’ heart?

This wisp of remnant soul didn’t have the great strength Lin Ming had imagined; it could even be called abnormally weak.

Presumably, in the past, Empyrean Primordius’ wounds had been extremely heavy or perhaps he had even perished, and the remnant soul he left behind was the tiniest fraction possible. After it slept so deeply for all this time, it even needed to draw support from Lin Ming’s divine dream energy to regain consciousness.

“Senior is Empyrean Primordius?”

Lin Ming asked.

“Who are you, that you can use the grandmist space?”

The black-robed man’s voice was ephemeral, weak and fading.

“This junior’s name is Lin Ming. In the Road of Emperor, I once obtained Senior’s blessing and was able to obtain a third of the Primordius martial intent inheritance, thus I am able to use the grandmist space.”

“I see, so that’s how it is. What you must be speaking of is the Samsara Road. Honorable Master indeed once left behind a part of his inheritance within the Samsara Road.”

The black-robed man’s words indicated his status. He wasn’t Empyrean Primordius but Empyrean Primordius’ disciple.

So this was what happened. Lin Ming suddenly became aware. It was said that Empyrean Primordius was a dual body and energy cultivator, and even though he focused on body and energy, leaving his soul a little weaker, a wisp of remnant soul that he left behind should still contain a tremendous pressure. It was something far from what this phantom in front of him could ever do.

And this remnant soul was the disciple of Empyrean Primordius. Did Empyrean Primordius have his own disciple leave his remnant soul to deeply slumber here, in order to protect his heart and also guard the body of the goddess?

“Senior, this junior is being chased down and hunted. I wish for my companion to borrow the body of the goddess to resurrect herself and fight against this person!”

In the past, Mo Eversnow had been a half-step World King master. Whether it was attainments in Laws or cultivation methods, she had reached an extremely high boundary. But unfortunately, she had lost her body and was unable to move true essence at all. This was especially detrimental for someone like her who had also dual cultivated body and energy.

If she could fuse together with the body of the goddess, then Mo Eversnow’s strength would rise to astronomical degrees.

“Borrow the body of the goddess? You are speaking of… Heavenly Empress Xuanqing?”

Heavenly Empress Xuanqing?

Lin Ming was stunned. He never imagined that a young woman who looked around 17-18 years old would possess such a title.

If she could be referred to as a Heavenly Empress, then she wasn’t a young elite at all. Rather, she was someone who had long come to fame, someone whose strength had already reached incomparably terrifying levels.

“Heavenly Empress Xuanqing is a monarch of the primal god race. Even if her divine soul is no longer here, wanting to possess her mortal body is not easy at all. If you cannot withstand the power of her mortal body then your divine soul will collapse and disintegrate. Do you know this?”

As the wisp of remnant soul spoke, Lin Ming was left dumbfounded. Primal god race?

This was another new race that Lin Ming had never heard of before. He had heard about the saints, the spiritas, and humanity; these were the three main races of the 33 Layered Heavens. Each race was separately skilled in body transformation, soul forging, and essence gathering, the three main cultivation systems. Lin Ming never knew that there was also a primal god race.

“Senior is… speaking about the primal god race?”

“Yes, the primal god race. The primal god race is the most perfect race to ever be formed by the heavens. They are powerful in the aspect of soul, body, and inner world, and are also able to triple cultivate in essence, energy, and divine. Their strength is great at birth and their talent defies the will of the heavens. Even their lifespans are 10 times longer than those of humans.

As the remnant soul slowly spoke, Lin Ming felt a chill crawl down his soul. Triple cultivators of essence, energy, and divine, talents that defied the heavens’ will, lifespans 10 times longer than those of humans… this was simply too incredible.

“There is such a race in this world that completely surpasses the three main races?”

As Lin Ming spoke, a trace of surprise appeared on the face of that remnant soul. “I never imagined that you would also know of the three races. Yes, the primal god race truly possesses all advantages of the three main races, but, perhaps because they are existences that defy the heavens too much, the Heavenly Dao does not abide by their existence. Thus, even though they once prospered in the most ancient of times, they began to slowly decline afterwards. The number of their people became extremely low, finally nearing the point of extinction.

“Then Heavenly Empress Xuanqing is…” Lin Ming was puzzled. He simply didn’t know how Empyrean Primordius had gotten mixed together with the primal god race.

“You do not need to know this. These are matters that involve the secrets of this universe. There is no significance in you knowing, and you possessing this knowledge would only draw disaster upon yourself.”

As the remnant soul spoke, he had subconsciously assumed that Lin Ming was a local martial artist of the Sky Spill Planet. When this was added to Lin Ming’s weak blood vitality and fading strength, it was impossible to connect him to being the number one genius of the Divine Realm.

However, as the remnant soul finished speaking, he paused, “Eh… you seemed to have burnt most of your blood essence?”

This remnant soul was a disciple of Empyrean Primordius, thus before his death he was likely at least a Great World King level character. Moreover, he too cultivated dual body and energy, and was highly sensitive to the power of blood vitality. As he probed Lin Ming’s body, he discovered to his astonishment that Lin Ming had burnt over half his blood essence. Even so, he was still able to stand here.

If an ordinary person were to do this, their life would be feeble and fading and they would find it difficult to continue supporting themselves.

“30 some year skeletal age, dual body and energy cultivation, and you even opened the complete Eight Inner Hidden Gates?”

The remnant soul was shocked. This was no minor matter. In this universe, the body transformation technique was no longer compatible with the rules of the Heavenly Dao. Even his honorable master, Empyrean Primordius, hadn’t been able to open the complete Eight Inner Hidden Gates in his thirties.

“You… have had such a fortuitous encounter?”

The remnant soul could clearly feel that Lin Ming was a martial artist native to the Sky Spill Planet. For a native martial artist to grow to such a degree, they must have had countless lucky chances paving their road. This was simply inconceivable.

“Who is hunting you?” The remnant soul immediately asked. Perhaps the reason Lin Ming had burnt half his blood essence was that he was being chased down by this person.

“Tian Mingzi, he is a Great World King from the Divine Realm. He severed his hand, turning it into an avatar to enter the Sky Spill Planet in order to hunt down this junior. Now, he will likely arrive here in another quarter hour.”

Lin Ming said. Although he was anxious as he spoke, he was still able to maintain his calm.

“A Great World King severed his hand to hunt you down?” The remnant soul looked at Lin Ming with incredulity etched on his face. He could faintly feel that Lin Ming’s strength was far greater than what he had imagined. Such a character was in no way a tiny fish in a pool.

“If you were able to learn the grandmist space, it could be said that you have a certain fate with my honorable master. Moreover, at such a young age you also opened the complete Eight Inner Hidden Gates. You even chose to dual cultivate body and energy, the same path that my honorable master took. Perhaps this is the karma of the world… perhaps you are the person that my honorable master has been waiting for all this time…”

The remnant soul quietly said. At the precipice of death, Empyrean Primordius had left behind his own inheritances so that in the future, those fated juniors could enter and inherit his legacy.

Now, no matter how one looked at it, Lin Ming was the most suitable candidate.

If this remnant soul could see Empyrean Primordius’ last wishes being inherited by the next generation, he could finally die in peace.

“You are so young and yet have such talent; you must be truly incredible. Unfortunately, even though you are being chased down by others, I cannot help you. All that remains of me is a wisp of a remnant soul; I have almost no strength remaining. There is a choice, but the decision must be made by you. If you have the confidence then your companion can take possession of Heavenly Empress Xuanqing’s mortal body. As for you, if you are able to withstand the baptism of my honorable master’s blood vitality, then you may attempt to direct the power of blood vitality within his heart into your own to temper yourself.”

“Direct the power of blood vitality into my heart and temper myself?”

Lin Ming was bewildered. He looked once more at the beating heart in the endless starry skies. The power of blood vitality contained within it was as vast and deep as the fathomless oceans. This was the power of blood vitality that only an Empyrean could possess. Moreover, Empyrean Primordius likely had the Demon Bead at some point, which was what allowed his body transformation technique to reach such an inconceivable boundary. If he were to direct the power of blood vitality within Empyrean Primordius’ heart into his own, just what sort of scene would that be?

Chapter 1368 – Tian Mingzi Arrives

After possessing Heavenly Empress Xuanqing’s body, it could be said that Mo Eversnow had been fully transformed, gaining a new life.

To be able to communicate with the Primal God Realm, to be able to simultaneously cultivate the body transformation system, essence gathering system, and soul forging system without any restraints, the primal god race were truly the favored children of the heavens. Whether it was in cultivation speed, awareness of the Laws, or true combat strength, those of the primal god race far surpassed all martial artists of the same level.

Currently, Lin Ming had absorbed the power of blood vitality from Empyrean Primordius’ heart, and his strength had been restored to its peak condition. Even so, when he faced Mo Eversnow, even though her figure and appearance were delicate and soft, he could sense that she contained a fathomless strength, as vast as the stars in the sky.

If Lin Ming were to fight Mo Eversnow now, he had to admit that he would lose without a doubt.

Not just that, but Mo Eversnow was still in the melding phase of her soul and new body; it was impossible for her to display her true strength and cultivation. Once this melding phase was over, Mo Eversnow’s strength would rise by leaps and bounds, and her cultivation would fly past anything she had ever reached. Mo Eversnow had an extremely high fusion compatibility with this new mortal body; there would be no hindrances in her future cultivation.

Mo Eversnow originally had an extremely rare heaven-gifted talent. Now that she had obtained the body of an extreme talent from the primal god race, as she cultivated in the future, the great road before her would be flat and limitless, with no obstacles! At that time, underneath the 33 Layered Heavens, in the myriad worlds, Mo Eversnow would become a supreme elder of her own domain, living for a hundred million years!

After listening to Lin Ming’s words, Mo Eversnow unconsciously turned to the distance, her eyes becoming deep and profound. “If I can step onto the peak of martial arts one day, I will reform my own mortal body, as well as revive Senior Heavenly Empress Xuanqing to thank her for this kindness…”

Heavenly Empress Xuanqing was a senior supreme elder and Mo Eversnow was simply a tiny junior. Heavenly Empress Xuanqing had been countless times stronger than Mo Eversnow, even when Mo Eversnow was at her peak. Mo Eversnow had been able to possess Heavenly Empress Xuanqing’s body because she had allowed it, otherwise Mo Eversnow’s soul would have long been turned to ash.

In her life, Mo Eversnow would never forget such a graciousness.

“Of course. At that time, Senior-apprentice Sister will surely have the ability to reshape your mortal body. Moreover, I should also have reached an extremely high boundary in the body transformation technique and my understanding of the Life Laws should have gone even further. I will definitely be able to lend Senior-apprentice Sister a helping hand.” As Lin Ming spoke, his heart stirred. He turned and looked towards the exit of the tomb, his eyes flashing with a cold brilliance.

“Our friend has finally caught up. He’ll arrive in another quarter at most. To rush all the way from the Divine Realm to the Sky Spill Planet, and even chase us down to the Eternal Demon Abyss only for us to bid our farewells here, it must be hard for him.”

As Lin Ming spoke, he sneered in a mocking smile. When he said quarter hour, he was referring to time within the enchantment. If he were to remove the enchantment, Tian Mingzi would catch up in 10 breaths of time.

As Tian Mingzi’s name was mentioned, Mo Eversnow didn’t bother to hide the unfiltered killing intent in her eyes. Towards Tian Mingzi, she felt nothing but a searing hatred that extended down to her very marrow!

“This time, it is only his hand and a wisp of his soul. Killing him will only ruin a bit of Tian Mingzi’s cultivation. But next time, I will take his life. I will suck out his soul and refine it, torturing it until he dies from suffering. I will use his sacrifice to console the countless lives of the Verdant Feather Holy Lands that are in the heavens!”

Mo Eversnow was not some overly empathetic or tender-hearted woman. As the Saintess of a World King Holy Land, she was decisive and ruthless in her actions, remembering favors and avenging grudges. Although sucking out someone’s soul and refining it was a method of the demonic path, Mo Eversnow would still do it without any scruples.

Lin Ming raised his hand and lifted the time enchantment. As the time enchantment was lifted, he could feel an extremely powerful aura approaching at incredible speed, overflowing with killing intent. This was Tian Mingzi.

“Hehe, I’ve found you!”

As Tian Mingzi saw the black mountain that held the tomb of the goddess, he fiendishly grinned.

“You entered this mountain peak? Do you think you can bury your head in the ground like an ostrich? Did you finally realize that you cannot escape me, thus you ran into this mountain to draw support from something like an array formation inside? Is this your final stand?”

Tian Mingzi’s senses swept over the black mountain peak but he didn’t discover any traps at all. Although there were many evil spirits in the thousand mile forbidden zone, these evil spirits were only a minor inconvenience to Tian Mingzi. He simply didn’t fear them at all.

However, it was always better to be safe than sorry. Tian Mingzi had no intention of entering this mountain peak; he was prepared to launch an assault from outside.

“I will destroy this mountain first!”

Tian Mingzi extracted an eight foot long sword, and just as he was about to slash out, a cliff of the mountain distorted and Lin Ming came walking out from the goddess’ tomb with the Phoenix Blood Spear in hand.

As Tian Mingzi saw Lin Ming, he sneered. “To think that you came out on your own. Lin Ming, you truly are a heaven-gifted eternally rare genius. Your future prospects were originally without limit, but what a pity that you have become my enemy. You truly have no idea of death or danger. Today, you are doomed to die beneath my blade!”

“Oh? Is that so…” Lin Ming grasped the Phoenix Blood Spear, pointing it straight at Tian Mingzi. At this moment, as Tian Mingzi looked at Lin Ming, he was suddenly shocked.

He could clearly feel that Lin Ming’s missing blood vitality was already restored!

No, he hadn’t just restored it. To be more accurate, the power of Lin Ming’s blood vitality was almost double what it used to be. The strength of his body was as deep as the sea, surging forwards. His cultivation had nearly broken through to the late Divine Sea realm!

Lin Ming was indeed ready to break into the late Divine Sea realm any time now. Originally, when he fought with Tian Mingzi, because Mo Eversnow was beginning to burn her divine soul, his potential had erupted from within him, nearly allowing him to break into the late Divine Sea realm. That final strike of his had not just been because he burnt half his blood essence but also because his cultivation had increased by a tremendous amount.

“How could this be possible… once your blood essence is lost, it is extremely difficult to make up for it, especially for an extreme talent like you with such a powerful blood vitality…” Tian Mingzi looked at Lin Ming with disbelief, then glanced at the tomb of the goddess behind him. “It really is this mountain, there must be some treasure here!”

Tian Mingzi was overjoyed. If an extreme genius like Lin Ming was able to rapidly restore his potent blood vitality, and even double it, that must mean that there were some peak treasures in this black mountain. It absolutely had to be a transcendent divine miracle medicine!

“Lin Ming, you truly have a great destiny upon your body. But, just because your blood vitality is powerful, do you really think you can defeat me with just that? Once I kill you, all the secrets you possess will be mine. All your lucky chances, everything you have will be taken by me! Hahaha!”

Tian Mingzi wildly cackled. At this time, his smiling face suddenly stiffened. He discovered that behind Lin Ming, another person had emerged from the black mountain.

This was a true peerless woman. Her slender waist, her tall and steady stature, her ephemeral appearance, everything about her had reached the pinnacle of perfection. It was like she wasn’t a woman from this world at all, but an immortal goddess exiled from the highest heavens.

But this time, Tian Mingzi was of no mind at all to appreciate this woman’s beauty. He could only feel a cold and dense air covering him… this woman was terrifying!

Moreover, before now, this woman had been nearby and yet he hadn’t sensed her at all. This left a feeling of dread in Tian Mingzi’s heart.

“Who are you? Have we met before?”

Tian Mingzi’s eyes shined brightly as he stared at Mo Eversnow. Because Mo Eversnow had taken on the appearance of Heavenly Empress Xuanqing, he wasn’t able to recognize her at all. He could only faintly feel that she was somewhat familiar.

“We have indeed met before… and our origins are extremely deep…” As Mo Eversnow spoke, there was no expression on her face. But, her killing intent had already locked onto Tian Mingzi, sending cold chills down his spine.

He took a step back. “Origin? I do not remember having any grudge with you.”

Tian Mingzi was secretly frightened; he couldn’t imagine just where he had seen this woman before. At this time, if he were to somehow provoke someone who held such deep-seated hatred against him, his fate could be imagined.

“You will remember!” Mo Eversnow sneered. As she spoke, she suddenly stepped forwards, her speed reaching incredible degrees. In just a flash she had arrived in front of Tian Mingzi, her palm slashing down at him!

Mo Eversnow had just taken possession of Heavenly Empress Xuanqing’s body and didn’t have a weapon. But, she didn’t need a weapon for her attacks to be brutal and swift. The primal god race could cultivate all Laws and were born to triple cultivate in essence, energy, and divine. Heavenly Empress Xuanqing’s mortal body had long been tempered to a terrifying degree, high enough that she could even slice apart a high-grade spirit artifact with her bare hands.

As her palm came slashing down, a massive chunk of space collapsed. A storm of time and space began to billow behind her palm, sweeping towards Tian Mingzi!

Tian Mingzi was shocked. He didn’t dare to be incautious. He rapidly drew backwards and cut out with his sword, the black sword light meeting Mo Eversnow’s palm wind.

Kacha!

The sword light exploded. Mo Eversnow’s body moved like ghosts and gods, immediately stepping in front of Tian Mingzi once more. With her cold eyes and her long hair dancing about in the wind, she was like a death reaper that had come at night.

Peng!

With a thunderous crack, Tian Mingzi was sent flying backwards. He barely managed to block Mo Eversnow’s second palm strike and the attack left all his blood vitality tumbling within his body, leaving him breathless. Just who was this woman? Did she come from the Divine Realm or the lower realms, and how could she just emerge out of nowhere?

Chapter 1373 – Crystal Bones

These blazing black flames combusted over the 10,000 mile diameter of the Eternal Demon Abyss.

These were not true flames, but virtual flames produced by energy.

A terrifying energy followed these flames, swirling from the Eternal Demon Abyss, ascending into the skies. In such an aura, Lin Ming felt himself constantly baptized in a massive storm of power, making him feel a deep sense of awe.

In the past, Empyrean Primordius had descended down to his home planet from the Divine Realm and established his own Samsara Heavenly Dao. His supernatural powers had been nearly unparalleled; it was impossible to imagine just how magnificent that time was.

But what a pity, such an extreme character couldn’t avoid the inevitable fate of extermination. Even if he didn’t perish halfway on his road of martial arts, he still wouldn’t have been able to withstand the erosion of the passing years.

Lin Ming stood on the edge of the Eternal Demon Abyss, looking into it. He could see at most several dozen miles into the deep darkness.

Downwards, more and more endless flames of ash and gloom blocked his sight. He couldn’t imagine just what sort of horrifying and wondrous world lay beneath him.

The diameter of the Eternal Demon Abyss was 10,000 miles wide and over 100 million miles long. To put it more simply, if one considered the size of mortal nations, hundreds upon hundreds of them could exist within that 10,000 mile diameter.

Even if one rode a horse all day for an entire month, they still wouldn’t be able to complete a lap around the giant circle of the Eternal Demon Abyss.

At the edge of the Eternal Demon Abyss, just ten miles away from Lin Ming, he could make out a giant iron chain. This chain was pierced into the walls of the Eternal Demon Abyss, extending downwards endlessly until it slowly vanished into the infinite ashy flames.

This iron chain was thicker than the phantom of the Heretical God Tree when Lin Ming used Heavenly Dao Judgment!

This iron chain was simple and plain, filled with a heavy sense of texture. It was unknown just what sort of material this chain was made from, but all sorts of runes were engraved on it. These runes faintly shimmered, melting into the surrounding heaven and earth origin energy.

For 100,000 years, for countless days and countless nights, this iron chain had been continuously tempered by heaven and earth origin energy, swallowing the essence of the sun and moon. This chain absorbed endless surges of power every second of the day; it was impossible to imagine just how firm it was.

Lin Ming suspected that there was more than one of these iron chains. Rather, they were spread all over the periphery of the Eternal Demon Abyss. It was just that his vision was limited so he could only see one.

“I should follow this iron chain downwards.”

Lin Ming bowed towards the Eternal Demon Abyss, then walked towards the wall area where the iron chain was located and jumped down.

In the incomparably massive Eternal Demon Abyss, Lin Ming’s figure was like a tiny speck of dust, simply insignificant.

To be safe, Lin Ming chose not to fly. Climbing down this iron chain was slower than flying, but it also wouldn’t arouse the attention of some unknown existences.

This thick iron chain was cold to the touch and it also contained a potent power. As Lin Ming climbed down it, he looked like an ant climbing down a tree.

As he continually went deeper and deeper into the Eternal Demon Abyss, he felt that he was trudging through the mountains and rivers of time, finally arriving at a different, ancient time-space.

The Eternal Demon Abyss was simply far too deep. Lin Ming’s speed wasn’t too fast either. After climbing down for three days and three nights, he estimated he had gone a thousand miles down the Eternal Demon Abyss. However, compared to the 100 million mile depth of the Eternal Demon Abyss, this distance was nothing at all.

During these three days, Lin Ming didn’t encounter any danger at all. Within the Eternal Demon Abyss, there existed nothing but a deathly stillness as well as the beating ash flames and the swirling heaven and earth origin energy. Besides that, Lin Ming couldn’t make out any strange energy fluctuations.

Time slowly passed, a day at a time.

Lin Ming had already climbed down this iron chain for an entire ten days, nearly reached 10,000 miles deep into the Eternal Demon Abyss.

As he looked up, he could see the rough dark red stone walls extending upwards without end.

At 10,000 miles deep, all of his surroundings had turned pitch black. Outside of the Eternal Demon Abyss, there was the faint starlight that illuminated the ground, but this weak starlight simply couldn’t penetrate through the endless fog. It came down just a tiny distance before completely disappearing.

Lin Ming took a step at a time, steadily climbing downwards. With such slow progress, it was unknown just how long he would have to climb for. But, he wasn’t worried at all. To him, withstanding the baptism of the world essence energy within the Eternal Demon Abyss was also a kind of training.

Lin Ming restrained his aura, moving with utter caution. However, danger finally arrived.

Just as Lin Ming penetrated 15,000 miles deep into the Eternal Demon Abyss, there was a common-looking rock. As Lin Ming approached it, it suddenly burst into action. It was like a big lizard, suddenly stretching out its claws as it grasped at Lin Ming.

Lin Ming’s vision condensed and he reflexively counterattacked with his spear. The colored lights of thunder and fire wove together, and with a faint crackling sound, the body of this big lizard was pierced through by the spear light.

“It’s dead?”

Lin Ming was startled. This beast was that easy to kill?

“Lin Ming, be careful!”

Mo Eversnow’s voice resounded in Lin Ming’s mind. At that moment, he felt his spiritual sea suddenly shake as a demonic will formed a sharp cone that thrust towards Lin Ming’s soul!

“It really wasn’t that easy to kill!” Lin Ming hadn’t lowered his guard at all. Even if Mo Eversnow didn’t remind him, he could still respond in time.

Divine dream energy flooded into his spiritual sea without hesitation. From between Lin Ming’s eyebrows, a brilliant divine light began to shine. A fierce killing intent poured into his grandmist spirit, forming a sword that slashed outwards.

With a tearing sound, this evil will was chopped into several pieces by Lin Ming’s grandmist battle spirit.

These several evil spirits seemed to have a life of their own. They wildly struggled, wanting to fuse back together.

“How tenacious!”

Lin Ming swept out his spear. The power of thunder and fire heavenly tribulation descended. Underneath the baptism of heavenly tribulation, this evil spirit simply wasn’t able to withstand it. It melted into ash and faded away.

This strike thoroughly killed this evil spirit. This evil spirit was extremely cunning; even after its body was ruined it could still use a spiritual attack. In truth, it was nothing but a mass of demonic will and a wisp of energy, intangible and invisible. If it weren’t for Lin Ming’s dual thunder and fire heavenly tribulation being the ultimate restraint on evil spirits, it would have taken him some time to kill it.

“This is an evil spirit formed from infernal energy.”

Mo Eversnow informed. She was sure this was not an ancient life form from 100,000 years ago, otherwise it wouldn’t be so weak.

The entrance of the Eternal Demon Abyss was surrounded by the aura left behind by Empyrean Primordius, thus evil spirits didn’t dare to approach. But in this 100 million mile deep abyss, not every section contained the aura of Empyrean Primordius, thus there were many evil spirits born here.

“Mm? It seems that the gravity is changing here…?”

After killing these evil spirit, Lin Ming discovered that there was some strange change in the gravity of the Eternal Demon Abyss.

Gravity pulled downwards originally, but the further down Lin Ming went, the more gravity angled at an incline, as if there was some strange attractive force in the walls of the Eternal Demon Abyss.

After Lin Ming climbed down a little more, he let go and directly fell onto the walls of the Eternal Demon Abyss, standing at a steady 90 degree angle.

This feeling was the exact same as being on flat land.

After taking several more steps, Lin Ming discovered more evil spirits similar to the one he killed before. These evil spirits were very good at hiding and staying dormant. To be more exact, if no one came, they were no different from stones on the ground without any life fluctuations at all. But, once a stranger approached, they would be like sharks that smelled blood, suddenly striking out to swallow the flesh and blood essence energy of their prey.

These evil spirits were not Lin Ming’s match. He poured the power of thunder into the Phoenix Blood Spear. Purple arcs of electricity crazily danced on the spear shaft. These evil spirits were rapidly annihilated by Lin Ming, and their final spiritual attacks were all easily resolved with Lin Ming’s grandmist battle spirit.

In terms of soul force and will, how could these evil spirits possibly be Lin Ming’s opponent?

As these evil spirits died, they turned into a rich yin energy, causing the surrounding infernal energy to be increasingly strong. An ice-piercing cold thrust into the bones, making one feel as if they were a corpse in a grave.

“Lin Ming, this sort of evil spirit is formed from corpse energy. With so many evil spirits around, a reason they would often appear is that many powerhouses were once buried in an ancient battlefield or perhaps this might have been a mass grave for prisoners. This land beneath our feet was likely such an ancient battlefield.”

As Mo Eversnow spoke, Lin Ming suddenly felt something crack beneath his feet as if he had broken something.

He looked down and saw that he had stepped on a skeleton.

Because it was too far in the distant past, these skeletons were already as frail as rotten wood, breaking with just a single step.

To find bones here wasn’t surprising at all.

As he walked further, more and more bones appeared.

These skeletons were at two extremes. Some were decayed and shattered, and others glowed and glittered like carved crystals.

After an essence gathering system martial artist died, their energy would slowly dissipate. Without their mortal body being vitalized by their energy, they would quickly erode.

As for those that had died 100,000 years ago and yet their bones remained as bright as crystals, they had either tempered their own bodies using arcane techniques or they were body transformation martial artists.

“These crystal bones, are they corpses of saints?”

Lin Ming’s mind stirred, inevitably thinking this. The saint race focused on the body transformation cultivation system. After dying, it was reasonable for them to leave behind such a skeleton.

However, Mo Eversnow shook her head.

“These are not saints!”

“Oh?”

Lin Ming was puzzled. At this time, Mo Eversnow flew out from the Magic Cube space and floated high in the air.

She stood in front of all these crystal skeletons for some time. Then, she said in a soft voice, “Lin Ming, as I look at these crystal skeletons, I feel a faint resonating pain in my heart. In truth, I don’t know where these crystal skeletons come from, but I can feel in my bones that I share the same roots as them… perhaps these skeletons were left behind by people of the primal god race…”

“Primal god race!?”

Lin Ming was startled. Why did so many people from the primal god race die here? How was Empyrean Primordius related to the primal god race? “Before, didn’t that senior say that there were very few people from the primal god race remaining? How come so many of them died here?”

Mo Eversnow shook her head, “I’m not sure. I only inherited Senior Heavenly Empress Xuanqing’s body and not her memories. As for how many of the primal god race are left, I am not sure. But what I can be sure of is that these crystal skeletons are the remains of people of the primal god race…”

Mo Eversnow had possessed Heavenly Empyrean Xuanqing’s body, thus she naturally came under the influence of Heavenly Empress Xuanqing. Towards the primal god race, she couldn’t help but feel warm and tender-hearted.

“Lin Ming, do you remember the Forsaken God Clan and the pendant of the jade goddess?”

Mo Eversnow asked. Lin Ming naturally wouldn’t have forgotten something like this.

In the past, when Lin Ming first entered the tomb of the ancient goddess, he had taken a jade pendant form her body, and he was even carrying it with him now.

Chapter 1376 – Black Dragon

Facing this ancient life form that was rushing towards him, Lin Ming didn’t hesitate at all to open up the grandmist space!

Mo Eversnow was also ready to face this adversary. She stepped forwards, combining her Primal God Pure Lands with the grandmist space.

Chi chi chi!

As that creature broke into the dual domains, its entire body soared, actually ripping apart the dual domains of Lin Ming and Mo Eversnow. Its bone-thorned scythe hands seemed as if they were a weapon that surpassed all spirit artifacts, easily tearing through space.

“This is an ancient saint race powerhouse! Or perhaps even a contract beast of an ancient supreme elder saint!”

Mo Eversnow rapidly shouted. And at this time, Lin Ming had already summoned the phantom of the Heretical God Tree. The power of thunder and fire wildly poured into the Phoenix Blood Spear – Heavenly Dao Judgment!

A spear thrust out, crushing the void.

This ancient life form crashed into Lin Ming’s spear light!

Rumble rumble rumble!

A terrifying storm of energy swept through the Eternal Demon Abyss. As this energy reverberated outwards, it caused countless glowing walls of patterns to shine in the air. As this storm crashed into these patterns, it wasn’t able to shake the great array at all.

In this frenzied explosion, Mo Eversnow also slashed out with her sword of light. Her attack was even more terrifying than Lin Ming’s. As her sword slashed out, a harsh whistling sound cut through the air.

A brilliant divine light seemed to swallow everything. It was like a round sun had risen within the Eternal Demon Abyss, puncturing through 10,000 miles of the gloomy haze.

Underneath the onslaught of such a formidable attack, the creature emitted an angry roar as it was sent flying backwards by the joint attack of Lin Ming and Mo Eversnow.

Bong!

With a loud bang, the ancient life form crashed into the barrier of the array formation, causing the shimmering walls to shake.

Its entire body was covered in blood and yet it still managed to crawl.

Lin Ming swept out with his divine sense and grimaced. In truth, the wounds of this creature weren’t heavy at all. It wasn’t leaking too much blood, and the injuries were only to the exterior body. The skeleton and tendons of the creature were intact.

Although his joint attack with Mo Eversnow was only 70-80% of their full strength, they had still directly struck the ancient life form. Even so, they still hadn’t been able to kill it?

Just what sort of terrifying defensive power was this?

Mo Eversnow said, “This is going to be troublesome. This ancient life form was likely a Holy Lord level powerhouse in the past, but because it was sealed away for 100,000 years, its sanity has fallen into depravity and all that is left over are its attack instincts.”

This ancient creature in front of them wouldn’t be able to use Laws or techniques, and its eyes were also filled with chaos, without the least bit of wisdom shining in them. Its offensive capabilities were the most barbaric and brutal methods possible, just forcefully hurtling against others and chopping at them. After being sealed for 100,000 years, this creature had been weakened to the extreme. Even so, it was nearly impossible for Lin Ming and Mo Eversnow to kill it.

At this time, two more loud roars echoed out. These roars contained a fierce killing intent, causing Lin Ming’s scalp to crawl. He turned to see more ancient life forms crawling out from behind the cocoons.

These two life forms were more similar to humans in appearance. However, their bodies were completely withered, looking as if they were in the last fading years of their life. But, the auras they emitted were still dreadful!

And behind these two life forms, there was also a red-haired man.

This red-haired man wore broken down armor. Two purple flames burned in his eyes and his disheveled hair was stringy and sparse.

However, his aura was vast and deep, as if he were a spiritual god.

Facing the aura of this red-haired man, Lin Ming felt as if his own flesh and blood would split apart. He didn’t need anything to know that this person was once a great figure of the past! He might have even been a World King level character!

A World King, even if they were sealed away for 100,000 years and were weakened to a fraction of their original power, still wasn’t someone that Lin Ming could deal with!

Moreover, this World King clearly had a glimpse of intelligence behind his fiery eyes. This person still retained his sanity, unlike those other ancient life forms that had nothing left but their instincts.

In that instant, Lin Ming suddenly felt that he was facing a danger beyond description!

He shuffled closer to Mo Eversnow, keeping full vigilance around himself. Lin Ming tightly gripped the Phoenix Blood Spear, his palms wet with sweat. Mo Eversnow’s complexion was dignified, her heart tightening.

It was impossible for them to defeat this existence in front of them. The only method possible was to use the array formation that Empyrean Primordius had left behind in the past. Empyrean Primordius should have left behind some methods to deal with these ancient life forms in the array formation, otherwise these ancient life forms would have left long ago instead of hovering around this area.

But, even if this sort of method was possible, wanting to find it and also activate it within several breaths of time was harder than ascending to heaven.

In this life or death moment, although Lin Ming’s palms were wet with sweat, his mind was as calm as water. He used his divine sense to rapidly sweep over the surrounding dao patterns, trying to see if there was anything he could use.

Mo Eversnow was also doing the same.

That red-haired man easily saw through Lin Ming and Mo Eversnow’s idea. He smiled – a cruel smile that crossed his face to reveal a pair of sharp canines.

“Futile… effort…”

The red-haired man actually spoke!

He spoke in the language of the Divine Realm, but his words were choppy and very stiff. Lin Ming felt his heart chill. He expected this red-haired man to have intelligence remaining, but he didn’t think it would be so high. It seemed that this 100,000 year confinement didn’t influence his mind at all.

How could he win against such an enemy?

As Lin Ming was lost on what to do, a sudden change occurred!

Not too far from Lin Ming, the iron chain that was as thick as a divine tree suddenly started trembling!

Bang bang bang!

The iron rings emitted a horrifying sound. These iron rings, if any single one of them were taken out and thrown down from high in the air, could easily smash apart a mountain!

With hundreds of thousands and millions of iron rings smashing together, it was like 10,000 thunderbolts suddenly being cast to the ground, the sound piercing straight into the ears!

This is…

Lin Ming was shocked. He looked at the massive chain. This chain was cast from divine iron and the weight of every link was simply unimaginable. Even so, hundreds of thousands of miles of this chain was shaken so wildly… just what sort of great strength was this?

Rumble rumble rumble!

Iron chains struck the stone wall, bringing massive chunks of stone falling down. The entire 100 million mile plus long wall of the Eternal Demon Abyss began to shake!

Such a horrifying power and might could truly be described as earth-shaking.

As the red-haired man heard this sound, the color of fear flooded his eyes. He looked deeply at Lin Ming before silently withdrawing back into the darkness.

The three other ancient life forms that came out with him also retreated.

They had left like that? Lin Ming’s mind stirred. This was…

Ang – !

At this time, a horrifying noise hurtled up from the depths of the Eternal Demon Abyss, setting off a terrifying storm of air that smashed into the rock walls, sweeping outwards for tens of thousands of miles. Lin Ming and Mo Eversnow were both caught up in this air current formed from the sound and were sent flying away!

All of this infernal energy, all of that dim haze, were completely flushed cleanly away by the horrifying sound.

This terrifying sound seemed to come from the endless ancient flow of time, piercing through reality!

This is…

A dragon’s roar?

Lin Ming supported himself with his Phoenix Blood Spear and slowly stood up. He looked as deep into the Eternal Demon Abyss as he could. Even so, all he could see was an endless darkness without a hint of light, as if it were a tunnel leading to another universe.

Lin Ming already had a faint speculation about what was happening. An existence that could make these ancient kings tremble in fear and even shake the trillion jin iron chains, perhaps the only possibility was the mysterious Black Dragon that was sealed away in the Eternal Demon Abyss.

And that dragon’s roar a moment ago had confirmed Lin Ming’s guess.

In the Eternal Demon Abyss, there was a living Black Dragon that once had a vital relationship with Empyrean Primordius in the past!

Perhaps it was the guardian God Beast of the Eternal Demon Abyss.

“Black Dragon…”

Mo Eversnow looked at Lin Ming. In the past, when Lin Ming had once entered the thousand mile forbidden zone by mistake, he had seen this Black Dragon. Its body was thousands of miles long and covered in brilliant red scales. Its horn was as tall as a mountain and its wings were like the starry night. After they were unfolded, those wings seemed to cover the vault of the heavens.

This was a true God Beast. Before that point, not even Mo Eversnow had seen one.

“Did the Black Dragon save us? That roar shouldn’t be a coincidence.” Mo Eversnow said. That roar was clearly a warning to these ancient life forms, otherwise they wouldn’t have backed away.

If this were true, then in a sense, Lin Ming had obtained the approval of the Eternal Demon Abyss’s guardian.

Lin Ming and Mo Eversnow looked at each other and then continued forwards.

And at this time, in the far off distance, there was the echoing sound of flapping clothes. Lin Ming looked up to see two skinny old men walking on the void, breaking through the wind.

Lin Ming was surprised and immediately grasped the Phoenix Blood Spear. But, he wasn’t too worried. With the deterrence of the Black Dragon, these two that were walking towards him had to be from the human race.

Human race? Were these Empyrean Primordius’ followers in the past?

Lin Ming immediately thought of this. Were the followers of Empyrean Primordius still alive in this world?

Chapter 1377 – The Gate of Space and Time

The two who arrived were old men wearing gray clothes. Their figures were withered and there didn’t seem to be any life in their faces.

However, their auras were formidable like a surging sea, making one feel daunted.

Then, they should have been disciples of Empyrean Primordius in the past.

“Junior Lin Ming greets two honored seniors!”

Lin Ming politely bowed. In Lin Ming’s opinion, the Eternal Demon Abyss was a land of death. Everyone here should have died in that great war 100,000 years ago; he never imagined there would still be some people living here.

In truth, thinking about it carefully, no matter how frigid that war was 100,000 years ago, there should have been some survivors. Even the saint race had some survivors, much less Empyrean Primordius’ followers.

A World King powerhouse could live for millions of years. To survive for 100,000 years in the Eternal Demon Abyss was only a fraction of their lifespan.

These two old men gazed deeply at Lin Ming and also looked at Mo Eversnow. As they saw Mo Eversnow, their expressions were extremely strange.

This was naturally because Mo Eversnow was possessing the body of the goddess.

“Are two seniors disciples of Senior Primordius?” Lin Ming asked.

The two old men didn’t reply. Instead, they only said, “Come with us.”

Then, they began flying deep into the Eternal Demon Abyss.

Lin Ming and Mo Eversnow glanced at each other before following suit.

Along the way, the two old men didn’t speak, nor did Lin Ming ask another question.

Slowly, Lin Ming could feel a great aura head towards him. The deeper he went, the more he felt that he was approaching an incomparably powerful existence.

Without a doubt, this powerful existence was the Black Dragon.

Lin Ming took a deep breath, his heart filled with awe.

In the past, this was the God Beast that had followed Empyrean Primordius. Just how magnificent was it?

The four people flew for around an hour. Lin Ming continued to hear the deep resonant dragon roar from the depths of the Eternal Demon Abyss, but now it was no longer just a roar. There was also a sound like a large bell being struck, its sound continuously echoing within the Eternal Demon Abyss as if it would last until the end of time.

The darkness gradually parted, and then, Lin Ming finally saw the Eternal Demon Abyss’ Black Dragon.

In the current 10,000 to 20,000 mile diameter of the Eternal Demon Abyss, half of this distance was occupied by the massive Black Dragon that extended for thousands of miles. Thousands of miles seemed simple, but when one was truly standing in front of this Black Dragon, only then could one truly understand how huge it was.

It wasn’t like a living being at all, but rather a celestial body!

It had to be known that an ordinary small planet only had a diameter of around 10,000 miles.

As Lin Ming flew towards this Black Dragon, he looked like a tiny speck of dust in front of it.

The Black Dragon seemed to be in a deep slumber. Its eyes were closed and it floated in the air. An incomparably horrifying aura was contained within its giant body. It was like all of existence, every living creature in this world, had to be respectful and cautious before this aura. This was the dignity of a God Beast. Once a God Beast’s strength erupted, it could even shatter the eternal heavens and smash apart planets and moons.

As Lin Ming flew to the Black Dragon’s head that was hundreds of miles wide, he was shocked by what he saw.

He could see that the black dragon’s spine, collar bones, wings, and four limbs were all locked down by thick chains. There were nine chains in total, and the chain that Lin Ming had climbed down on was one of these chains.

Not even hundreds of people holding hands could wrap around one of these chains. If one of these chain links were to fall down, it could easily smash apart mountains.

And, these nine iron chains were attached to titanic iron hooks. These iron hooks were hooked deep into the flesh of the Black Dragon, locked into its bones.

Because too much time had passed, these nine iron hooks had already fused together with the flesh and blood of the Black Dragon, becoming one with it. This was a ghastly sight.

This Black Dragon was actually caged here by these nine chains…

As Lin Ming thought of this, he let out a deep breath, an unspeakably heavy feeling weighing on his mind. Such a powerful existence had nine chains penetrated through its body, locking it here for 100,000 years…

“How could this be…?”

Lin Ming couldn’t help but think.

Beside him, the thin gray-clothed old man said, “This is the handiwork of the saint race’s Immortal Emperor… he locked down Dragon Sovereign with nine dragon trapping cables. After the war ended, because Honorable Master had burned away 80% of his blood vitality and had also suffered severe wounds, causing his boundary to fall, he was unable to unravel the dragon trapping cables. And, to break through dragon trapping cables with force would only cause the weakened Dragon Sovereign to die. But, to be trapped by the dragon trapping cables also means that Dragon Sovereign’s strength would slowly fade away until he perished. Even if Dragon Sovereign’s blood vitality is incomparably powerful, he would still only be able to last for 10,000 years here. Because of this, Honorable Master laid down a Yang Returning Grand Array, absorbing the power of the world, essence energy, and blood vitality from all around in order to make up for the strength that Dragon Sovereign lost because of the dragon trapping cables. With this, Dragon Sovereign would be able to continue surviving.”

“Yang Returning Grand Array…” Lin Ming recalled the saint race powerhouses that were sealed within the crystals. So that was the Yang Returning Grand Array…

This great array was used to prolong the life of the Black Dragon!

The saint race had bound the Black Dragon with dragon trapping cables, and then Empyrean Primordius had used the people of the saint race to form the Yang Returning Grand Array in order to make up for the Black Dragon’s losses.

This… was true endless hatred, a hatred that would never rest nor forgive.

As Lin Ming was thinking, he felt the space in front of him twist around. In front of him, a mass of fog appeared out of thin air, gradually solidifying into a tall and stately-looking middle-aged man.

This man was 30 feet tall. In front of him, Lin Ming and everyone else seemed like little children.

This man was pale white and his face was covered with black and red scales. His eyes shined like galaxies, profound and endless.

There was no powerful aura exuding from his body, but imperceptibly, the power of the void around this man twisted and shook as if it couldn’t withstand being in his presence.

Lin Ming was instantly aware that this man in front of him was the incarnation of the Black Dragon.

“Junior Lin Ming greets Senior Dragon Sovereign.”

Lin Ming respectfully bowed and Mo Eversnow also followed suit.

This middle-aged man glanced at Lin Ming and Mo Eversnow. In particular, Lin Ming. He looked at Lin Ming for a full ten breaths of time, peering through his inner world, spiritual sea, and probing his flesh and blood body.

“You can withstand the blood essence of Primordius’ emperor heart, and you have even opened the complete Eight Inner Hidden Gates. Your inner true essence is also unbelievably stable. As a martial artist from the lower realms, for you to arrive at this step proves that your destiny is truly dreadful, covering the heavens and moon. You are an extremely rare gem.”

The middle-aged man evaluated. He was most satisfied by Lin Ming’s attainments in the body transformation technique, because Empyrean Primordius was also a dual body and energy cultivator.

“When Primordius left behind his inheritance, I didn’t expect that there would be a successor with the ability to inherit it. I never imagined that today I would meet you. Lin Ming, are you ready?”

“I am.” Lin Ming respectfully replied. If the Black Dragon referred to Empyrean Primordius by his name alone, then it could be seen that the relationship between them was not that of subordinate and master, but like brothers, comrades who fought together.

Normally, an adult God Beast would have strength only slightly worse than an Empyrean. However, God Beasts were also divided into different ranks. There were some God Beasts that had a royal bloodline, and they were no worse than even outstanding top Empyreans. Lin Ming guessed that this Black Dragon before him was in that exact situation. This Black Dragon had clear differences from others dragons that Lin Ming had seen before. His body was far larger and he had a single horn and also a pair of giant wings.

“Then go.” As Dragon Sovereign spoke, he slashed at the skies, opening a gate of space and time.

From within this gate of space and time, a faint ancient and boundless aura rushed out, making one fall to their knees in awe.

Lin Ming had many questions in his mind, but he didn’t ask. He took a deep breath and stepped into this gate.

“You also go.”

The incarnation said to Mo Eversnow.

Mo Eversnow nodded and followed close behind Lin Ming.

The two gray-clothed old man watched as Lin Ming and Mo Eversnow entered the portal, silent.

The Black Dragon heavily sighed, saying, “When Primordius left behind his inheritance, he chose to leave it in a world of the lower realms… I never imagined that there would ever be anyone capable of inheriting it. For a lower realms world… it is simply too difficult to produce anyone talented. I wonder just how long this youth will be able to persist within Primordius Palace.”

“Maybe one year, maybe half a year. If he lasts less than three months then our efforts will have been wasted. Our thoughts are worthless, but what matters is that Honorable Master’s emperor heart blood essence will be wasted.”

As a gray-clothed man spoke, he still didn’t have any expression on his face.

“Three months… I don’t think it will be that short. Although I cannot be considered too familiar with humanity’s cultivation system, I can still see that this boy’s foundation is extremely solid. For him to have such powerful blood vitality and also be able to open the complete Eight Inner Hidden Gates is not because of the emperor heart blood essence but because of his own achievements. The fact that the emperor heart blood essence chose him is in itself proof of his amazing talent. No matter where he goes in the Divine Realm, he should still be a first class genius.”

The Black Dragon was unable to estimate what Lin Ming’s true combat strength was like. He could only speculate some clues through Lin Ming’s foundation. To classify him as one of the top geniuses of the Divine Realm was already a very high appraisal.

Speaking of this, the Black Dragon shook his head, “What a pity… when Primordius left behind his inheritance in the past, the difficulty he set to inherit it was far too high. To fully inherit it is a nearly impossible feat. Primordius was too strict; what he sought was perfection, and even in a world of the lower realms the tests he left for his inheritance were simply too hard. If no one is able to inherit it, then what is the point?”

As the Black Dragon sighed with emotion, Lin Ming had already stepped into the gate of space and time.

When Lin Ming passed through the gate of space and time, he felt his steps suddenly sink, as if something immeasurably heavy was pressing down on his body.

He was placed within a grand hall that was thousands and thousands of feet wide. The hall was extremely spacious, filled with deathly silence.

At this time, Mo Eversnow also arrived right by Lin Ming.

“This hall is…”

Mo Eversnow felt that after entering this hall, there was an incredible suppression on her. This suppression was not psychological, but originated from the suppression of one’s inner world and spiritual sea.

It was like there was some invisible force in this hall, suppressing the revolution of energy in the body, suppressing the flow of blood through the veins, and even suppressing one’s thoughts and spiritual sea.

This pressure left one strangely uncomfortable.

“This is grandmist energy! True grandmist energy!”

Lin Ming suddenly said. This heavy pressure was formed from grandmist energy.

In this hall, there was an incomparably faint wisp of grandmist energy. This was not elementary grandmist energy, but true grandmist energy.

Chapter 1380 – Trail of the Demon Bead

Lin Ming stayed within Primordius Palace for three years. This was something that the Dragon Sovereign had never imagined to be possible. In fact, when Empyrean Primordius left behind this test, the original intention of it was to have a martial artist withstand the heavy pressure of grandmist energy, allowing them to train in the Primordius martial intent as they perceived the Grandmist Heavenly Dao and opened the Primordius Gate.

But as for training speed, that all depended on a martial artist’s perception.

Originally, Black Dragon and the two old men both believed that if one could continue to withstand Empyrean Primordius’ test, then as long as they lasted for two years within it, they could nearly fully open the Primordius Gate. But now, Lin Ming had stayed within for three years.

The reason for this long period of time was that Lin Ming was refining grandmist energy.

He used one year and three months to absorb 30 wisps of grandmist energy.

Now, placed within the Primordius Bell, Lin Ming no longer felt that the heavy pressure of the grandmist energy upon his body was painful. Rather, because he kept pouring grandmist energy into his body, he felt himself filling up with a potent strength instead.

Finally, Lin Ming had reached the limit of his body’s ability to absorb grandmist energy. Lin Ming controlled his breath and collected those 30 wisps of grandmist into a surging current, using them once more to attack the threshold of life and death in his spiritual sea!

The already opened threshold of life and death opened even further as this mighty impact smashed upon it.

Lin Ming shook. His entire body released explosive crackling sounds as a strength beyond description erupted from within his body, as if a True Dragon were awakening inside him.

This strength recklessly flushed outwards, crashing into the Primordius Bell. With a loud echoing sound, the Primordius Bell was rung!

The melodious ringing sound echoed within Primordius Palace. The separate world that Primordius Palace was located in simply couldn’t contain this ringing sound. It echoed out, passing through the Eternal Demon Abyss, like the long beat of the Great Dao transmitted through ancient times, passing through from nothingness, cutting through the empty void and echoing throughout the skies.

At this moment, even outside of the Eternal Demon Abyss, many martial artists of the Holy Demon Continent could hear this ringing echoing between the heavens and the earth.

The 12 Skysplit Towers of the Blood Slaughter Steppes, the Tower Masters and High Lords, and all of the geniuses that came to adventure, heard this great sound.

This resounding bell sound deafened the senses, making the soul tremble as if it were the divine will of the heavens!

“Is it the Steppes Master?” Because of the Polaris Tower Master, the other 11 Tower Masters had already learned the news that Lin Ming, the true Steppes Master, had returned.

“What is the Steppes Master doing?”

“That ringing is coming from underground. It’s probably from the Eternal Demon Abyss!”

To the martial artists of the Holy Demon Continent, the Eternal Demon Abyss was the ultimate absolute life forbidden zone. Even when the number one master of the Holy Demon Continent entered the Eternal Demon Abyss in the past, they had still died.

Moreover, the Eternal Demon Abyss was now in its erupting state!

As the Tower Masters of the Blood Slaughter Steppes realized this, they were shocked, their minds immediately filled with awe.

And outside of the Blood Slaughter Steppes, the people also heard the harmonic ringing coming from the Blood Slaughter Steppes. It was completely unknown just what it was. This sound resonated several hundreds of thousands and even millions of miles outwards. Throughout the entire area, this sound echoed. This was surely something that couldn’t be accomplished by the hands of man!

“What sort of sound is this?”

“Could this be a sound coming down from the legendary Divine Realm?”

Underneath the baptism of this sound, everyone’s souls fell into awe and submission, a feeling of reverence filling their hearts. Some mortals even thought that a god had arrived so they fell to the ground in worship.

Only Swiftcloud Divine Kingdom’s General Wei was able to form some faint associations. Years ago, he had brought a mysterious youth to the Blood Slaughter Steppes. That youth, with his strength alone, had instantly defeated a battle array formed by a dozen late Divine Sea masters. And, these late Divine Sea masters each had the ability to easily defeat the Divine Sovereign of Swiftcloud Divine Kingdom.

This loud ringing definitely concerned that youth!

This concordant ringing continued echoing for a full quarter hour before it gradually subsided.

Lin Ming stood within Primordius Palace. In front of him, the Primordius Gate began to violently shake.

Rumble rumble rumble –

The shaking of the Primordius Gate became increasingly intense. A massive amount of dust was shaken to the floor. The gate had finally completely opened!

The moment that the Primordius Gate opened, an indescribable aura of the Grandmist Great Dao surged outwards, baptizing Lin Ming’s entire body.

As this aura of the Great Dao baptized him, Lin Ming felt himself fill with clarity. All of the strength within his body gathered together, wildly expanding his inner world.

In that instant, Lin Ming felt as if he had experienced an incredible change, like a butterfly that had broken free from its cocoon.

He knew that if he could thoroughly complete this change, he would have evolved from the Divine Sea realm to the Divine Transformation realm.

The key to Divine Transformation was the word ‘transformation’. Whether it was one’s spirit body or inner world, all would undergo a great transformation as they entered this boundary.

But now, Lin Ming’s accumulations were still slightly lacking. He had taken a half-step into the Divine Transformation realm, just a tad far from taking that final half-step.

He focused his mind, looking towards the Primordius Gate.

Sealed within the Primordius Gate was an independent space a hundred feet in radius. This was an ancient stone temple completely paved with timeless god stones.

In the center of this temple was a throne.

And on this throne, there was a person’s skeleton!

This skeleton was large and wide. It was inevitable that this person must have been a tall and stately person before they died. Their skeleton shined like crystal, countless dao patterns carved onto the surface.

This skeleton exuded a vast and profound aura. When Lin Ming had opened the Primordius Gate and the grandmist aura had surged out to baptize him, that aura had originated from this skeleton.

As Lin Ming stood in front of this skeleton, he could feel all the blood vitality within his body faintly resonating with it. His organs began to tremble and his blood boiled over as if it wanted to gush out from his body.

“Is this Empyrean Primordius’ skeleton?”

If just these bones had such an extraordinary aura that was even able to affect Lin Ming’s blood vitality, then perhaps only Empyrean Primordius could accomplish this.

However, he immediately changed his mind, thinking this was unbelievable.

Where was Empyrean Primordius’ flesh and blood body?

How come there was only the skeleton, but no flesh and blood body?

After an essence gathering system supreme elder died, their body would slowly decay until all that was left was a skeleton. Lin Ming didn’t think this was strange, but Empyrean Primordius was someone that had managed to open the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace and had tempered his mortal body to inconceivable heights!

Back then, when Empyrean Primordius had ripped out his emperor heart, it had continued beating for 100,000 years.

In these 100,000 years, that heart didn’t even show a hint of rotting away at all. Rather, it maintained its vast sea-like blood vitality, beating onwards for 100,000 years. Just what kind of terrifying body was that!

In Lin Ming’s opinion, even if Empyrean Primordius had perished in battle, his corpse should be everlasting!

Only when several hundred million years passed and all of the power contained within Empyrean Primordius’ flesh and blood was completely dissipated would his body finally begin to decay and his bones slowly become brittle and shatter.

“Are these really Empyrean Primordius’ remains?”

As Lin Ming stood before this throne, he could feel the pressure transmitting from the skeleton and see the dao patterns upon it.

Only an Empyrean could have so many numerous and profound dao patterns on their skeleton.

But this vast aura that simultaneously contained the power of the Grandmist Heavenly Dao made Lin Ming feel that besides Empyrean Primordius, there was no other candidate that this skeleton could belong to.

Layers upon layers of questions rushed into Lin Ming’s heart.

Could it be that Empyrean Primordius hadn’t died? Was there another mystery?

Or, perhaps Empyrean Primordius’ enemies were too strong in the past. If Empyrean Primordius was struck by that God Curse Art, then perhaps his body had rotted away because of this curse?

All sorts of thoughts flashed through Lin Ming’s mind, but he still couldn’t find a reasonable explanation for any of this.

He continued to gaze at the skeleton upon the throne. What he was sure of was that no matter who this skeleton was before they died, they were definitely an extreme character.

Lin Ming deeply bowed towards this skeleton.

After bowing, Lin Ming began to look around the stone chamber. In this stone chamber, besides this throne and skeleton, there was only a stone table. There was a single jade platform a square foot in size. And atop this jade platform was a simple brocaded box.

What left Lin Ming flabbergasted was that the material used to make this jade platform was actually nine sun jade!

Although it was only a square foot in size, the value of such a large piece of nine sun jade could be imagined.

But now, such wealth was only used to make the base for this brocaded box.

Just what was in that box?

Could it be…?

A thought flashed through Lin Ming’s mind and his breathing quickened. Within this box, he could feel something with a blood vitality that soared to the heavens, even faintly affecting Lin Ming’s bloodline.

He took a deep breath and then tentatively opened the box.

Within this box, there were two items.

One was a round black bead and the other was a simple ring.

This black bead was the size of a baby’s fist. It seemed like it was made from jade and not made from jade, and seemed made from stone and not made from stone. Countless mystical lines were carved onto its surface.

Within this round bead, Lin Ming could clearly feel an overwhelmingly vast blood vitality, as if it were a living creature.

“Is this the Demon Bead!?”

Lin Ming immediately thought.

However, he couldn’t confirm this either. And at this time, a regal voice sounded out, echoing throughout the entire temple.

“This bead is refined from a hundred million years of gathered blood vitality from the Grandmist Spirit Bead; it is a miracle medicine that surpasses a transcendent divine pill! However, the true Grandmist Spirit Bead has already been wrested away by the saint race.”

This sudden voice caused Lin Ming’s mind to turn cold. Was this the voice of Empyrean Primordius?

He swept out with his senses, wanting to see if there was some mysterious existence here such as a fragmented soul of Empyrean Primordius. However, he wasn’t able to find anything at all.

Lin Ming suddenly realized that this voice was only a message recorded by Empyrean Primordius using an array formation. Empyrean Primordius’ soul was not here.

It was a pity that Lin Ming still hadn’t been able to experience Empyrean Primordius’ dashing and heroic demeanor. After Lin Ming entered the Eternal Demon Abyss, he didn’t find a wisp of soul left behind by Empyrean Primordius or even his body.

He had only seen a part of Empyrean Primordius that he had left behind in the past: his heart.

“So the Demon Bead’s name was originally the Grandmist Spirit Bead… perhaps even the Magic Cube and all three ultimate divine treasures had different names given to them by different people over time.

“I never imagined that the Demon Bead would be taken by the saint race!

“Moreover, I have no idea just what price the saint race paid in order to start this war. Not just that, but for this reason alone, they likely had more than one Empyrean level master perish here. If they couldn’t obtain the Demon Bead after paying such a steep price, how could they ever give up?”

Lin Ming thought that no matter how powerful the enchantment was that Empyrean Primordius laid over the Sky Spill Planet, he still wouldn’t be able to stop the invasion of the saint race.

They were a race that was far more powerful than humanity. They had endless powerhouses pouring forth and a history of billions or even tens of billions of years.

If such a race decided to do something no matter what the cost was, it would be extremely difficult to stop them.

Chapter 1381 – Transforming the Divine Palace

Lin Ming carefully picked up the Demon Bead. This Demon Bead was only the size of a baby’s fist but it was as heavy as a mountain.

This Demon Bead contained essence energy, at least 10 times greater than the Demon Bead he had found before!

Originally, this was not a Demon Bead replica, but a Demon Bead formed from the condensed blood vitality of 100 million years using the true Demon Bead.

The Magic Cube could absorb souls and purify the soul fragments. Correspondingly, the Demon Bead should be able to absorb flesh and blood essence energy to form the most essential source of blood vitality.

“Junior, this bead contains a nearly infinite blood vitality. It is a supreme treasure to all body transformation martial artists. Today, I pass this on to you. You must use it cautiously and wisely; do not surpass the bearing limits of your body. In addition, within the Primordius ring I left behind there are many pills and spirit treasures, as well as the total accumulated knowledge and cultivation attainments in my 10 million years of life. Today, everything will be imparted to you. You must uphold my final will. When the great calamity of humanity arrives, you must contribute your own power to the effort. To lose the Grandmist Spirit Bead is the greatest mistake of my life. In there is ever a day where it is possible, you must retake the Grandmist Spirit Bead and return it to the human race, and seek a paradise pure lands for the orphaned god race.”

Empyrean Primordius’ words carried with them a thick sense of desolation. Although these words were the unfulfilled wishes he desired his successor to one day accomplish, Empyrean Primordius had likely merely said these words to psychologically comfort himself.

In truth, he didn’t think that there would be anyone able to retake the Grandmist Spirit Bead. This was simply far, far too difficult, a mission that required making an entire major race an enemy. Moreover, the strength of the saints surpassed that of humanity!

Not even Empyrean Primordius had this ability.

As Empyrean Primordius’ words were finished, at this time, the Primordius Gate began to wildly shake. In that moment, all of the grandmist energy that flooded the space within the Primordius Bell and outside the Primordius Bell began to flood this temple space.

The Primordius Bell was received into the temple where it hung high above in the center!

The enchantment all around the temple vanished. Lin Ming felt his vision instantly expand and he discovered that he had arrived in a massive Divine Palace.

This Divine Palace was thousands of feet tall, carrying with it a magnificent atmosphere and was emblazoned all over in gold and jade green.

Taking in a wider view, Lin Ming discovered that this hall was completely formed by violet sun crystals. Moreover, it seemed carved from a single massive piece of violet sun crystal.

Violet sun crystals were less valuable than nine sun jades, but they were also precious in their own right.

In the past, when Lin Ming went underneath Immemorial Imperial Palace, he had seen the Divine Seal Grand Array laid down by Empyrean Divine Seal. It was formed with countless violet sun crystals in order to write a single ‘seal’ character.

Currently, the violet sun crystals that formed Primordius Divine Palace were far less.

Not only was the main structure of the Divine Palace formed by violet sun crystals, but there were likely many other valuables inside that were extraordinary treasures.

Not just that, but on the Divine Palace walls, there were many murals engraved within them. These murals should have been the handiwork of Empyrean Primordius, and all of them contained the aura of the Primal Chaos Laws. Although they looked casually displayed about, if one observed and studied them closely enough, there would be significant gains.

If a young genius with high perception were to be enlightened from these murals, it wouldn’t be strange for them to make a sudden breakthrough in boundaries.

If any one of these murals were casually hung within a Great World King Holy Land, it would be an inestimable treasure that would be taken as one of the greatest inheritances.

Besides these murals and ornaments, behind the Divine Palace, there was a medicine garden. After 100,000 years, most of the plants within this medicine garden had reached the stage of maturity. These miraculous medicinal plants emitted fresh fragrances that refreshed the heart. If one just smelled these medicinal plants, they would feel invigorated. If a mortal were to breathe in this immortal fragrance, not only would it extend their life but it would broaden their minds. In some novels, there were stories of poor scholars that sucked in a breath of fragrance as they were searching for immortal treasures, and thus that smell awoke their minds, allowing them to become the number one scholar of the land.

“This Divine Palace… is truly a priceless treasure. It should be where Empyrean Primordius lived in the past!”

Lin Ming suddenly had this thought. In this Divine Palace he could see footprints left behind by Empyrean Primordius from the past. All of these ornaments and furnishings were presumably arranged according to Empyrean Primordius’ preferences.

Lin Ming was currently standing on the highest level hall of the Divine Palace. It seemed that the smelting trial Empyrean Primordius had arranged in the past had been within Primordius Divine Palace.

When Lin Ming had been in the smelting trial area, because the air was filled with grandmist energy and there were the protection of spells all around, he hadn’t been able to clearly see the full picture of Primordius Divine Palace.

Now, he was finally able to see its true colors.

“How luxurious!”

Lin Ming sighed with emotion.

At this time, Empyrean Primordius’ voice sounded out once more. “Junior! You may now refine the Primordius Gate. Once you do so, from that point on, this Primordius Heavenly Palace shall be your dwelling! There is an inherent space array formation within, so you may shrink or enlarge it as you please. There are also time formations contained within here that will allow you to control the flow of time. You may even use Primordius Heavenly Palace as a spirit ship to cross the void and journey out! Once you activate the Primordius Heavenly Palace’s great array, no one below an Empyrean will be able to break through the shields. Of course, the basis of all this is that you provide Primordius Heavenly Palace with enough energy!”

Empyrean Primordius’ few words left Lin Ming overjoyed.

No one below an Empyrean could break through!

This could be called an opportune act of grace from the heavens. Primordius Heavenly Palace wasn’t invincible. After all, once the array formation used up all the available energy, then Lin Ming would even find it hard to leave Primordius Heavenly Palace to escape any troubles. But, this would be able to buy a great deal of time for Lin Ming. He might even have the chance of using Primordius Heavenly Palace to directly break through the void during this time period and escape!

This Primordius Heavenly Palace could even be used as a spirit ship.

Moreover, one didn’t need to be a genius to know that this Heavenly Palace was much faster than an ordinary spirit ship! Once it began to undergo great void shifts, only an Empyrean master could hope to keep up with Lin Ming.

And from now on, he would be able to have Primordius Heavenly Palace as his own mansion?

How could Lin Ming not be excited about this? Although he was invincible amongst his age, the difference between him and the older generation was far too great.

He lacked a deep background, unlike Frost Dream, Xiao Moxian, and others like them. They had Empyrean level powerhouses to act as a deterrence for them and they often had the protection of Great World King level powerhouses.

This was one of Lin Ming’s most fatal weaknesses. Otherwise, he wouldn’t have been chased by Tian Mingzi to such an extent.

But now, with Primordius Heavenly Palace under his control, everything was different. From now on Lin Ming didn’t need to have scruples. Even if he were to encounter Tian Mingzi’s true self, he wouldn’t need to fear him.

As Lin Ming cast out his senses, he discovered that the Primordius Gate he had been watching all this time was in front of him. It was the main entrance to this grand hall.

And this great hall should also be where Empyrean Primordius closed up to cultivate in the past.

The most important room to a martial artist was not the bedroom, reception room, or meeting room, but rather their own cultivation area. Empyrean Primordius’ cultivation area used the Primordius Gate as an entrance, and then there were also countless array formations layered all within this hall, flooding it full of grandmist energy. In terms of training areas, this was one of the absolute best. By cultivating here, he would have twice the results with half the effort!

Lin Ming left the room and turned towards the Primordius Gate. This simple-looking gate was placed right in front of the Primordius Bell, like an immortal monument.

Facing this divine object that contained countless mysteries and was also forged by Empyrean Primordius himself, Lin Ming didn’t dare to be the least bit lacking in confidence.

He happily said, “Primordius Heavenly Palace, Primordius Gate, from this moment on, you shall accompany me! Today I am small and weak, and will find shelter in you. But in the future, when I rise to fame, you will shine in brilliance because of me!

“Primordius Gate, receive!”

Lin Ming generously cut open his wrist and sprinkled out a touch of blood essence!

To use his own source blood essence to imprint upon the Primordius Gate, only such a method was the most reliable and wouldn’t allow his mark to be forcibly wiped away by others.

Omm ~

The Primordius Gate began to shake, and the entire Primordius Heavenly Palace followed suit in vibrating.

Refining the Primordius Gate wasn’t easy or simple at all. If a normal martial artist were to come here, it would be impossible for them to do so. Even if Tian Mingzi’s true self were to arrive here, he still wouldn’t possess the ability to refine the Primordius Gate.

However, Lin Ming had already obtained the approval of Empyrean Primordius and he was also skilled in the Grandmist Heavenly Dao. Only someone like him could leave behind his mark on the Primordius Gate.

The burning hot blood essence fell onto the traces of the Great Dao Laws upon the Primordius Gate, circulating around it until it eventually carved itself into the pattern of a red lotus.

At this point, Lin Ming’s mind melded together with Primordius Heavenly Palace. It was like Primordius Heavenly Palace had become an extension of Lin Ming’s body. Every spell, every array formation, every rule and prohibition, he became aware of all of that.

Lin Ming was also able to clearly see through every corner of Primordius Heavenly Palace.

And at this time, Lin Ming also saw Mo Eversnow.

She was actually isolated in a closed and separated hall, unable to leave.

It had to be known that Mo Eversnow had stayed here for three straight years!

In such a long period of time, the average mortal would have already gone crazy. But from beginning until end, Mo Eversnow’s mind had been as calm and tranquil as a placid lake.

After Lin Ming was covered by the Primordius Bell, there had been no news from him. Mo Eversnow had been a little worried, but she also had absolute faith in Lin Ming. In her opinion, if Lin Ming couldn’t complete Empyrean Primordius’ test, then there would be no one that could possibly inherit his legacy. Even if this inheritance waited another 3.6 billion years for another great calamity, it still would never be passed on.

Thus, for these three years, Mo Eversnow had been at ease and calmly cultivating in the meantime. This sort of waiting required a tremendous amount of patience, and Mo Eversnow had never been hurried or anxious during this time period. She believed that the more time passed, the greater Lin Ming’s gains would be from Empyrean Primordius’ test. Perhaps when Lin Ming finally exited, she might no longer be his match.

Mo Eversnow didn’t wish to be left behind by Lin Ming’s progress. Otherwise, if he were to encounter some life-threatening danger, she would only be able to watch from the sidelines without being able to help. For instance, when Tian Mingzi first chased after them she had only been able to watch helplessly on as Lin Ming burnt over half his blood essence, to the point where he also exhausted his life potential and nearly died.

Mo Eversnow did not wish for such a situation to ever occur again.

So, for these last three years, Mo Eversnow had been diligently cultivating, slowly melding together her soul with the goddess’ mortal body even as she simultaneously improved her cultivation.

Mo Eversnow originally had a half-step World King cultivation. Now, with the goddess’ mortal body, her cultivation progress could be described as walking 10,000 miles in a single day!

Just as Mo Eversnow was deeply concentrating, she felt the space in front of her suddenly distort. In the next moment, Lin Ming stepped out into the hall as if he had teleported there.

“Lin Ming!”

Mo Eversnow was shocked for a brief moment before immediately being overjoyed.

Although her mentality had been wonderful for these past three years, she still couldn’t help but look forwards to Lin Ming reappearing. Now, Lin Ming had returned, and not only was he safe and sound but his strength had clearly risen a great deal!

This was truly a matter worthy of celebrating.

“Senior-apprentice Sister, I’ve had you wait a long time.” Lin Ming guiltily said. When he first accepted Empyrean Primordius’ test, that had also caused Mo Eversnow to go into seclusion herself for three years. He simply hadn’t thought that such a matter would occur.

“There is no harm, I can cultivate wherever I am. Usually when I close up for training, it isn’t strange for me to do so for 10 years at a time.”

Chapter 1384 – Child of the Dragon

“Lin Ming, come with me.”

The Dragon Sovereign waved his hand and a beam of light wrapped around Lin Ming, instantly causing the both of them to disappear. Lin Ming felt space around him twist about and in the next moment he had arrived in a completely separate space.

This space was extremely vast and broad. The area where Lin Ming was standing was a desolate and bleak land.

The brown and ashen land was endless. Broken rocks littered the ground, without the least bit of life anywhere. Occasionally, massive bones thrust out from gaps in the earth. It was unknown just what sort of creature had left behind these giant bones, but as these bones were half exposed to the air they resembled broken halberds that pointed towards the skies.

The skies were also empty, without any clouds at all. There were no stars or other celestial bodies and the heaven and earth origin energy was very thin.

In the vast distance, Lin Ming could even see certain areas of space collapse, crashing apart into turbulent space flows before returning to normal. Besides that, this world was without the tiniest sound; it was utterly silent!

“The space here naturally collapses on its own; this is proof that the space here has reached an extremely fragile point.”

Lin Ming thought to himself. This sort of world seemed like the moment in stories when vast dimensions were on the verge of annihilation. All life would cease to exist and space would become extremely unstable.

Great dimensions also had their own life cycle. After many hundreds of millions or even billions of years, everything would collapse before returning to nihility.

“This place is…” Lin Ming began to ask the Dragon Sovereign.

“This is my inner world.” The Dragon Sovereign indifferently replied, as if this didn’t matter at all.

Lin Ming’s heart skipped a beat.

Inner world!

The Dragon Sovereign’s inner world had already reached this degree of decay?

Although this inner world was incomparably vast, countless times greater than Lin Ming’s own, it was hanging on the thread of destruction, without the least bit of life!

If this continued, then perhaps in just several tens of thousands of years, this entire inner world would collapse into nothing!

At that time, the Dragon Sovereign himself would likely perish, forever gone from this world.

“Lord Dragon Sovereign, you…”

Lin Ming didn’t know what to say. He only felt a dark discomfort in his heart. A legendary character like the Dragon Sovereign, a being who was able to stand side-by-side with Empyrean Primordius as brothers in arms, was likely to be an outstanding character amongst all God Beasts.

Even so, such a grand existence would end up with such a pitiful fate, his life force slowly grinding to a halt until he exhausted himself and died.

“It doesn’t matter.”

The Dragon Sovereign’s expression was calm and peaceful; he had long ago accepted his fate.

“My life should have ended 100,000 years ago. It was only that at that time, Primordius used a great array to forcefully extract blood vitality and essence energy of the world to restore the strength I was losing to the dragon trapping cables, barely allowing me to maintain a feeble existence for all of these years. Life and death, those are things I have long since come to terms with.”

As the Dragon Sovereign spoke, he shook his head as if he were remembering that great war 100,000 years ago. In terms of strength, the Dragon Sovereign was naturally inferior to Empyrean Primordius. Underneath the combined assault of several extreme Empyrean masters, it would be extremely difficult for him to survive! Back during that great war he had already believed that he would die in the chaos. For him to live for all these extra years was already more than enough.

Lin Ming silently paid tribute in his heart. In a sense, in that war 100,000 years ago, Empyrean Primordius and the Dragon Sovereign should have known the general direction of their fates. If they sacrificed the interests of the world and only cared for their own lives they could have given up the Demon Bead. Although the Demon Bead was precious, it was still inferior to one’s own life.

And after giving up the Demon Bead, the saint race naturally wouldn’t have continued to pay such a great price to attack Primordius and the Dragon Sovereign. But even so, the two of them had refused to do so. If one had to look for a reason, then it was likely because they didn’t wish for the Demon Bead to enter the hands of the saint race.

This would cause the great calamity of humanity to become even more impossible to overcome.

Lin Ming couldn’t help but ask, “Lord Dragon Sovereign, is the Grandmist Spirit Bead now with the saints?”

“Yes!”

The Dragon Sovereign nodded.

“However… you once said that even if a True Divinity powerhouse wished to tear open the God Lamenting Wall of the 33 Heavens, they would have to use up a massive amount of their life source and even have their cultivation steeply drop for several tens of thousands of years. If so, then after the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign tore apart the God Lamenting Wall in the past to send Empyrean powerhouses of his race into the Divine Realm, the channel should have closed up. How could those Empyreans have brought the Grandmist Spirit Bead back?”

The Dragon Sovereign shook his head, “The saint race possesses more than one True Divinity! But, these True Divinities often do not have peaceful relations with each other, thus I have no idea how their relations are. Moreover, the Grandmist Spirit Bead itself has a certain function to pass through the barriers of the God Lamenting Wall, so the price of returning should be much less.”

“So that’s how it is!”

Lin Ming was suddenly aware. Divine heavenly tools like the Magic Cube and Demon Bead were the condensed form of the universe’s fundamental aspects. It was reasonable that they would be able to ignore the rules of the 33 Layered Heavens.

The Magic Cube definitely had such a function. When Lin Ming was in Carefree Island and had gone to the Red Desolate Mystic Realm, that Red Desolate Mystic Realm also forbade the entrance of anyone above the Divine Sea realm. By all reasoning, Mo Eversnow had already awakened and her strength had reached the Divine Lord realm, thus she shouldn’t have been able to enter. But, she did manage to enter and that was because she had hidden herself away in the Magic Cube space where she didn’t receive any hindrance from the God Lamenting Wall at all.

If the Magic Cube had such a function then it wouldn’t be strange if the Demon Bead shared it too.

Thinking of this, Lin Ming felt his heart stir. If so, then perhaps by relying on this he could find methods to enter the other universes.

The Dragon Sovereign continued to say, “To lose the Grandmist Spirit Bead is the greatest regret and guilt in Primordius’ life. In the past, Primordius and Heavenly Empress Xuanqing wanted to use the Grandmist Spirit Bead as the foundation to create their own Samsara Heavenly Dao, creating a paradisiacal pure lands that existed independently from the 33 Layered Heavens. They wanted to rely on this Samsara Heavenly Dao to unravel the secrets to eternal life, in hopes that when their lives came to an end they would be reincarnated with perfect memories of their previous lives and bypass the amnesia of the womb. Unfortunately, they ultimately failed.”

Eternal life was the perpetual and greatest pursuit of all supreme elders in the Divine Realm. No one wished to return to dust, and even Empyrean Primordius wasn’t an exception to this. The reason he wanted to establish the Samsara Heavenly Dao was to seek out the method to eternal life.

“Empyrean Primordius actually wished to use the Grandmist Spirit Bead as a foundation to establish his own paradisiacal pure lands that could stand side by side with the 33 Layered Heavens…” Lin Ming didn’t imagine that Empyrean Primordius’ aspirations were so high. The 33 Layered Heavens were not ordinary great dimensions. Rather, every Heaven was in itself an endless and boundless universe. To create such a world seemed far too exaggerated.

The Dragon Sovereign seemed to see through Lin Ming’s thoughts. He smiled, “You probably feel that Primordius was a bit too indulgent in his own whimsical fantasies. But, the truth is that if Primordius was allowed to continue on his road, breaking through into the realm of True Divinity and even reaching the peak of True Divinity, then perhaps there really might have been a chance of success. This is because the Grandmist Spirit Bead is the condensed ‘essence’ of a universe, and also the seed of a universe. Empyrean Primordius speculated that the Grandmist Spirit Bead, Divine Crystal Magic Cube, and other such divine objects of the heavens and earth are in fact a complete formative state of a universe. Perhaps there should have been 36 Layered Heavens, with universes of ‘essence’, ‘energy’, and ‘divine’, each leading groups of 12 universes. But, because of some unknown reasons, these three universes were unable to successfully grow, finally only condensing into universe seeds. The Diviner Crystal Magic Cube and Grandmist Spirit Bead should be these kinds of miraculous existences.”

As the Dragon Sovereign casually spoke these words, Lin Ming felt his mind wildly shake.

Universe seed? This was the first time he had heard of such a concept. He subconsciously traced his stomach… that small Magic Cube was really the formative state of a universe?

Lin Ming felt this was too incredible to believe. There was a universe within his body?

“Alright, I brought you here because there is something I wish to give you…” As the Dragon Sovereign spoke, Lin Ming felt the earth in front of them suddenly tremble. Countless runes appeared in the void, slowly spreading out in a large array for several miles.

This giant array formation was profound and exquisite, faintly gathering all the nearby heaven and earth origin energy. In the center of this array formation was a giant cocoon formed from crystalline silk threads. The cocoon was translucent, and one could even faintly make out what was occurring within.

Within, one could make out lumps of flesh that were wrapped up together.

“This is…”

Lin Ming could feel a vast ocean-like power of blood vitality rushing out from this giant cocoon. There was clearly a living creature within that cocoon, and it seemed to be growing ever so slowly as it absorbed the essence energy of the world.

The cocoon was covered in numerous complex dao patterns, exuding the aura of 10,000 different Heavenly Laws.

It was like an egg, an egg that wrapped a flesh and blood embryo.

In that moment, Lin Ming was already able to faintly guess what it was.

Following that, the Dragon Sovereign’s words confirmed Lin Ming’s guesses. “This is a unhatched dragon. I know that I do not have much time left in this world thus I have been preparing this dragon egg within my inner world. For these past years, I have been fusing all of my life source, blood essence, and blood vitality into this dragon egg, forming a flesh and blood embryo. This egg is now an extension of my life. Soon, in the future, it will hatch, and I do not wish to see it be born into the world of the Eternal Demon Abyss, a land without life or light. Take it, and treat it well, allow it to see the vast mysteries of the endless universes…”

As the Dragon Sovereign spoke, the countless silk threads that wrapped the dragon egg split apart and the dragon egg came slowly floating towards Lin Ming.

This was a baby God Beast, a true God Beast.

Lin Ming held his breath, his eyes staring unblinkingly at this unhatched dragon egg. Up until now he had never had a true contract beast. Most extreme talents like him were also the same; even Frost Dream and Hang Chi were the same.

It wasn’t because contract beasts were useless, but because they couldn’t find one that was appropriate.

A God Beast was simply an unthinkable wish. As for other contract beasts, their rate of growth couldn’t compare to these peerless geniuses. If the talent of these contract beasts was cast too far off from these extreme geniuses, their function would be greatly reduced.

But now, Lin Ming possessed his own dragon, a true God Beast!

Such a contract beast was something that not even an Empyrean descendant could dream of possessing. This was because there weren’t many more God Beasts than Empyreans, and most God Beasts in existence were wild and freely wandering existences that were also incomparably proud and lofty; just which one would lower themselves to work as the contract beast of a human?

Let alone an Empyrean descendant, even an Empyrean wasn’t good enough!

Only an extraordinary Empyrean like Empyrean Primordius could possibly have the lucky chance to encounter a God Beast and also to subdue it. But in truth, calling it subjugation was wrong, because Empyrean Primordius and the Black Dragon were brothers in arms to begin with.

In the future, Lin Ming and this young dragon would also have such a relationship.

To be comrades in battle and also friends.

Lin Ming didn’t say any words of refusal. He simply allowed this dragon egg to fly into his inner world.

After the dragon egg fell into Lin Ming’s inner world, Lin Ming immediately summoned the pure world power within him to fuse into the dragon egg without reserve, nourishing the growth of the baby dragon.

Then, Lin Ming deeply bowed towards the Dragon Sovereign. “Lord Dragon Sovereign, rest assured that this junior will treat this child like a true brother!”

The Dragon Sovereign nodded. “You have a startling destiny. If it follows you, it will also be affected by your destiny. I hope that because of this, its future growth will be even better…”

Chapter 1389 – Meeting

“This… this…”

The Seven Star youth sitting beside Lin Ming had already entered a stunned state, completely slack-jawed. He originally thought that Lin Ming was Lin Xiaoge’s lover, but now that he saw so many great figures fly over to the packed little corner he was sitting at, he was left dumbfounded.

It would be almost impossible for him to see any of these characters.

Let alone these people, even high stage Life Destruction martial artists that were ranked on the Destiny Decree were nothing but mythical existences to him.

But now, so many of these top level figures were right next to him. Just the pressure they exuded was hard to withstand.

And, all of these characters had gathered around Lin Ming. As for little princess Lin Xiaoge, she was continuously crying in Lin Ming’s arms.

Just who was this young man?

The Seven Star youth’s brain was already abuzz with chaos; he could not imagine just who Lin Ming truly was.

And besides the Seven Star youth, everyone else in the audience wasn’t sure what was happening either. They were already panic-stricken and in shock, so how could they have the presence of mind to think about it?

At this time, the Seven Star Divine Kingdom’s Divine Sovereign Li Yuxiao’s few words caused the hearts of all present to shake.

“Seven Star Kingdom’s Li Yuxiao greets Sage Lin.”

Lin Ming was far younger than Li Yuxiao, but Li Yuxiao still greeted him with the utmost respect. In the world of martial arts, strength was revered above all. As for Lin Ming’s strength, he had already far surpassed them by 108,000 miles as well as being the great benefactor to all those present.

“Sage Lin? What did the Seven Star Divine Sovereign just say? That young man is Sage Lin?”

For most in the audience, this was the first time that they had seen Lin Ming. They never imagined that this character who had created the most fantastic and wondrous myth in the Sky Spill Continent, a great hero who far surpassed all others, would actually be standing right in front of them.

This sort of feeling was just like a mortal casually bumping into someone on the city streets and finding out that they were the current Emperor. Moreover, to these martial artists, the shock of seeing Lin Ming was at least a hundred times more intense than a mortal running into his Emperor!

“It’s really Sage Lin! Didn’t Sage Lin already ascend? How could he have returned to the Sky Spill Continent? I heard that those who ascend aren’t able to return?”

“I have no idea. We cannot speculate on the affairs of such greater characters. I never imagined that Sage Lin would be so young! He seems like a young man in his early twenties.”

“What nonsense, Sage Lin is very young to begin with. When he rose to fame he was just over twenty years old, and now he should be in his thirties.”

Lin Ming was far too strong. People subconsciously regarded Lin Ming as their senior, forgetting the fact that he was thirty some years old.

And not too far away from Lin Ming, the Seven Star youth felt his hand shaking.

His hand had been patting Lin Ming’s shoulder just now!

Rubbing his hand, the Seven Star youth felt his entire body lighten up, as if he were living a dream. “I actually spoke to Sage Lin and I even patted his shoulder. I ever said that nobodies like us would have no chance of matching with Lin Xiaoge… whatever happened, I’m glad I didn’t say anything too excessive or who knows how I would have ended up…”

It wasn’t just the Seven Star youth, but all those around him who had been seriously ‘educating’ him about Demonshine, the divine guardian hound of the Vermillion Bird Divine Kingdom, felt their minds go blank, completely losing all ability to process any thoughts.

“Shang Family’s Shang Yuetian greets Sage Lin.”

“White Clan’s Snow Gale greets Sage Lin.”

One by one, all the great figures present came up to greet Lin Ming.

Those with the qualifications to stand in the inner circle and greet Lin Ming directly were all Divine Sovereigns, heads of great families, or at least top level Princes of Divine Kingdoms. Without an exception, each one was a Divine Sea powerhouse.

As for those Sovereigns and Patriarchs of lower level sects and family clans, all of them were stuck in the periphery, simply not possessing the ability to speak with Lin Ming.

As Lin Ming saw all these familiar faces once more, his face was filled with emotion. Over a dozen years had passed since these old allies had helped him lay siege to Yang Yun. Now, they had established their status even more, becoming the absolute controllers of the Sky Spill Continent.

With them looking after the Vermillion Bird Kingdom that was formed by Divine Phoenix Island as well as the Lin Family, Lin Ming could feel relieved.

And with the resources he left behind, that was enough to supply the Vermillion Bird Divine Kingdom for the next several hundred years. They would be able to train a group of core leaders in the upcoming centuries, and at that time, the Vermillion Bird Divine Kingdom would be much more stable.

At this time, a small red dog pushed his way through the bustling crowd, yelling out, “Lin Ming! Good heavens, you finally came back!”

With Lin Ming’s current status, only Demonshine was able to speak so carelessly and jokingly to him. When Lin Ming’s cultivation was low, it had been Demonshine who had helped protect him. The youth and the dog had gone through many trials together, and even though Lin Ming became far stronger afterwards, they still considered each other friends and comrades in arms, without any distinction between who was higher and lower.

Lin Ming faintly smiled, jokingly replying, “I suppose. After so many years, it seems you’ve also become the national divine guardian hound.”

Hearing these teasing words, Demonshine’s complexion turned red. He playfully said, “Don’t make fun of someone as great as me. In just a dozen some years, you’ve already returned to the lower realms from the Divine Realm. From what I know, it isn’t easy to return. You need the necessary strength to pass through the space storms as well as a considerable amount of money for the transmission fee. Normally, others wouldn’t think of returning to the lower realms so easily. It seems you’ve done quite well for yourself in the Divine Realm.”

“It’s been okay.” Lin Ming smiled, not bothering to narrate all his brilliant successes. If he told Demonshine that he had obtained second place in the Divine Realm First Martial Meeting, the little dog would probably go crazy.

“Okay is good enough.” Demonshine stretched out his paw, patting Lin Ming’s shoulder, seeming as if he were worried for him.

However, this scene combined with the earnest and serious expression on Demonshine’s face made one want to laugh out loud.

“It’s hard to survive in the Divine Realm. Many geniuses of the lower realms often perish in the years after they ascend. As for those that survive, most just linger around uselessly, barely managing to maintain a living. Those that can produce some results and finally rule over their own area are the minority within the minority. Luckily, your talent is far too freakish, and with someone as wonderful as Fairy Feng guiding you, this shouldn’t be a problem for you at all. So how is it, have your days at the Ancient Phoenix Clan been well?”

Demonshine knew that Lin Ming met with Fairy Feng, thus he naturally assumed that Lin Ming was also residing at the Ancient Phoenix Clan.

“I left the Ancient Phoenix Clan a long time ago…” Lin Ming casually said. When he had decided to go to the True Martial Great World to inherit the wealth that Mo Eversnow left behind, he had left the Ancient Phoenix Clan. Now, only his name existed there.

Looking back at his journey these past years, when Lin Ming first ascended, he needed the protection of Fairy Feng in order to reach the Divine Realm. Otherwise, he would have been torn apart by the space storms that existed between the lower realms and the Divine Realm.

But now, Lin Ming’s strength far surpassed that of Fairy Feng. And in order to accomplish this, Lin Ming had put forth an endless level of effort, experiencing countless struggles, and even surviving innumerable life or death battles and dangerous situations.

Lin Ming didn’t speak of any of this to Demonshine. He only smiled, clearly and gently.

“You’ve left the Ancient Phoenix Clan? Isn’t that a bit too premature? The Ancient Phoenix Clan is a Holy Land level influence of the Divine Realm and they have many resources that are quite good. If you leave the Ancient Phoenix Clan so soon, you might encounter many dangers…” Demonshine rubbed a paw over his chin, speaking with some worry.

Lin Ming chuckled. “There have been some dangers. Before I returned to the lower realms, I was in a tight spot, but I’ve finally resolved that manner. In fact, not only did I not lose anything, but I gained some advantages instead.”

Lin Ming naturally referred to the matter of himself being hunted down by the saint race’s spy and then Tian Mingzi. This was not just a tight spot, but an extremely dangerous death chase that nearly killed Lin Ming. However, he kept his tone even and understated so that he didn’t arouse Lin Xiaoge’s concern.

But even so, just a brief description caused Lin Xiaoge’s heart to tighten. She wanted to ask him just what happened, but Lin Ming only spoke a little bit about it to resolve her worries.

“Big Brother, Big Sister Qianyu and Big Sister Xingxuan both went searching for you. Have you seen them?”

In accordance with customs, Lin Xiaoge should have referred to Mu Qianyu and Qin Xingxuan as her sister-in-laws. However, she was used to calling them big sister, thus she continued to do so.

“Mm, I saw them.” Lin Ming nodded. Mu Qianyu and Qin Xingxuan had finally met with Lin Ming once more after several twists and turns in the Divine Realm. All of this was glossed over in just a few simple words.

“That’s wonderful!” Lin Xiaoge happily said. But at this time, she seemed to think of something. She whispered, “Big Brother… can I also go with you to the Divine Realm? I…”

Lin Xiaoge’s voice dimmed down. Her cultivation was simply too low. No matter how stable her foundation was, she still only possessed a Revolving Core cultivation, soon to enter Life Destruction.

This sort of cultivation naturally didn’t give her the qualifications to enter the Divine Realm. It was only that she feared that once Lin Ming went back, she wouldn’t be able to see him for who knew how many years.

However, Lin Xiaoge never thought that Lin Ming would only faintly smile and say, “You can. If you want to go to the Divine Realm, then I will lead you there.”

In the Divine Realm, Lin Xiaoge would have a better space to grow. As for Lin Ming, he only needed to place Lin Xiaoge, Mu Qianyu, and Qin Xingxuan in an Empyrean level Holy Land and he wouldn’t need to worry about any sort of retaliation from Tian Mingzi.

The only worry was the upcoming great calamity of humanity. If the situation turned out worse than imagined, Lin Ming would send Lin Xiaoge back to the lower realms.

“Big Brother, are you for real? That’s great!”

Lin Xiaoge jumped up in joy. She didn’t think that Lin Ming would agree to her request. Going to the Divine Realm with her Revolving Core cultivation was one matter, and even if she was able to ascend, she feared that Lin Ming would refuse her because he thought it would be too dangerous to take her there. Because of this, she didn’t believe he would agree so suddenly and readily.

“Big Brother, you’re too awesome!”

Lin Xiaoge jumped up and hugged Lin Ming’s neck.

At this time, not too far from Lin Ming, a black-clothed woman was standing calmly in the void, looking at him.

This woman was Situ Yaoyao. At this time, because of the intense battle that had just occurred, her complexion was still slightly pale. It made her seem a bit less demonic and a bit more delicate.

She and Situ Yaoyue truly were surprisingly similar in appearance.

Looking at Situ Yaoyao, Lin Ming couldn’t help but feel a tinge of guilt. No matter what was said, the truth was that Lin Ming was the one who had brought about the destruction of the Asura Divine Kingdom, toppling their dynasty. The order to exterminate the Asura Divine Kingdom had also been handed down by Lin Ming. With his strength and prestige at that time, he indeed possessed the ability to erase a Divine Kingdom with a few simple words.

The annihilation of the Asura Divine Kingdom had caused Situ Yaoyue and Situ Yaoyao to live a rough and perilous life. If that hadn’t happened, their growth would have been much smoother than it was now, and their statuses would have been very different. Although they would still have been inferior to Lin Xiaoge, they would absolutely have been unattainable and proud daughters of heaven.

“Is your older sister doing well?” Lin Ming suddenly asked in a soft voice.

Chapter 1391 – Seeking an Audience with Divine Dream

Divine Dream Great World –

An expensive and fast spirit ship shuttled through the starry skies. Along the way, one could faintly make out the mist-filled world of the Divine Dream Great World’s central mainland. This was a land of dream and illusion, filled with wondrous sights everywhere, beautiful to behold.

As one of the several largest of the Divine Realm’s 3000 great worlds, the Divine Dream Great World possessed the richest spiritual energy in the entire Divine Realm. The scenery here was correspondingly enchanting.

Lin Xiaoge stood within this ship, looking down at all the scenes in the mainland. She would occasionally cheer out, just like a child.

Even Demonshine came out to watch. After 50,000 years, he was finally returning to the Divine Realm so he was certainly excited by this.

“With the degree of richness of this heaven and earth origin energy, it should be one of the peak great worlds of the Divine Realm’s 3000 great worlds. How was the Ancient Phoenix Clan able to establish themselves on such an awesome world?”

Lin Ming faintly smiled. “We aren’t at the Ancient Phoenix Clan.”

“Mm? We didn’t go to the Ancient Phoenix Clan? Then where are we?” In Demonshine’s opinion, Lin Xiaoge was far too weak right now. It would be better for her to join the Ancient Phoenix Clan first. She would have the protection of a Holy Land as well as a safe place to train.

“We’ve arrived.”

Lin Ming suddenly said. This trip had taken over a month. If he had used Primordius Heavenly Palace to travel instead it would have taken less than half the time, but Primordius Heavenly Palace was far too eye-catching; Lin Ming wouldn’t casually take it out if he could help it.

Demonshine and Lin Xiaoge looked up to see a vast sea of clouds in the distant horizon. Within this sea of clouds floated thousands of celestial mountains, and these celestial mountains were covered with all sorts of wonderful treasures of the world. The most inferior of these precious treasures still exuded spiritual auras that were hundreds and thousands of times more intense than the most valuable heavenly materials of the Sky Spill Continent!

A mysterious and dazzling immortal palace floated among these celestial mountains, similar to an illusionary mirage that could disappear at any moment. Spiritual springs surged, coming down in waterfalls that looked like endless bolts of white silk sprinkling down from the heavens. A single drop of this divine nectar, if dropped onto a field of mortal grass, could turn all of it into spiritual herbs. But now, rivers of this water were sprinkling down into the sea of clouds, vitalizing the heaven and earth origin energy in the surroundings.

“This… this is…”

Demonshine’s three blue eyes popped wide open, filled with absolute disbelief.

This was definitely not a level of strength and prestige that a Holy Land level sect should be able to possess. If a single item from within this sea of clouds was to be dropped in a small world of the Divine Realm, it would absolutely provoke a bloody and terrifying war as all the small sects struggled for it with their existences on the line. But here, these items were only decorations that were casually strewn about!

Lin Xiaoge also oohed and aahed in praise. Her eyes were wide open, looking at as much as she could.

In truth, she didn’t know what this scenery meant. Even so, this didn’t stop a profound and amazed feeling from swelling within her heart.

“This is Divine Dream Heavenly Palace, the dwelling of Empyrean Divine Dream.”

Lin Ming slowly said. But as these words fell on Demonshine’s ears, he nearly spat out a mouthful of blood in shock.

“You… what did you just say? Empyrean Divine Dream!? Are you sure!?”

Demonshine’s claws shook. 50,000 years ago, he had followed the Demon Emperor to a mission at the Verdant Feather Holy Lands. In the army of 10,000 powerhouses, Demonshine had been insignificant. To him, an Empyrean was a completely unimaginable existence. Moreover, Empyrean Divine Dream was known as the most terrifying of all Empyreans. It was possible that she was the greatest powerhouse of the entire Divine Realm!

To Demonshine, such an existence was a god, and Lin Ming had actually led him here to Empyrean Divine Dream’s Heavenly Palace! Demonshine definitely didn’t believe that Lin Ming would bring them here just for some sightseeing.

Could it be… that Lin Ming had joined Divine Dream Heavenly Palace?

“Lin Ming! Are you joking with me? Did you join Divine Dream Heavenly Palace? No… that shouldn’t be true… it’s said that Divine Dream Heavenly Palace only accepts female disciples, so how could you have possibly joined?”

Demonshine had never lost his composure like this before. And beside him, Lin Xiaoge asked, “Uncle Demonshine, what is it? What is this Divine Dream Heavenly Palace…?”

“You won’t understand if I tell you. Even I cannot describe just how great the status of Empyrean Divine Dream is. In the past, when the Demon Emperor established a sixth-grade sect and then ascended, his strength increased by several times in the Divine Realm. But even during his prime, he wouldn’t even have been considered an ant in front of Empyrean Divine Dream! Empyrean Divine Dream might possibly even be the strongest powerhouse of the entire Divine Realm, the true god of a trillion quadrillion lives!”

Demonshine used the Demon Emperor as an example to explain Empyrean Divine Dream’s strength to Lin Xiaoge because besides Lin Ming, the most powerful character that she had heard of before was the Demon Emperor.

Although Lin Xiaoge found this hard to imagine, she could still faintly make out how magnificent it was.

Empyrean… the god of a trillion quadrillion lives?

“Lin Ming, how do you know Empyrean Divine Dream?” Demonshine placed his paws on Lin Ming’s shoulders, forcefully shaking him in his shock and excitement.

In his opinion, although Lin Ming did possess a heaven-defying degree of talent, it was still lacking when placed in the context of the entire Divine Realm. At the very least, he shouldn’t be great enough to enter the vision of someone like Empyrean Divine Dream. To a character like Empyrean Divine Dream, even Empyrean descendants were nothing but ordinary juniors not worthy of mention. In her millions of years of life, she had seen countless Empyrean descendants. Only the greatest peak geniuses amongst all Empyrean descendants could attract her attention a little, and that was only an extremely tiny bit.

“Lin Ming, how could your luck be so great? If you can bring us here then that definitely means you have some significant relation with Empyrean Divine Dream!” Demonshine couldn’t imagine just how Lin Ming had come into contact with Empyrean Divine Dream.

Lin Ming said, “I joined the Divine Realm First Martial Meeting and made it into the rankings, thus I obtained Empyrean Divine Dream’s attention.

Lin Ming casually said. In truth, he knew that if it weren’t for the pending arrival of the great calamity of humanity then he wouldn’t have attracted the attention of so many Empyreans no matter how wonderful his results in the First Martial Meeting were. But now, Lin Ming, Xiao Moxian, Hang Chi, and all the others were already recognized as leads in the future great calamity.

“What rank!?” Demonshine’s voice grew increasingly high-pitched and frantic. He had also experienced the Divine Realm First Martial Meeting in the past. He had known many people that he considered extraordinary in the past, but when they participated in the First Martial Meeting, a land of tides that washed away all until the true gems emerged, they weren’t even able to pass the preliminaries.

If one had to insist on their rankings, they were likely ranked under a million!

However, even that sort of result was enough to be proud of!

If Lin Ming could obtain the attention of Empyrean Divine Dream then he definitely wasn’t lower than a million in rankings.

“Second place.”

Even though Demonshine was prepared for an answer like this, he still froze solid, harder than stone.

Divine Realm First Martial Meeting, second place… this sort of result… was that a result that a human could really accomplish?

“Heavens! How could this be possible! Lin Ming, you actually came second at the Divine Realm First Martial Meeting? Just what have you been up to in your years in the Divine Realm!?”

Demonshine’s mind blacked out. He could be said to understand Lin Ming to an extent, but even so, he didn’t believe that with the level of talent that Lin Ming displayed in the lower realms, he would somehow have placed second in the Divine Realm First Martial Meeting.

And at this time, they had arrived at Divine Dream Heavenly Palace.

Lin Ming said, “Let’s leave this for later. I have to see Empyrean Divine Dream first. There is some extremely important information that I have to report to her. You can wait outside.”

As Lin Ming spoke, he left the spirit ship and flew straight towards the depths of Divine Dream Heavenly Palace.

“Disciple Lin Ming wishes to seek an audience with Empyrean Divine Dream!”

Lin Ming stood outside Divine Dream Heavenly Palace and spoke to the two female guards.

These two women both possessed Holy Lord level cultivations.

Divine Dream Heavenly Palace only had a mere several hundred core disciples. With the maids, guards, and other servants added on, there were only several thousand people. Of these people, every single one was outstanding!

“Enter.”

At this time, a faintly recognizable force spread to Lin Ming’s ears, like the quietest of sighs. This was the sound transmission of Empyrean Divine Dream.

Lin Ming was delighted to hear this. He estimated that in the four years he was gone, Empyrean Divine Dream should have long ago finished her closed door seclusion. Without a doubt, Frost Dream should have broken into the Divine Transformation realm much earlier than he did.

Lin Ming flew straight into the Heavenly Palace to pay a visit to Divine Dream.

After four years passed, Divine Dream was still the same as before. She wore a long white dress and there wasn’t the tiniest bit of a powerhouse’s aura emitting from her body. She seemed just like a mortal woman, but her appearance and temperament were like a blue moon in the highest heavens, as quiet and deep as an iceberg, noble and cold, disallowing anyone from having blasphemous thoughts against her.

Standing beside Divine Dream was a young woman who bore a striking resemblance to her; this young girl was Frost Dream.

And as Lin Ming thought, Frost Dream had already stepped into the Divine Transformation realm, and even surpassed Lin Ming as she had reached the peak of the early Divine Transformation realm. She was making great progress in stepping into the middle Divine Transformation realm.

Frost Dream was Divine Dream’s sublime incarnation, and not a true reincarnated soul that had passed through the cycle of samsara. Thus, in order to raise Frost Dream, Divine Dream had to pay an immense amount of resources and care.

“What is the matter?” Empyrean Divine Dream lightly asked. Her eyes swept past Lin Ming’s inner world and then her eyebrows pricked up. “Oh? You have inherited Primordius’ inheritance from the lower realms?”

Empyrean Divine Dream’s mental perception and acuity was more illuminating than the sun. Lin Ming said, “Yes! I have gained the recognition of Senior Primordius, thus this junior has inherited the full legacy of Empyrean Primordius.”

“Mm, well done.” Empyrean Divine Dream softly said. “Then you can now be considered a true descendant of Primordius. Primordius was a marvelous and prodigious person. If it weren’t for the matters that occurred 100,000 years ago, then perhaps he truly might have become a True Divinity in the future.”

Lin Ming’s heart skipped a beat upon hearing such a high evaluation from Divine Dream. Empyrean Primordius could have become a True Divinity?

In his mind, Primordius was similar to Divine Dream in strength. Moreover, listening to her tone, she likely placed herself on the same level as Empyrean Primordius.

If Primordius had survived to this day, then he would have been close to stepping into the realm of True Divinity. Then, what about Divine Dream?

Had she seen the realm of True Divinity? Or was she already a half-step into that fabled realm? Perhaps she was waiting for Frost Dream to mature before directly ascending into a True Divinity, becoming a true god of the Divine Realm!

As Lin Ming realized this, he felt that Divine Dream was increasingly unfathomable.

“Lin Ming, for what matter did you wish to see me?”

“Reporting to Senior, before this junior went to the lower realms, I needed to look for a mortal body for an old friend, thus I went to the Demondawn Great World. Then…”

Lin Ming reiterated his entire bitter experience with Tian Mingzi to Divine Dream, from beginning to end. He spoke of the Nine Star Heaven Pill that Tian Mingzi was refining, the saint race spy, and Tian Mingzi hunting him down all the way to the lower realms. He retold the entire story without omitting a single detail.

At the start, Empyrean Divine Dream didn’t have an expression. But afterwards, her eyebrows wrinkled together. “Where is the corpse?”

Empyrean Divine Dream suddenly said, an ice cold chill to her words.

Lin Ming quickly took out the corpse of the saint race spy from his spatial ring.

As Divine Dream saw this corpse, a cold light shimmered in her eyes. “It truly is the saint race! They ruined their cultivation to pass through the God Lamenting Wall and now wish to restore their strength with the Nine Star Heaven Pill. The saint race’s hands have already reached deep into many places within the Divine Realm, but we actually know nothing about them!”

Dim and gloomy clouds seemed to cover Divine Dream’s face. “Lin Ming, you have earned a great merit this time. In the future, when the great calamity of humanity arrives, you will surely be a part of the main force. From this point alone, whether or not you are my disciple, I will put forth my full strength to help raise you. You cultivate dual body and energy, and as for that Nine Star Heaven Pill that you mentioned, I actually possess an incomplete formula for it. I can attempt to help refine it for you to help you make a breakthrough.”

Chapter 1392 – Drastic Change

As Lin Ming heard Empyrean Divine Dream say she would refine the Nine Star Heaven Pill for him, he was ecstatic.

Under the current Laws of the universe, the Nine Star Heaven Pill by itself was likely insufficient for Lin Ming to break into the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace. But even so, it would bring Lin Ming closer to that final step he needed.

As he gathered more and more momentum over time, he would eventually break through that barrier.

Empyrean Divine Dream said, “Lin Ming, I will train you as far as I can, but I also need your word that in the upcoming great calamity, you will do everything in your power, exhausting your entire being to resist the saint race. Hair cannot survive without the skin. The Divine Realm is already the final universe of humanity, and once the Divine Realm is conquered and destroyed, there will be no foothold for humanity any longer. Every human will devolve into a slave of the saint race, and it is likely that we shall be washed away by the river of history!”

“This disciple understands.” Lin Ming solemnly nodded. This great calamity concerned the survival of humanity itself. The future of the human race was also his own future.

If all of humanity were to degenerate into slaves and the saint race were to massacre all human martial artists on sight, then it would be nearly impossible for the still low cultivation Lin Ming to reach the peak of martial arts.

“You’ve also brought others here?”

Empyrean Divine Dream suddenly asked. With her sense, she had already discovered that Lin Ming was coming to Divine Dream Heavenly Palace long before he arrived, and also knew how many people he had brought.

“Yes, this junior was too abrupt. Because I offended Tian Mingzi, I…”

“Mm. Tian Mingzi has a Great World King cultivation and he is even soon to step into the half-step Empyrean realm. If he wishes to move against your friends or family then even the Ancient Phoenix Clan will not have the strength to protect them. You may gather all of those close to you. The men will enter Vast Universe Heavenly Palace and the women will be kept at my Divine Dream Heavenly Palace. I shall look after them, and, if they are of the temperament to walk the road of martial arts then I may also provide them with certain inheritances and resources.”

Empyrean Divine Dream readily responded. Lin Ming was overjoyed to hear this. “Thank you, Senior Divine Dream.”

In the time following this, Empyrean Divine Dream began to move. She gathered the materials of the Nine Star Heaven Pill for Lin Ming. Although these materials were extremely difficult for Tian Mingzi to find, Empyrean Divine Dream was able to collect all of them in a mere few months.

As for the Nine Star Heaven Pill, Lin Ming didn’t begin to refine it. He felt that depending on the Nine Star Heaven Pill alone to break into the boundary of the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace was still lacking; he would need to support it with the Demon Bead essence.

Currently, Lin Ming’s cultivation was far too weak. He wouldn’t be able to absorb much of the Demon Bead essence and would instead waste it.

Thus, the matter of the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace was placed to the side. Lin Ming spent most of his time deep in cultivation within Divine Dream Heavenly Palace.

As for Empyrean Divine Dream, she took this time to launch a massive cleansing of the Divine Realm.

Her goal was clear – the spies of the saint race.

This was a monumentally massive workload and it also had to be carried out in secret. Otherwise, if the saint race spies were to find out and hide, it would be impossible to catch them all.

In normal times, this would be impossible to do; the Divine Realm was far too large and there weren’t many saint race spies to begin with. To find them was harder than finding a needle in the endless oceans.

But this investigation was personally led by Divine Dream. She would suddenly appear in a land without any indication at all and instantly open the divine dream space, causing everyone to fall into her dreamland. Then, she would probe everyone’s spiritual sea with the Divine Dream Law. Although it was impossible for Divine Dream to instantly search through all the memories of so many people, there were key differences in the spiritual sea of humans and saints, thus Divine Dream was able to search for this using her abilities.

The Great World King Holy Lands of all 3000 great worlds were the key targets of this investigation. In particular, those Great World Kings that had a high chance of becoming an Empyrean. This was to prevent a situation like that of Tian Mingzi from ever appearing again.

Only Empyrean Divine Dream was capable of such extraordinary methods, and this time, she was serious. Her actions were kept an absolute secret and as she searched through the various Holy Lands, all news from the inside was strictly blocked out. Not even ordinary World King Holy Lands were let off.

Such an investigation was an extremely burdensome matter; Empyrean Divine Dream used a full two years to accomplish this.

And, she had indeed found several spies of the saint race.

This result didn’t bring her any happiness at all. Rather, it filled her heart with a cloud of gloomy darkness.

This situation had surpassed Divine Dream’s expectations; the saint race had far more spies here than she had speculated. This also proved that the saint race already had an approximate understanding of humanity’s forces.

On the other hand, the human race was completely oblivious to the saint race. Divine Dream didn’t know how many True Divinity powerhouses the saint race possessed or even how many Empyreans they had. Even though she searched the souls of the saint race spies, she wasn’t able to find any valuable information. From this point alone, it was clear that the saint race had already made preparations in advance for something like this to happen.

Once they fought, the fate of humanity was likely to be miserable!

But, nothing could be done about this. Even if a martial artist harmed their cultivation to pass through the God Lamenting Wall, it still wasn’t that simple. A True Divinity and an Empyrean could do it, but they would have to lose a significant deal of their cultivation.

Divine Dream could also send human disciples into the universes of the saint race, but after the cultivations of these disciples were damaged, it would only be sending Divine Sea and Divine Transformation powerhouses into the saint race territories. The gains simply wouldn’t be worth the losses.

The situation was becoming increasingly grim. Empyrean Divine Dream had a premonition that the great calamity wasn’t too far away, and yet Lin Ming, Xiao Moxian, and the others still hadn’t grown up yet. Just how much time would the heavens give them?

Like this, another year passed.

Since Lin Ming returned to the Divine Realm, a total of three years had passed.

In the long history of the Divine Realm, a short three years was only an instant. Normally, this time period was too short for anything to happen.

However, these three years were doomed to be recorded in the annals of history…

………

On a sunny day, there was a land surrounded by mountains with a hazy origin energy filling the air.

In the Bright Luster Holy Lands, many young disciples had gathered onto a martial field, prepared for their long day of training.

The Bright Luster Holy Lands was established by the Bright Luster World King; they were also the number one influence of the Bright Luster Great World.

The Bright Luster Great World was a middle ranked great world, and the scale of the Bright Luster Holy Lands was comparable to the True Martial Holy Lands. They were a storied Holy Lands with a 5 million year history.

At this time, there were many intense battles on the martial field. Many Elders of the Bright Luster Holy Lands had appeared to direct the moves of the juniors, and even occasionally demonstrating skills to them. This was a sect filled with bustling liveliness and energetic peace.

At this time, the Chief Elder’s mind stirred. He turned towards the horizon, a hint of doubt flashing across his face.

“What is it?”

Several other Elders near the Chief Elder asked him, thinking someone had arrived.

“Strange… I felt the Bright Luster Mystic Realm trembling just now… it’s like something happened in the mystic realm?”

Many sects possessed their own exclusive mystic realm. These mystic realms often had many treasures and people could enter these mystic realms to seek the wealth within them. The only problem was that it cost a considerable amount of violet sun stones to open these mystic realms, and it was extremely difficult for any powerhouse at the Divine Transformation realm or above to pass through the barriers that separated the mystic realms from the Divine Realm. Thus, these divergent mystic realms had become a smelting trial for the young disciples of many sects.

The Bright Luster Mystic Realm was the largest mystic realm of the Bright Luster Great World. Compared to the second largest mystic realm of the Bright Luster Great World, it was at least 10 times larger.

The Bright Luster Mystic Realm had a vast and nearly limitless world within that contained countless rich resources. A significant reason for why the Bright Luster Holy Lands were able to rise to their current state was because of the Bright Luster Mystic Realm.

But on this day, the Bright Luster Mystic Realm was constantly shaking with tremendous changes occurring inside, as if it would collapse at any given moment.

This event alarmed even the Bright Luster World King.

“What is going on?”

The Bright Luster World King frowned. Even the Chief Elder was confused. He quickly called together the Divine Sea realm geniuses to enter and investigate the situation.

A massive number of violet sun crystals were inserted into the portal. And just in case, for backup, the Bright Luster World King even sent out a Divine Transformation realm core disciple. Because of this disciple, the activation cost of the transmission array increased by an entire nine sun jade.

A nine sun jade was worth a trillion violet sun stones. To a Great World King Holy Land, this was not a small amount of wealth. But, to spend so many violet sun stones on an investigation showed just how important the Bright Luster Mystic Realm was. The Bright Luster Holy Lands could not allow there to be any problems with it.

However, just as the transmission array began to revolve, a brilliant shine radiated outwards, causing the entire transmission array to explode!

A terrifying surge of energy exploded outwards. Many of the Divine Sea realm disciples present were grievously injured in the detonation, and there were even many low-ranking escort disciples that were directly killed.

“What is happening?!”

The Chief Elder was shocked. This transmission array had been used for the last several million years without incident. The construction cost was extremely high and it also went through inspections every decade. There shouldn’t be, and there had never been, a case of an explosion.

He hurriedly moved forwards to see just what had gone wrong. But then another terrifying explosion rang through the air. This time, even space was shattered by the energy. Even though the Chief Elder had reached the peak of the Holy Lord realm, he was still sent flying backwards and vomiting blood as he was struck by this explosion!

“Hahahaha! I’m here! I’m finally here!”

A reckless laughter echoed through the air. From the torn apart space, a group of figures flew out!

“3.6 billion years, we’ve waited for such a long time!”

“The shame of the past defeat will be washed away with your blood!”

“Divine Shifting Heavens, I will establish my immortal feats of wonder here! This is now the territory of my race!”

As strong roars and howls filled the air, countless people began gushing forth from the torn space. The disciples of the Bright Luster Holy Lands were completely dumbfounded!

As these voices fell onto the ears of the Bright Luster Holy Land disciples, they actually had no idea what these shadowy figures were saying; this was because they weren’t speaking the native language of the Divine Realm.

And, from these people’s auras, any single one of them was stronger than their Chief Disciple!

There were even those among them that could compare with the Bright Luster World King!

This terrifying mob of people could destroy their Bright Luster Holy Lands at any time!

And among these dark figures, a tall youth in white robes smiled as he drifted down from the sky like a spiritual god, looking down at the many Bright Luster Holy Land disciples underneath him.

This youth’s aura wasn’t formidable at all; he seemed similar to a human Divine Lord. But even so, the many World King and Holy Lord level powerhouses near him seemed to faintly respect and revere this youth.

This youth calmly lifted his right hand. In the palm of his right hand, a black bead slowly spun about.

As this youth appeared, all of the heaven and earth origin energy around him began to violently shake. The Laws of the heavens seemed to take this youth as their focal point.

As the Bright Luster World King saw this youth appear, his complexion completely changed.

Chapter 1393 – The Great Calamity Arrives

The cultivation of this youth in front of him wasn’t high, but as the Bright Luster World King looked at him, he could feel a sense of dread and fear in his heart, a sense of creeping unease about what could happen.

This terrifying possibility caused the Bright Luster World King’s body to turn ice cold and his palms to sweat.

“Who are they?”

“How could this be? No one above the Divine Transformation realm can enter the Bright Luster Mystic Realm, so how could they have come out from there?”

The many disciples of the Bright Luster Holy Lands wondered this. None of them yet knew what was happening.

In the last three years, news of the upcoming great calamity had already spread throughout the Divine Realm. But, no one would first think of the great calamity when something dire happened, because in their subconscious, this event was something on the distant horizon. To them, this was something that might not occur for tens of thousands of years or even hundreds of thousands of years.

Moreover, even if the great calamity were to arrive, none of those present thought it would begin at their Bright Luster Holy Lands.

As the white-robed youth heard the disciples underneath him talking to themselves, he sneered, “Are all humans so stupid?”

What he spoke in was the language of the Divine Realm, and these words instantly caused the many people below him to grimace. However, when comparing their strength to that of this other party, they could only hold in their anger without any way of speaking back.

“Who are you? Why were you in our Bright Luster Mystic Realm!?”

Several Bright Luster Holy Lands disciples loudly shouted out.

The white-robed youth laughed. “You are all really so stupid. Even now, you still have no idea what is happening. Then, let me tell you who I am. I am the Good Fortune Saint Son, and the 3000 worlds of the Divine Realm will all be the territory of my kingdom in the future!”

“Good Fortune Saint Son?!”

The Bright Luster Holy Lands disciples barely had time to react when the white-robed youth suddenly raised his hand. A black bead flew out and began to rapidly spin in the air. “Now, with your lowly flesh and blood, become nourishment for the Grandmist Spirit Bead!”

“Grandmist Spirit Bead! It really is the Grandmist Spirit Bead! How is this possible, how could the Grandmist Spirit Bead be in their hands!?”

The Bright Luster World King had a vast amount of experience. Although he didn’t know about the relations between the Grandmist Spirit Bead and Empyrean Primordius, he had still heard of this object before. Now, he watched with his own eyes as the Grandmist Spirit Bead emitted a thick and inky black light, seeming to shroud the entire sky in dark chaos. This scene made the Bright Luster World King feel as if his own heart were being slowly devoured by darkness!

And feeling the terrifying aura that these figures were sending out, the Bright Luster World King could finally confirm that the saint race had arrived!

The great calamity that he thought would come in several hundred thousands of years had actually arrived so soon!

“Run away! All disciples scatter and flee!”

The Bright Luster World King roared out. At the same time he didn’t hesitate at all and turned around to tear apart the void. But as he thrust out his hand, he felt the power of space repel him, bouncing back his hand. The Grandmist Spirit Bead had sent out an energy field that locked down the neighboring vicinity of space, making it impossible for him to use the great void shift!

“A smart decision. But what a pity, it will not change your destiny.” The Good Fortune Saint Son cruelly smiled as the Grandmist Spirit Bead shot out.

The Bright Luster World King’s complexion paled. He launched his movement techniques to the limit, wanting to run out of this domain.

And at this time, he heard a cacophony of miserable cries behind him. The Grandmist Spirit Bead had aroused a crimson vortex of flesh and blood. A massive number of core disciples, all characters that the Bright Luster Holy Lands had spent a great price to raise, were sucked into this flesh and blood vortex, immediately turning into pure flesh and blood essence energy that was then absorbed by the Grandmist Spirit Bead.

This horrifying scene was macabre and disturbing. And, the one who had begun all of this, the white-robed youth, was actually watching all of this with a smile on his face. It was like he wasn’t cutting down lives of others but plucking flowers from the ground.

“Two High Masters, that Bright Luster World King will be left to the two of you. With my current cultivation, dealing with the likes of him is still a bit difficult, even if I have the Grandmist Spirit Bead.”

“Alright, haha!” Beside the white-robed youth, two gray-robed men nodded. One had a giant head and the other was as thin as a bamboo pole. Although their appearances were strange, they clearly had cultivations at the level of a Great World King. If they were placed in the Divine Realm, they would be characters that could rule a great world!

The two Great World Kings rushed towards the Bright Luster World King together.

The Grandmist Spirit Bead began to shine with an even more demonic and monstrous light…

……..

Within his chambers at Divine Dream Heavenly Palace, Lin Ming was closed up in training. During these three years he had slowly gathered more and more accumulations, growing increasingly close to the middle Divine Transformation realm.

Divine Sea, Divine Transformation, Divine Lord, every time one rose by a realm, the time required to advance multiplied by several times.

At this time, a clarion alarm sounded throughout Divine Dream Heavenly Palace, the grating sound even penetrating into every training chamber! The training chambers were isolated by enchantments to form their own separate space, so as to avoid martial artists being disturbed during their cultivation.

If there was an alarm that could sound throughout the training chambers, this was a warning alarm of the highest degree, one that interrupted all martial artists during their seclusion. Unless it was a sect-annihilating event, such an alarm would not be sounded.

“What is happening!?”

Lin Ming’s eyes flashed open from his cultivation, a surprised light shining within them. He couldn’t imagine just what events had happened for Divine Dream Heavenly Palace to sound such an alarm.

It couldn’t be that the great calamity had already arrived, right?

Even Lin Ming also subconsciously believed that the great calamity wouldn’t arrive for an extremely long time.

Compared to the entire history of the Divine Realm, 10,000 years was an extremely short period of time. Although the great calamity was said to be soon approaching, this ‘soon approaching’ would often need tens of thousands or even hundreds of thousands of years.

Lin Ming’s figure flashed and he appeared at Divine Dream Heavenly Palace. As he appeared, he saw a great commotion of Elders and disciples rapidly heading towards the Assembly Hall.

Lin Ming’s heart also flashed with a moment of anxiety. He followed the crowd towards the Assembly Hall.

Empyrean Divine Dream was already waiting at the Assembly Hall. She had a solemn and dignified look.

After the main figures arrived, Empyrean Divine Dream finally spoke. “The great calamity has arrived. The first disruption of the God Lamenting Wall was at the Bright Luster Holy Lands’ divergent mystic realm. In one day, the Bright Luster Holy Lands was exterminated and the Bright Luster World King also perished in battle. In five days, the saint race thoroughly captured the entirety of Bright Luster Great World’s central mainland. Countless martial artists have been slaughtered and innumerable lives have been wiped away!”

“Great calamity!? How could it have come so quickly!?”

“Only several years have passed!”

“We aren’t prepared and yet the great calamity has come!”

Although the disciples of Divine Dream Heavenly Palace were elites amongst the elites, even they felt panicked upon hearing this news.

Lin Ming took a deep breath, tightening his fists as he grimaced.

Divergent mystic realms were originally transitionary spaces from the Divine Realm to other universes. If the God Lamenting Wall was torn apart somewhere, it would often be at these divergent mystic realms first.

“How could it be so fast… I’m only at the Divine Transformation realm. Even if I am invincible amongst those at my level, when facing the older generation, the most I can handle is a half-step Holy Lord. And in this great calamity, that level of strength isn’t even a tiny splash in the ocean!”

Thinking back to the great calamity of the Divine Realm 3.6 billion years ago, that was a struggle of Empyreans with even True Divinities taking action. Even the lowliest soldier had a Holy Lord level boundary.

A half-step Holy Lord could only be considered common cannon fodder.

In this great calamity, Lin Ming simply didn’t have any use or role to play. Let alone tempering himself in this great calamity, he only could watch as humanity fought with the saints.

This caused Lin Ming to feel very unwilling.

“Damnit, how could it be like this? If I had another several hundred years, then as long as I could reach the Holy Lord realm or a half-step Holy Lord cultivation, at least I wouldn’t be as useless and powerless as I am now!”

Lin Ming didn’t want his destiny to be decided by others. Now, if he wanted to rapidly enhance his strength, the only method was to enter a time enchantment and train. However, in a time enchantment, the Laws were distorted. If one couldn’t properly perceive the Laws, then that would make cultivating there far less effective.

Empyrean Divine Dream didn’t have any expression. It was only when the hurried discussion began to quiet down that she spoke again, “For this expedition of the saint race, the greatest powerhouse they have sent out so far is a half-step Empyrean. Even so, that is more than enough to annihilate a middle level world without an Empyrean present. In particular, in this war, there has been a person sent out called the Good Fortune Saint Son. His Saint Lord cultivation is equal to our human Divine Lord realm. This person possesses a mysterious bead that might possibly be the Grandmist Spirit Bead. Although he only has a Saint Lord level cultivation, he can still fight with a World King master! His level of talent is simply unimaginable!”

As Empyrean Divine Dream spoke, her eyes fell onto Lin Ming.

Lin Ming’s mind shook – Grandmist Spirit Bead!

When Empyrean Primordius lost the Grandmist Spirit Bead, did it fall into the hands of this Good Fortune Saint Son?

In that moment, Lin Ming’s mood was extremely complex. He remembered the final words that Empyrean Primordius had left behind in Primordius Heavenly Palace –

‘To lose the Grandmist Spirit Bead is the greatest mistake of my life. If there is ever a day when it is possible, you must retake the Grandmist Spirit Bead and return it to the human race, and seek a paradise pure lands for the orphaned god race.’

Lin Ming clenched his fists together. He had to retake the Grandmist Spirit Bead one day. However, he was simply far too weak right now.

Chapter 1395 – Fears of the Saint Race

“The saints wish to negotiate with us?”

As this news was spread out, many Empyreans were stunned.

A hundred Empyreans stood atop the 100,000 foot high announcement platform. The terrifying pressure of their combined auras caused even the celestial bodies in the skies to tremble.

They had originally held onto a determination to engage in war without fear of death, but because of the sudden proposal of negotiations from the saint race, all of these thoughts disappointed.

If possible, humanity didn’t wish to start a war of death.

However… why would the saints want to start negotiations?

If they planned on fighting until the extermination of humanity then there was no need for negotiations; they would simply start their all-out slaughter. If there were negotiations, then there would likely be talks of peace.

Just what did the saints fear?

From the start, the saint race didn’t begin an all-out war. Rather, they sent out World King, Holy Lord, and Holy Lord level powerhouses. The highest captain of the forces they sent out so far had only possessed a half-step Empyrean cultivation.

The Empyreans had only been used so far to protect the Good Fortune Saint Son and had been still the entire time. As for True Divinity powerhouses, they hadn’t been seen at all. It was clear from this that the saints didn’t wish to start an all-out battle with humanity as soon as they arrived.

Thus, the Empyreans wanted to know just why the saints weren’t willing to begin an all-out war. If they knew this point and were able to find out the bottom line of the saint race then they would be able to obtain the greatest benefits during the negotiations.

The deadline for the negotiations was in one month.

For this period of time, the saints and humanity fell into a strange and short period of peace.

On the Bright Luster Great World, the armies of the saint race no longer spread outwards. Humanity also retreated back into their safe territories, not coming into conflict with the saints.

The hundred plus Empyreans were still gathered at Mount Potala, staying up the entire day to discuss countermeasures. However, they weren’t able to come up with anything conclusive.

If there had to be a reason for all of this, then it was that humanity didn’t know anything about the saints.

“Humph! The saint race is just trying to play tricks! In truth, they likely aren’t much stronger than our human race, and even though they have a True Divinity powerhouse, that True Divinity powerhouse already overdrew his essence energy in the war 100,000 years ago. Now, they are probably only at the ordinary Empyrean level. As for the others of the saint race, if they are compared to us, then if we are both engaged in a true life or death duel war, it’s unknown just which side will ultimately perish, or which side will be able to obtain any advantages! Stealing our resources is important, but if they wanted to steal our resources at the cost of their lives, then even those saint Empyreans will have to think it over!”

The one who spoke was a large and robust bald fellow who wore a shimmering red robe. His title was Fire God and he was also an Empyrean powerhouse.

If someone were to dare title themselves Fire God, then that meant this person’s attainments in the Fire Laws stood at the peak of the Divine Realm!

This person’s temperament was the same as the Laws he cultivated, fierce and violent, just like fire. He stood in the offensive camp of Empyreans, and didn’t agree with the other Empyreans who decided to not do anything. He advocated directly engaging in a mass slaughter and struggling to the end with the saints.

The speculations of Fire God were what many other Empyreans of the Divine Realm were thinking; it also seemed to be the most reasonable explanation so far.

Perhaps… the saint race wasn’t as terrifying as they had imagined.

If the saints and humanity were to wage war, they might not necessarily lose!

However, in three days, these suspicions were all refuted.

After three days, the entire Bright Luster Great World surged with a divine light, with energy tyrannically gushing forth!

The tear in the God Lamenting Wall began to expand. At first, this tear was only in the Bright Luster Mystic Realm, but soon it expanded to cover the entire sky!

Looking at the starry skies of the Bright Luster Great World from afar, one could see terrifying surging currents, wild and chaotic. The entire sky was swallowed up by a massive black hole. This black hole slowly spun around, seeming to lead to another world.

At the other end of this wormhole was the world of the saint race!

From within this swirling black hole, terrifying life forms roared out. These roars didn’t need any medium to spread through the starry heavens, passing out to the trillions of celestial bodies outside! Moreover, even if one was extremely far away, these sounds still caused one’s heart to shake!

After one day, a massive claw stretched out from that swirling black hole, ripping apart the endless skies like a piece of ragged cloth! From the darkness, immense phantoms gushed forth. Their figures were fierce and vicious and they grasped heavy swords or carried spears. Each one emitted a horrifying pressure, making it difficult to breathe!

On the fifth day, the loud roars peaked to the limit, as if a thousand God Beasts were roaring out together. Their roars were mixed in with the crashing sound of metal shackles, dreadful and titanic. The sounds spread throughout the entire central mainland of the Bright Luster Great World, causing the void to collapse.

Even the human martial artists near the Bright Luster Great World felt their bodies shake, their blood energy surging upwards. Those with weaker cultivations even vomited blood, extremely wounded!

As the human Empyreans heard this sound, all of them were silent. Not even that raging Fire God uttered a single word.

Another Empyrean meeting was urgently held. The atmosphere of this meeting was one of dread and fearfulness.

That terrifying aura, that terrifying sound, those were absolutely not something that could be randomly sent out. In these days, there were absolutely at least a hundred Empyrean level existences that had entered the Bright Luster Great World. As for that final sound, it was possible that it was sent out from a True Divinity life form!

It wasn’t necessarily a saint race supreme elder, but there was a chance it could be a True Divinity level God Beast.

True Divinity…

Before the great calamity arrived, when the saint race was spoken of, although it was already acknowledged that the saints possessed a True Divinity powerhouse, this was an extremely distant matter even to Empyreans.

But now, as they felt the reality of a True Divinity’s pressure, all of them felt a deep desolate fear.

Fire God and many other Empyreans had strange complexions, all of them unable to speak.

Divine Dream sighed. “The saint race’s strength cannot be doubted any longer. They absolutely exist above humanity. They have more universes under their control, and in terms of resources or sheer numbers, humanity cannot compare with them. Before this, I also wished to find the reason for why the saint race feared engaging in all-out war with humanity. Seven days ago, I had the corpse of a saint race World King shipped back from the front lines. I searched his soul using the Divine Dream Laws in hopes that I could find out from that corpse’s memories just what the saint race was fearing, but in the end I failed to find anything at all. Now, all of you use your own methods to give it a try!”

In the war on the Bright Luster Great World battlefield, even the saint race had World King powerhouses perishing.

However, as Empyrean Divine Dream used a soul searching technique to probe the saint World King’s spiritual sea, she discovered that all memories related to the saint race’s internal workings were sealed away, completely impossible to read.

The person who sealed these memories was extremely strong, and compared to Divine Dream, they had a far more familiar understanding of the saint race’s spiritual sea and soul characteristics. As for Divine Dream, she was familiar with the human soul.

Empyrean Divine Dream waved her hand and a corpse flew out from her spatial ring. This was the saint race World King.

Ever since the war between humanity and the saints erupted, Empyrean Divine Dream hadn’t taken a single moment of rest. To an Empyrean, taking several years without a moment of rest wouldn’t influence them at all, but it would still place psychological pressure on them. Even Empyrean Divine Dream would feel somewhat mentally exhausted from all the work she had been doing.

“Divine Dream, if even you cannot search the memories, then perhaps we won’t be much better…” Near Empyrean Divine Dream, a gray-clothed old man spoke. In terms of the soul, this old man was also extremely skilled.

Although he said that, he still walked over to the saint World King corpse to give it a try.

Even though the situation was impossible, he still had to give it a try. Perhaps he really might be able to unravel the seal on the memories.

Facing the saint race World King’s corpse, the gray-clothed old man raised his hands and instantly formed hundreds of seals. Seven black skulls flew into the World King’s corpse, galloping around his body.

After a long time, the gray-clothed old man suddenly shook and he stepped back from the World King’s corpse. He shook his head over and over again, saying, “No… it’s not possible. Even I cannot find out anything. All I can confirm is that there are memories sealed within him and not erased.”

If memories were erased, they would definitely cause damage to the soul. To the saint race, even a World King powerhouse was considered a decent figure, so their memories naturally wouldn’t be erased so easily.

As the gray-clothed old man failed, many others tried their own unique soul searching techniques, using their complete understandings of the soul in their attempts. Even so, they were far inferior to Divine Dream and the gray-clothed old man.

Some people hoped there would be an infinitesimally small chance that they would somehow succeed. But without a doubt, all of them were completely defeated in their attempts.

Finally, this meeting ended without any result.

The deadline given by the saint race for negotiations drew increasingly near. There were even some people who suspected that these negotiations were simply a façade laid down by the saint race, a trap to capture all the human Empyreans in a single attempt.

There were also some people who believed that the saint race was using the negotiation deadline as an excuse to delay for time in order to slowly gather their forces. Once the month passed, they would not negotiate and instead launch an all-out offensive.

Everyone had different opinions.

Lin Ming was also staying at Mount Potala. He was silent as he listened to all these discussions.

He had heard that Empyrean Divine Dream brought back a World King’s corpse from the frontlines and had wanted to search their soul using the soul searching technique. But, in the end, she had failed.

“Even Empyrean Divine Dream was defeated. Do you think we have a chance of succeeding?”

Lin Ming asked Mo Eversnow.

“We can try… whether it is the spiritual sea of saints or humans, in front of the Magic Cube, a divine soul instrument that surpasses the highest Laws of the universe, all souls are the same. It is extremely important to the negotiations that we find out just why the saints are too afraid to commit to all-out war.”

Chapter 1401 – Sneak Attack

“What!?”

With this word, the entire audience was shocked. It wasn’t just the saint Empyreans, but even the human Empyreans were lost for a moment. Empyrean Divine Dream’s rejection had been too sudden. Her words had carried a tone implying that she had no plans of bargaining.

The Good Fortune Saint Son’s smile was frozen for the briefest moment before he coldly sneered. “Are you not satisfied with the conditions? We can hash out the details.”

Empyrean Divine Dream indifferently looked at the Good Fortune Saint Son, contempt thick in her eyes. “There is no need to discuss anything. I refuse any and all contents of this treaty.”

Hearing Empyrean Divine Dream’s words, the Good Fortune Saint Son’s complexion became increasingly dark. The human Empyreans were all panicked and began to constantly discuss amongst themselves with true essence sound transmissions.

Divine Dream was too forceful. Although this brash nature made many of the human Empyreans feel proud and elated, they still lacked courage when thinking back to how formidable the saints were, and they also feared that they had offended the Good Fortune Saint Son and taken this too far.

“Divine Dream, do you know what you are saying?” The Good Fortune Saint Son’s hands both grasped his fan. As the end of his fan scraped across the stone table, it made a high pitch squeaking noise.

The Good Fortune Saint Son had originally given space in the conditions to bargain with Empyrean Divine Dream. But, he never imagined that she would not bother bargaining at all and would flat out refuse him!

“Divine Dream…” Skyrend Godlord and Empyrean Vast Universe spoke to Divine Dream with a sound transmission. They were afraid that such an absolute rejection would provoke the saint race too far. If an all-out battle broke out, the consequences would be unimaginable!

“Divine Dream, you must endure the sword above your head; showing the necessary patience is what we must do here. Although we will shoulder the sins of humanity, that isn’t anything compared to the fate of humanity.”

As Skyrend Godlord said this, he and the others didn’t say anything more. Then, Empyrean Divine Dream actually waved her hand, “I understand.”

These words left Skyrend Godlord and the others without any avenue to speak further. Even so, they had no confidence about what was happening here.

“Is this what they mean by saying it is better to live as pieces of jade than to live as tiles on the ground?” The Good Fortune Saint Son demonically grinned and stood up. Beside him, the four saint race Protectors also stepped forwards. Astral essence swirled about their bodies, causing the earth to vibrate.

The human side refused to admit to being inferior. Although the 100 plus Empyreans here were weaker overall compared to those from the saint race, they still had the support of Mount Potala’s array formation. If a true battle began, even if they were defeated they would be able to cause deep losses to the saints.

With Divine Dream at the lead, there were also the great masters Skyrend Godlord, Emperor Shakya, and Great Limitless Buddha.

Ka ka ka!

The void shook. The four great masters of humanity stood in sharp opposition to the four Protectors of the saint race!

The eight auras smashed together. Of these, Divine Dream’s icy blue aura was the largest and most magnificent. With her strength alone, she forcefully withstood the pressure of two Protectors! As for Skyrend Godlord, Emperor Shakya, and Great Limitless Buddha, the three of them joined forces and withstood the aura of the remaining two Protectors.

“How interesting!”

The black-armored leader of the four Protectors diabolically grinned. The astral essence swirling about him became increasingly wild. At the same time, from between the four of them, a golden shining dharmic wheel took form and began spinning below their feet.

The human side refused to show weakness. Great Limitless Buddha smashed his staff against the ground. With a loud peal of thunder, the floor made of timeless god stone exploded beneath the staff. A massive amount of golden energy began to gather towards him from all direction, turning into Buddhist seals and symbols that gathered towards Great Limitless Buddha’s body!

For a time, Buddhist prayers echoed throughout the world. It was like a great bell had been rung, enlightening all!

This was the power saved within Mount Potala’s array formation and now directed by Great Limitless Buddha. By borrowing the battlefield of Mount Potala, he could multiply his strength. Even if the four saint Protectors joined together in an array formation, it was impossible for them to shake Great Limitless Buddha’s aura.

“Mm?”

The black-armored man’s complexion changed. He hadn’t truly started fighting. He had only used his aura to probe his enemies’ respective strengths.

The human Empyreans were far stronger than he had imagined. This also meant that if they were to truly fight, it would be hard for either side to gain an advantage.

Such a situation had never appeared since the negotiations had started. They had lost control of the negotiations.

Once the negotiations fell apart, the saint race would be unable to obtain any benefits. They didn’t want to fight here nor did they dare to fight upon returning. Like this, the saint race’s plan to put forth their strength and threaten humanity would completely fail.

The Good Fortune Saint Son’s complexion grew increasingly gloomy. Suddenly, he looked at Lin Ming.

Recalling the previous events, when the saint race had revealed their great strength, the humans had already acquiesced. Even that Skyrend Godlord had tacitly agreed to sign the treaty and was ready to bargain about the details of the treat. Even Empyrean Divine Dream hadn’t opposed this.

But then, Lin Ming had appeared from nowhere and had spoken some unknown words with Empyrean Divine Dream in a true essence sound transmission.

Following that, Empyrean Divine Dream’s attitude had taken a complete 180 degree turn and she had ended up rejecting all conditions that the saint race had put forth.

If someone said that none of this had anything to do with Lin Ming, the Good Fortune Saint Son wouldn’t believe them at all.

“Brat! Just what have you said to Divine Dream!?”

A deep cruel light of hatred flashed through the Good Fortune Saint Son’s eyes. This peace treaty with the humans involved a tremendous amount of benefits. If they signed it, then that was the same as grasping all the benefits of the Divine Realm without losing a single soldier!

Not only did this affect the benefits of the entire saint race, but to a certain degree it also affected the final result of the war between the saints and the spiritas. And, most importantly, the vast majority of the benefits would have flowed into Good Fortune Divine Palace, where he would have been able to use them. These benefits would have become a stepping stone that paved the way for him to become a True Divinity in the future.

Now, because of Lin Ming’s appearance, all of this had disappeared in a puff of smoke.

How could he not hate Lin Ming!

And faintly, the Good Fortune Saint Son had a premonition that this Lin Ming would become a scourge upon him in the future. If he were to ruin the long-laid plans of the saint race once, he might do it again in the future!

As the Good Fortune Saint Son thought of this, he took out the Demon Bead from his spatial ring and began to galvanize its strength with his bloodline.

With a horrifying roar, the phantom of a demon king flew out from the Demon Bead, hurtling straight towards Lin Ming!

This was not the Good Fortune Saint Son’s strength, but was the power that the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had sealed within the Demon Bead. The Good Fortune Saint Son had only spurred this power. But with his current strength, he was only able to animate a tenth of this energy. Even so, a tenth of this energy was amazing enough!

The Good Fortune Saint Son’s plan was simple. These negotiations were not going to progress anywhere, and since the humans dreaded a battle just as much as the saints did, it was impossible for them to start a battle first. Even if he did anything too excessive, the humans wouldn’t do anything to him. If this was the case, he might as well be excessive to the limit and kill off Lin Ming!

At this time, Empyrean Divine Dream and the others were all resisting the pressure of the saints. Even the other Empyreans had joined the fray. No one thought that the Good Fortune Saint Son would launch a sudden attack, and that his goal would be Lin Ming!

Seeing that black demon phantom rush towards him, Lin Ming was greatly shocked. He rapidly drew backwards, extracting the Phoenix Blood Spear from his spatial ring at the same time.

He could feel a terrifying strength approaching him, just hundreds of feet away. Lin Ming felt as if all the blood essence within his body was being pulled out. His body began to crack, as if he would be mercilessly crushed to death under this pressure!

Chapter 1402 – A 100 Year Agreement

“Lin Ming!”

On the human side, the many Empyreans were shocked. But at this time, most of them weren’t able to extend a helping hand.

At this critical moment, a white-clothed middle-aged man’s figure flashed like a bolt of white lightning in front of Lin Ming, facing this black demon phantom and punching out with his fist!

Bang!

With a terrifying explosion, the timeless god stones all around him completely disintegrated.

Horrifying shockwaves surged outwards. This was a collision on the level of Empyrean masters. Even though Lin Ming was protected behind this white-clothed person, he felt his blood vitality tumble within him, feeling as if his body would explode at any moment.

Peng!

Lin Ming thrust out his spear, breaking down several true essence shockwaves. Even so, he was still sent flying backwards until he roughly crashed into a wall. He coughed out a mouthful of blood, his face extremely white.

In that single move just now, he had been severely injured!

Just what sort of character was the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign? Even if his boundary had dropped, and the Good Fortune Saint Son had only used a tiny portion of the power he left in the Demon Bead, the might of that attack was beyond reckoning!

Once this strength locked onto Lin Ming, even though there were people around him to block it, he was still wounded underneath that tremendous swallowing force!

In the end, Lin Ming was far too weak.

At the Divine Transformation realm he was equivalent to a half-step Holy Lord. But in this meeting hall, that level of strength was the same as an ant.

Even the relatively weak Good Fortune Saint Son was still dozens and hundreds of times stronger than Lin Ming was!

Moreover, the Good Fortune Saint Son had a True Divinity powerhouse protecting him. All sorts of resources and magical tools were freely supplied to him; this was not something that Lin Ming could hope to compare with.

“I’m too weak!”

Lin Ming touched his own chest, examining his injuries. His internal meridians and blood vessels were in a complete mess, ruined by a dark energy. Without three to five days of rest, it would be extremely difficult to restore himself.

In this meeting hall, if there was any kind of intense collision, it was possible that Lin Ming would be sucked into the mess and perish in the aftermath. This was why Skyrend Godlord had opposed Lin Ming entering the meeting hall at the start.

This was the sorrow and pity of the weak.

“I must succeed Empyrean Primordius’ final wish and retake the Grandmist Spirit bead. I have to reach the peak of martial arts and inherit the will of Empyrean Divine Seal, leading humanity to cross this great calamity. But right now, I am weak to the point of shame. Even the aftermath of any attack here can ruin me, so what else is there for me to talk about?”

Lin Ming clenched his fists so tightly that his nails dug into his flesh.

He needed to become stronger, and he needed to become stronger much faster. This peace between the saints and humanity would only last for perhaps a thousand years. During this thousand years of time, he if couldn’t grow strong enough, just what qualifications would he have to say he would accomplish the dreams and wishes of those that came before him?

“Lin Ming, are you okay?!”

Empyrean Vast Universe grimly said as he protected Lin Ming behind him. Empyrean Vast Universe’s situation wasn’t too good right now. After frontally colliding with the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s power, although he wasn’t injured, he was left in a distressed state.

Empyrean Vast Universe angrily glared at the Good Fortune Saint Son. This was a meeting for negotiations, and yet he had attacked with a killing move without even giving a warning, all in order to eliminate Lin Ming.

“You blind and reckless little beast, to think you would dare to kill others during negotiations! Our human race will never tolerate someone like you!”

Empyrean Vast Universe blew up into a violent rage, immediately raising this matter to the level of his entire race. This caused the atmosphere in the meeting hall to become even more tense!

“Hahaha!” The Good Fortune Saint Son recklessly laughed. “What did you just call me? What gives you the right to speak to me like that? You are simply nothing at all! In 10 million years of life, you’ve only managed to become a middle ranked Empyrean, and in the future, this is all you will ever be! In my eyes, you are nothing but garbage! Thousands of years from now, you will truly be nothing but an animal to me. If I want to kill you then, it will be no different from slaughtering a chicken! It won’t take me any strength at all!”

“What did you say!?” Empyrean Vast Universe raged. His entire body swelled with blood energy as he neared the point of launching an attack.

The Good Fortune Saint Son thought little of it. He sneered, “Are you too stupid to understand what I just said? If you have the courage then we can engage in a life or death battle 300 years from now! Do you dare?”

The Good Fortune Saint Son’s words were aggressive and arrogant. Empyrean Vast Universe stiffened and all the blood in his body seemed to rush to his face.

He certainly remembered that at the start of these negotiations, Fire God had also come into conflict with the Good Fortune Saint Son. The Good Fortune Saint Son had proposed a death match several hundred years later, and Fire God had almost agreed. However, he had been stopped by Empyrean Divine Dream.

If Empyrean Divine Dream had done so, that was because she believed that several hundred years from now, Fire God wouldn’t be a match for the Good Fortune Saint Son!

And, Empyrean Vast Universe held a high degree of faith in Empyrean Divine Dream’s judgment.

As for Empyrean Vast Universe’s potential, he was even faintly worse than Fire God. Now that he faced the Good Fortune Saint Son’s challenge, he was left in a dilemma!

If he agreed, then there was an 80-90% chance he would die in battle.

But if he didn’t agree and chose to shrink back, then in this sharp and tense atmosphere where his actions concerned his own personal dignity and as well as the glory of humanity, he would weaken the momentum of the human race and also shame himself.

Humans had a sense of bravery and they also tried to live with dignity. This was especially true for those that had reached the level of an Empyrean!

At this time, Empyrean Divine Dream and the others were focused on facing the four Protectors. Empyrean Vast Universe grit his teeth, nearly agreeing to this battle!

But at this moment, Lin Ming raised his Phoenix Blood Spear and stepped forwards until he stood in front of Empyrean Vast Universe.

He wiped the blood from the corners of his lips and said, “Senior Vast Universe, if it’s going to be a hundred year duel, then allow this junior to participate!”

Lin Ming’s tone was casual, as if this battle was no big deal to him.

“Mm?” Empyrean Vast Universe was stunned. He didn’t immediately respond.

Lin Ming looked at the Good Fortune Saint Son and pointed the Phoenix Blood Spear straight at him. On the spearpoint, a cold light sparkled, blinding to the eyes. “How about you and I duel instead? I don’t even need 300 years… a hundred years is fine. In a hundred years, let us battle to the death. Do you dare to follow me?”

Lin Ming grinned as he spoke, revealing white teeth stained with blood.

This caused everyone to be shocked.

Lin Ming wanted to fight with the Good Fortune Saint Son in a hundred years?

For a time, even the confrontation between the Empyreans seemed to simmer down.

No one here doubted Lin Ming’s talent. But in the eyes of many people here, a Divine Sea martial artist fighting a Divine Lord master was much easier than a Divine Lord master fighting a World King.

In other words, Lin Ming was inferior to the Good Fortune Saint Son. And, the Good Fortune Saint Son also possessed the Grandmist Spirit Bead, a divine tool of the highest magnitude to help support his training. Moreover, there was also the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign, a True Divinity powerhouse that was pouring all sorts of resources and inheritances upon the Good Fortune Saint Son without limit.

Such a character only surpassed others. There had never been a time when others had surpassed him.

And Lin Ming actually wanted to battle him in a hundred years. To overtake the Good Fortune Saint Son in a mere century, just what sort of bold courage was that!

“Lin Ming! Don’t be rash!” Empyrean Vast Universe hurriedly said. He knew that Lin Ming was stepping forwards for him. Lin Ming wasn’t someone that liked owing favors to anyone. When Empyrean Vast Universe had blocked that strike for Lin Ming just now, and now Lin Ming was receiving this challenge for Empyrean Vast Universe.

A favor for a favor.

“You want to duel me in a hundred years? Hahaha!” The Good Fortune Saint Son wildly chortled, his eyes flashing with contempt. “I admit that you are talented. To come in second place in the humans’ First Martial Meeting can be considered decent, but what a pity, compared to me, you still fall far short! If our cultivations were swapped right now and you were at the late Divine Lord realm while I was at the early Saint Transformation realm, you might have a chance of winning. But unfortunately, that isn’t reality at all. My cultivation is over a large boundary and a half higher than yours! Let alone 100 years, even 1000 years or 10,000 years from now, you will never surpass me! Instead, the difference between you and me will only continue to grow larger!”

Between Lin Ming and the Good Fortune Saint Son, one was at the early Divine Transformation realm, and the other was at the late Saint Lord realm, equal to the human late Divine Lord realm. This difference in cultivation was simply too great. For a normal genius, it would be extremely difficult to rise from the early Divine Transformation realm to the late Divine Lord realm in a hundred years, especially in a situation where Lin Ming had to overtake the Good Fortune Saint Son while he was at it!

A hundred years from now, it was likely that the Good Fortune Saint Son would have reached the Holy Lord realm and would even have traced the threshold of the World King realm. At that time, his strength wouldn’t be too far away from that of an Empyrean.

The difficulty of this feat could be imagined!

“That boy has gone crazy! He actually wants to duel my race’s Saint Son in a hundred years, it’s as if he wants to die!” A saint Empyrean coldly scoffed.

“Hehe, does he think that the Good Fortune Saint Son is casually chosen from nowhere? The Saint Son is the next appointed Saint Sovereign of my people. From birth, he has gathered the destiny of my saint race unto him. With such a destiny supporting him, how can he not be lucky!”

“Yes, my race’s Saint Son has entered countless life or death situations, and not only has he not died but he has obtained innumerable treasures. Now, he even has the Grandmist Spirit Bead with him. In terms of fortuitous events, no mere human can compare with him. And in terms of inheritances, he is number one in the world! As for resources, there is no need to mention them. And, as for natural martial talent, he possesses the bloodline of the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign as well as the Saint Heavenly Demon Princess. From birth he has been soaked in baths of heavenly materials, and there is even the essence embryo of a God Beast fused into his body; his foundation and his bones are far superior to all others’. In the future he will definitely become a True Divinity level character!”

“Haha, how could this stupid little boy know all of this? Does he think he is invincible just because he obtained second place in some silly little human Divine Realm First Martial Meeting?!”

As the saint Empyreans spoke, they didn’t bother hiding their words with true essence sound transmissions, instead choosing to bluntly speak in front of the human Empyreans. With every word that fell into the ears of the human Empyreans, their complexions became that much uglier.

The Good Fortune Saint Son possessed the bloodline of the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign as well as the Saint Heavenly Demon Princess. There was also the great destiny of his entire race supporting him, and fused in his body was the essence embryo of a God Beast. There was no need to mention the various inheritances and resources he enjoyed.

How could such a character come to be? What did it mean to be the next appointed Saint Sovereign of the saint race? Did this mean that in every generation of the saints, there would always be someone that appeared on the level of the Saint Sovereign?

Even those that believed in Lin Ming’s potential, such as Empyrean Divine Dream and Empyrean Vast Universe, felt that Lin Ming had been too reckless this time.

“Lin Ming…” Empyrean Divine Dream took a deep breath. “Why did you settle on a duel in a hundred years? I know that you have some great heaven-startling secret that you are hiding, but it is impossible for that to surpass the Grandmist Spirit Bead. In terms of lucky chances, I fear that you are also inferior to the Good Fortune Saint Son. Moreover, this Good Fortune Saint Son has a great destiny swirling about him. If you wish to fight at some appointed date with him, I won’t oppose you, because in the future, you and him are destined to battle sooner or later. But, to set the date a hundred years from now is far too soon!”

Lin Ming thought for a moment. Before he put forth this hundred year date, he didn’t know that the Good Fortune Saint Son would be so lucky. Even so, he didn’t regret anything at all. “I thank Senior Divine Dream for the advice, but this junior has already set forth a date of a hundred years. It isn’t because I am arrogant, but because I wish to place enough pressure on myself. Any temporary peace between the saints and us humans will last no longer than a thousand years; it might even be much shorter than that. When the true great calamity finally erupts and I still do not possess the strength of a half-step True Divinity, what use is there in thinking I can do anything to help humanity resist this tribulation?”

Chapter 1403 – The Result of Negotiations

Lin Ming’s words caused Empyrean Divine Dream’s heart to skip a beat. Reach the same level of strength as a half-step True Divinity within a thousand years?

It had to be known that Divine Dream herself, Emperor Shakya, and the other leaders of humanity were only half-step True Divinities.

They had used innumerable years to reach this step, and now Lin Ming said he wished to reach this level in just a thousand years. If this was said out loud, who would believe him?

But, if he wished to play a prime role in this great calamity, becoming a half-step True Divinity was the most basic step.

This was a war that involved the fates of two races. Empyreans could be considered the backbone of the forces, World Kings were soldiers, and as for Holy Lords, they were nothing but cannon fodder.

Lin Ming didn’t wish for his own destiny to be controlled by others when the great calamity truly erupted. Even becoming a half-step True Divinity wasn’t his final goal. What he wanted was to become a True Divinity, someone that could frontally contend with the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign!

Only like this could he truly bring about a change in the war!

“Lin Ming, well said!” Empyrean Divine Dream suddenly said with a true essence sound transmission, “Geniuses should be bold and filled with determination, ready to make decisions that shake the heavens and earth. For us who walk down the road of martial arts, we did not do so to be defeated. Since you have recognized that this is the path you wish to take, Divine Dream Heavenly Palace will support you to our fullest capabilities.”

For Lin Ming with his Divine Transformation realm cultivation to challenge the late Saint Lord Good Fortune Saint Son in a hundred years was indeed a decision that would shake the heavens and earth. In several days, whether it was the saint race or human race, this matter would spread throughout both of them.

“Lin Ming, hehe…” The Good Fortune Saint Son looked at Lin Ming, a joking smile on his face. “Since you wish to duel me, very well then, let it be so. Let us form a heart demon soul contract with a transcendent divine might. 100 years from now, if one of us dares to back out, then he shall suffer a backlash of his heart demons, his meridians shall be torn to pieces, and his soul will evaporate into nothing, never to enter samsara!”

As the Good Fortune Saint Son put forth such a vicious and cruel oath, a demonic smile split his face. He wanted to rid himself of Lin Ming. Since it was no longer possible for the saints to co-exist in the Divine Shifting Heavens, exterminating Lin Ming could be considered a consolation prize.

Towards this type of genius that was sure to become an extreme Empyrean in the future, the Good Fortune Saint Son only thought of killing him off to end all potential troubles!

“Fine!”

Lin Ming readily agreed.

He and the Good Fortune Saint Son bit down on their fingers and flung out a drop of blood essence.

These two drops of blood essence connected in midair, forming patterns of blood-colored seals.

These seals seemed to burn like red-black flames. Then, these seals turned into curse seals that sank into Lin Ming and the Good Fortune Saint Son’s bodies.

Seeing this, all of the human Empyreans present were shocked. Once this heart demon soul contract was signed, it meant that after a hundred years, only one of these two geniuses would emerge alive.

Signing this sort of contract required a titanic amount of courage and confidence.

Lin Ming… could he win?

Hu – !

All of the blood vitality began to condense within Lin Ming’s body. The transcendent divine might curse seal formed a black-red mark on Lin Ming’s chest that slowly hid itself away.

The contract had been formed!

As the Good Fortune Saint Son saw this, he diabolically grinned.

He knew that the goal of today’s negotiations would not come to fruition. If they continued this stalemate there would be no meaning to it at all. No matter what the humans had learnt, it was impossible for them to give in any longer.

Killing Lin Ming in a hundred years was the only harvest of today.

“We’re leaving!”

As the Good Fortune Saint Son spoke he immediately turned and flew away. Behind him, the many saint Empyreans also followed him and left. The array formation of Mount Potala was torn apart once more!

Then, the hundred plus saint Empyreans tore through the void of the Divine Realm, disappearing from sight.

The human Empyreans looked at each other, speechless. Negotiations had concluded like that?

In these negotiations, they had all thought that they would have to make concessions, otherwise death and war would spread through every corner of humanity. But, everything had ended just like this?

In the end, the saint race hadn’t come at all. They had come in with a threatening posture and a menacing air, but in the end they left without anything at all.

From start to end, the saint race seemed reckless and wild, but the truth was that they never started an all-out war at all. Rather, they had tried to intimidate the human race, but once that intimidation failed, they were instead defeated!

This was proof that the saints dreaded something!

They were afraid. Even their powerful lineup was merely a mirage meant to threaten them.

But even so, it was true that the momentum of the saint race had been extremely horrifying.

If it weren’t for Divine Dream insisting until the final moment and defending their bottom line, then perhaps they might have truly signed this treaty with completely disastrous conditions for humanity!

Thinking of this, everyone looked at Divine Dream and then looked at Lin Ming.

They certainly knew that before Divine Dream’s attitude had undergone a complete change, she had conversed with Lin Ming using a true essence sound transmission.

“Divine Dream… what did Lin Ming say to you?”

The one who asked was Skyrend Godlord. He couldn’t imagine just what Lin Ming had said to change Divine Dream’s mind.

Before this, many Empyreans were puzzled as to why the saints didn’t dare to start an all-out war; it was as if they dreaded the human race for some reason.

But, those were only speculations. The saint race had at least one True Divinity powerhouse as well as many half-step True Divinity masters. They were far more formidable than humanity in terms of overall strength. In a crucial moment that involved the life or death of the entire human race, who among them would dare to draw some conclusion based on some random information?

Divine Dream shook her head, “Nothing. Lin Ming only gave some suggestions.”

Divine Dream was being specifically ambiguous in her wording; she clearly didn’t want to reveal too many details. This was to protect Lin Ming’s secret. The less people knew, the better it would be for him.

Skyrend Godlord hesitated for a moment and finally didn’t ask again. He knew that Divine Dream didn’t wish to explain herself.

Like this, the negotiations that involved the survival of humanity had ended. Following this, the saint race didn’t act out in shame and rage, nor did they begin a large scale invasion of the Divine Realm. Rather, they stayed in the Bright Luster Great World.

Humanity also didn’t send out Empyreans to retake the Bright Luster Great World. This was the best result possible. They didn’t cede further territory, they didn’t pay any compensation, and they also didn’t lose sovereignty of the Divine Realm. In this situation, humanity even gained a moment of peace.

Empyrean Divine Dream was aware that the saint race dreaded humanity right now. But, if humanity were to force them to desperation, they would truly engage in a war where both sides perished. This was something that neither the humans nor the saints wished to see.

Thus, no Empyreans could be sent out in this war. Battles would be limited to the World King level.

Like this, a brief lull of peace appeared between humanity and the saint race. The Bright Luster Great World was temporarily occupied by the saints. For now, every human in the Divine Realm was cheering, cheering for the magnificence of the many Empyreans.

And at this time, news of Lin Ming challenging the saint race’s Good Fortune Saint Son also spread out, traveling through the entire Divine Realm like a tide.

In contrast to what the Empyreans thought, most human martial artists thought that Lin Ming challenging the Good Fortune Saint Son was an extremely grandiose and wonderful feat!

After humanity was forced back again and again, suffering the sorrow of repeated losses, they sorely needed a hero to appear, a figure they could use to encourage themselves. They needed a hearty and vigorous battle with their enemy, one that could give them the courage to continue resisting the saints!

And Lin Ming jumping ranks to challenge the Good Fortune Saint Son had undoubtedly accomplished this. This caused many human martial artists to feel proud and joyous!

Even the common mortals of the Divine Realm vividly painted a scene of Lin Ming challenging the Good Fortune Saint Son at the negotiation table. Of course, this all came from their imaginations.

In their imaginations, Lin Ming appeared like a hero from the dark skies, suppressing everyone present and overwhelming the world!

But, the reaction in the saint race was the complete opposite. They heard stories where Lin Ming was casually struck by the Good Fortune Saint Son to the point of vomiting blood. As for the duel between the Good Fortune Saint Son and Lin Ming in a hundred years, everyone took that as a joke.

As their future Saint Sovereign, how could he possibly be defeated by a little Divine Transformation realm boy?

Chapter 1407 – Enlightenment Beneath the Bodhi Tree

“Grandmaster Yuanji, born 2.61 billion years after the great calamity and died 2.7 billion years afterwards. He had an Empyrean realm cultivation and was an abbot of Mount Potala…”

Lin Ming quietly read the inscription on a stone tablet before perceiving the Buddhist scriptures upon it. A day later, when he came out from this Irreproachable Stupa, he discovered that this was already the last one.

Lin Ming didn’t know how long he stayed in this forest of pagodas. After he left, he felt that his divine sense had reached an unprecedented state of purity, filled with wisdom.

As he stared within this forest of pagodas for days and nights, he experienced the samsara of many lives, gaining insight into life.

“Mm… this is…”

As Lin Ming left the forest of pagodas, the surrounding scene had undergone some strange and inexplicable change.

Within the 72 Irreproachable Stupas was a pure land of ultimate bliss.

This was an extremely beautiful land. Spirit springs trickled through brooks and flowers and plants bloomed everywhere. Walking here, one seemed to arrive in a paradise of heaven.

In the skies, flower petals danced in the air, filling the world with auspicious bursts of shimmering colors.

And in the center of this paradise was a unique spirit tree.

There were many spirit trees in this utopia, but this tree was special; it immediately attracted Lin Ming’s eyes.

It wasn’t too thick nor was it too tall. It was only 40-50 feet high.

But, the trunk of the tree was like a powerful and vibrant divine dragon that grasped its claws deep into the earth.

This tree trunk was ancient. The bark was cracked and the hollow of the tree seemed to have experienced endless years before growing into such an appearance.

On the crown of this tree, most leaves were already faded away, leaving only several hundred still hanging on the branches. Although they were scattered, these hundreds of leaves were still luscious green, glistening with a healthy light like they were carved from jade.

Standing in front of this ancient divine tree, Lin Ming could feel an inexplicable peace amidst a deep and ancient aura.

Lin Ming felt something stir in his mind. He walked underneath this tree and carefully sat down. At this moment, he could inexplicably feel the aura of Buddhism envelop him.

Looking up, every green leaf danced around like a little fairy. Lines ran all over the trunk, containing the infinite charm of the Great Dao. Lin Ming didn’t doubt that even if a mortal with an extremely poor perception was to sit under this ancient tree they could also enter an ethereal state and achieve supreme enlightenment.

Bodhi Tree…

The name of this tree flashed through Lin Ming’s mind.

Lin Ming was 15 years old when he first stepped onto the road of martial arts. He entered the Seven Profound Martial House, and the first teacher he had there was a Martial House Instructor, Hong Xi.

Hong Xi had told Lin Ming about a fable he once heard.

In the legends, 3000 years ago in the Sky Spill Continent, there once existed a peerless genius named Emperor Shakya. Emperor Shakya sat underneath a Bodhi Tree for seven days and seven nights, fusing seven different martial intents into one and achieving supreme enlightenment. He had broken through the shackles of martial arts, cultivation and indestructible vajra body before breaking through the void for his martial path and ascending to the Divine Realm.

To the Lin Ming at that time, this legend had only been a legend. Whether it was ascending to the Divine Realm or fusing together seven different martial intents, all of this was simply fanciful stories, impossible matters.

He had even been suspicious of whether this legend was true or false. In the legends, Emperor Shakya had used a mere seven days and seven nights of enlightenment to break through his bottleneck of martial arts, allowing his cultivation to wildly rise by several large boundaries. This was a nearly unbelievable story. It had to be known that in the Sky Spill Continent, when going from Revolving Core to Life Destruction and Life Destruction to Divine Sea, these great bottlenecks could stop a person for thousands of years, or even their entire lifetime. For Emperor Shakya to suddenly jump through several realms of cultivation was simply too exaggerated.

But it was only recently Lin Ming realized that this legend left behind in the past, a mystery of unknown origins, was actually a riddle. The low-key Buddhist Emperor Shakya was in truth an Empyrean of Mount Potala.

Moreover, he was the youngest Empyrean of humanity. He had used a mere 10,000-20,000 years of cultivation to reach the realm of an Empyrean. His future was limitless.

For such a character, jumping past several lower realms and fusing together seven different martial intents was nothing at all.

Moreover, it was said that Emperor Shakya had sent out a billion incarnations to the three thousand worlds to experience a billion lives. Even now, most of these avatars had yet to return.

If Emperor Shakya received all of his avatars, then perhaps his strength would rise to yet another level. At that time, it would be hard to tell just who was weaker or stronger between him and Divine Dream.

Bodhi Tree… seven martial intents fused as one…

Lin Ming sat in meditation. Currently, the martial intents he knew were the samsara martial intent, ethereal martial intent, and Primordius martial intent, the last of which included the Heavenly Demon martial intent, Heavenly Mortal martial intent, and Heavenly God martial intent.

But in fact, even though Lin Ming had closed up for several years in Primordius Heavenly Palace, he still hadn’t been able to fuse together the Heavenly Demon, Heavenly Mortal, and Heavenly God martial intents.

In addition, Empyrean Divine Dream’s divine dream space and Empyrean Divine Seal’s black hole horizon could both be considered martial intents.

If a martial intent had to be explained, it was a Concept of martial arts that came from the martial artist themselves. What it corresponded to were the Laws. Laws originated from the universe and were a martial artist’s understanding of the universe’s rules.

When everything was considered, Lin Ming actually had seven different kinds of martial intents.

But, to completely fuse these seven different kinds of martial intents together was more difficult than climbing to the heavens!

This was because, of his martial intents, five of them were peak transcendent divine mights. In fact, the black hole horizon left behind by Empyrean Divine Seal had likely surpassed the category of a transcendent divine might.

To fuse them together was to endure a thousand sufferings and 10,000 hardships.

As Lin Ming sat beneath the Bodhi Tree, he soon entered a complete ethereal state.

Time passed day by day. Lin Ming remained motionless, like a sculpture in a garden.

Every day, there would be a crystalline leaf that gently fell down from the Bodhi Tree. As it fell onto Lin Ming’s body, it would drip with a verdant green.

Occasionally there would be a Bodhi seed that fell down. These fingernail-sized Bodhi seeds were completely covered with ancient patterns that weaved together into images of Buddha, lifelike and spiritual.

The Bodhi leaves and Bodhi seeds would eventually turn into crystalline motes of light that fused into Lin Ming’s body.

The Buddhist scriptures and Buddhist comprehensions that Lin Ming studied began to slowly swirl within him, fusing with his spiritual sea.

The samsara martial intent that was within Lin Ming’s spiritual sea had faded away. It turned into a pure flow of energy that converged onto the Primordius martial intent. The ethereal martial intent was also the same.

All of these changes were sublimated within Lin Ming’s soul, becoming purely lucid.

Like this, Lin Ming sat beneath the Bodhi Tree for 33 days.

33 days later, Lin Ming’s eyes flashed open.

With an incomparably loud whistling sound, a spear-shaped battle spirit the color of blue jade howled into the air, circling in the air before returning to Lin Ming’s spiritual sea.

As for Lin Ming’s aura, it suddenly exploded outwards like an army of galloping horses!

His strength had greatly increased. The bottleneck of the early Divine Transformation realm had long been shattered by Lin Ming during these last 33 days!

Middle Divine Transformation realm!

Blue soul battle spirit!

As Lin Ming rose up from beneath the Bodhi Tree, he felt as if the entire world was different.

His soul had undergone a nirvana, and his martial intents had been thoroughly smoothed out.

Heavenly Demon, Heavenly Mortal, Heavenly God, these three martial intents had fused into the complete Primordius martial intent. As for the samsara martial intent and ethereal martial intent, they had also fused with it.

It was only the black hole horizon and divine dream space that Lin Ming wasn’t able to fuse together. But even so, his understandings of these two martial intents were much clearer than before.

“Congratulations, Benefactor Lin.”

At this time, an old voice sounded out in Lin Ming’s ears.

Lin Ming perked up and he respectfully bowed. “Junior greets Senior Great Limitless Buddha.”

In this moment, the land of pure utopia began to blur. A form slowly walked in from the edge, becoming gradually clearer.

This old monk with the white eyebrows and large earlobes was Great Limitless Buddha.

“Benefactor Lin, this old monk originally agreed to allow you to stay in the Irreproachable Stupa for seven by seven, 49 days, but Benefactor Lin has been in enlightenment under the Bodhi Tree for 33 days…”

Lin Ming was startled. As he was gaining insights within the Irreproachable Stupa he had entered a completely ethereal condition and had long forgotten about the seven by seven, 49 day deadline that Great Limitless Buddha had set for him.

“My apologies. Because this junior was reading the scriptures, I momentarily lost my wits and forgot the time.”

“No harm. If Benefactor Lin can stay here for such a long time and even see the pure lands of ultimate bliss and meditate beneath the Bodhi Tree, that is your Buddhist faith, and a good deed. Empyrean Divine Dream entrusted this old monk to help temper you and enhance your strength as much as possible, and this old monk can be considered as barely having accomplished that. Of course, this mainly depends on Benefactor Lin’s own ability.”

“I thank Senior.” Lin Ming felt a heartfelt gratefulness. He was extremely lucky. Even though he didn’t have any background at all, he was still able to study the essence of Empyrean Primordius, Empyrean Divine Dream, and Empyrean Divine Seal’s inheritances: the true inheritances of two peak Empyreans and a True Divinity powerhouse.

Now, he had even been able to grasp some insights of Mount Potala, an influence with a 3.6 billion year background.

In the Divine Realm, there were no other Empyrean disciples that were able to experience such things and have such lucky chances.

In addition, Empyrean Divine Dream was willing to support him with any resources at her disposal. Currently, in terms of resources, he was no worse than any top Empyrean disciple.

Lin Ming thanked all of these supreme elders that helped him from the depths of his heart.

“Very well, Benefactor Lin, the battle at the Bright Luster Great World has grown fierce. In order for a genius to grow, it is impossible to seclude yourself forever to cultivate into an Empyrean. You must go to the Bright Luster Great World and walk your own road of martial arts!”

As Great Limitless Buddha spoke, he waved the sleeves of his robe. Lin Ming felt space blur around him, and in the next moment he had appeared at the entrance of Mount Potala.

Thinking about it, since the First Martial Meeting had concluded, eight or nine years had passed in the blink of an eye.

In this long period of time, Lin Ming had experienced only a handful of battles. He had fought several times at Demondawn World and had also been chased down by Tian Mingzi to the Sky Spill Continent.

For the rest of that time, Lin Ming had been closed up in training. He had trained in Divine Dream Heavenly Palace for one year and Primordius Heavenly Palace for four years. After returning to the Divine Realm, he had also cultivated for another three some years.

In this long span of time, Lin Ming had gone from the peak of the middle Divine Sea realm to the middle Divine Transformation realm. That was a full boundary of cultivation that he had overcome.

All of his previous accumulations had exploded out at once.

Lin Ming’s steps moved and he appeared hundreds of miles away. He stepped on space, flying away. In the air, Lin Ming took out the Primordius Heavenly Palace that had been shrunk by hundreds and thousands of times. His figure turned into a beam of light that flew into it. Then, Primordius Heavenly Palace turned into a soaring comet that flew towards the Bright Luster Great World!

During this great calamity, there was a treaty in place which stated that besides the Bright Luster Great World, fighting was off limits in the other 3000 great worlds of the Divine Realm. Even so, Lin Ming intended to be careful. The defenses of Primordius Heavenly Palace were much stronger than those of any ordinary spirit ship.

As for how high profile and glaring Primordius Heavenly Palace was, Lin Ming completely ignored it, not bothering with hiding anymore. In jumping over a boundary and a half to challenge the Good Fortune Saint Son to a duel 100 years from now, his actions could not be any more high profile.

Chapter 1410 – Attack and Defend

Bang!

Blacksalt’s sword smashed atop Hang Chi’s Wheel of Samsara. With a terrifying ringing sound, the Wheel of Samsara violently shook and a crack snaked across its golden surface.

What an absolutely horrifying strength!

“Fires of darkness, shatter!”

At this time, Witchplume’s two wings slashed out and the Dark Golden Crow behind her also rushed forth, the black flames around it turning into a pitch black sea!

Hu – hu – hu –

Flames roiled. At that moment, the Wheel of Samsara seemed to melt. Hang Chi’s forehead began to seep with sweat as his face paled. How could he withstand the attacks of two people by himself?

“All Existence to Void!”

Dragon Fang suddenly opened one of the variation states of the Three Lives Pupils. Nine years ago, Dragon Fang had only been able to use All Existence to Void for a short period of time, but now he was able to freely wield it.

All Existence to Void was an eye technique able to see through all Laws in the world. Before the Three Lives Pupils, all Concepts were seen through!

“The power of space, the power of time, gather unto me!”

Dragon Fang’s raised his hands and energy erupted from his body. From all around him, the power of space and the power of time began to wildly rush towards him. Then, his figure divided into sixteen copies.

16 spatial mirror images!

16 Dragon Fangs slashed out together. Their black sword lights gathered as one, thrusting straight forwards!

That raging sea of black flames was split apart by Dragon Fang’s sword. The sharp and keening sword light pierced straight towards Witchplume’s forehead.

“What!?”

Witchplume was immensely shocked. She never imagined that Dragon Fang’s attack would be so terrifying!

In these 16 sword strikes, each one contained a tenth of the real Dragon Fang’s strength. With 16 swords gathered as one, their might wasn’t as simple as adding them together. In other words, this strike was several times stronger than Dragon Fang’s strongest strike by himself!

Bang!

With a loud ringing sound, Witchplume’s body was sent storming backwards by the Dragon Fang Sword. She cried out in the air and quickly closed her wings to defend against this sword light.

Ca!

The sword light ravaged forwards, causing massive clumps of feathers to rain down from the sky. These were all Witchplume’s feathers.

Dragon Fang’s sword strike had slashed through her two wings, leaving her in a bloody mess! Even the flexible armor that covered her upper body was nearly broken apart!

Damn it all!

Witchplume fell to the ground and staggered backwards. Dragon Fang’s sword has used the Three Lives Pupils to see through her Darkness Laws. When the 16 strikes gathered as one, they were incomparably fierce and dangerous!

His sword strike had severely wounded Witchplume!

“Witchplume, are you alright?!”

Blacksalt supported her with his thin arms.

Witchplume cruelly smiled. She wiped the blood from the corners of her lips, “I’m fine!”

As the human audience members saw that their side had gained the advantage, all of them erupted in a chorus of cheers.

“Dragon Fang! Dragon Fang!”

Many people began shouting out for Dragon Fang. Back during the First Martial Meeting, Dragon Fang was ranked sixth amongst the top six geniuses. But, that had been because when he first participated in the First Martial Meeting finals, he had only just opened the Three Lives Pupils and his strength hadn’t been able to fully develop.

Even so, his potential was astonishing. After entering the Asura Road to adventure, he crawled back from the precipice of death, and now he had grown by a large margin!

“Haha, Dragon Fang is stronger!”

“That’s right, what do those saints think? Dragon Fang was also only ranked sixth in the human First Martial Meeting!”

“Humanity will win! Humanity must win!”

All of the human martial artists were extremely excited. But not too far away, as Imperial Prince Naqi saw this scene, his smirked in contempt. “What a pack of fools, it’s as if they think they will really win! What a stupid race; there isn’t even any meaning in conquering them. However, those two fellows on stage are a bit more troublesome than I had thought.”

In truth, Imperial Prince Naqi didn’t care much for the result of this fight. Witchplume and Blacksalt couldn’t be called the true peak geniuses of the saint race. The true geniuses were the top three ranked martial artists of the saints’ First Martial Meeting.

If Witchplume and Blacksalt lost it wouldn’t matter much to begin with, let alone that it was impossible for them to lose now!

Naqi’s vision fell upon Hang Chi. At this time, Hang Chi was pale and his hands shivered as he grasped his long staff.

When everyone saw Dragon Fang reveal his momentous strike, they actually ignored the real hidden hero – Hang Chi.

If Hang Chi hadn’t used the Wheel of Samsara to block the attacks of two people, then it would have been impossible for Dragon Fang to break apart Witch Plume and Blacksalt’s joint attack on the battlefield and wound Witchplume!

However, for a single person to withstand two attacks, the pressure could be imagined!

Hang Chi had already been severely wounded. There was no way he could repeat what he just did.

“Hang Chi!”

As Dragon Fang saw Hang Chi’s current state, he felt his heart gripped. In that exchange just now, if one had to say how useful they were, Hang Chi was responsible for 60% while Dragon Fang was only responsible for 40%.

“I’m fine!”

Hang Chi took a deep breath, revolving the Diamond Sutra to suppress the roiling blood vitality within him and seal up all the tears in his organs with true essence. After all, he wasn’t a body transformation martial artist. Once his mortal body was injured his combat strength would rapidly plummet.

“Hang Chi!”

“Hang Chi was injured!”

The young elites present were all the most outstanding geniuses amongst their peers, thus they naturally had amazing sight. After their short period of cheering, they then discovered that Hang Chi was in a very poor situation!

“This is bad!”

Everyone felt their heart skip a beat. All those young elites that were cheering immediately quieted down.

In a group battle, defense was the most difficult aspect. Attacks struck one person, but the one defending had to defend against two; they would naturally be in a much more miserable state!

The young human elites all had a grim complexion. If Hang Chi was defeated, how could they continue fighting?

“Hang Chi, don’t bother with defending, let’s attack together.”

Dragon Fang rapidly said to Hang Chi with a true essence sound transmission. He was well aware that it was impossible for Hang Chi to withstand a similar strike.

“That’s impossible. My offensive ability is inferior to my defensive ability. If we give up our current advantage they will inevitably attack us. Even though we will mutually wound each other, we will be in a far worse state than they will be. This is because one of them is a saint and the other is a saint and monster hybrid. Regardless of which one it is, their mortal bodies are extremely formidable and their defensive powers are extraordinary!”

Hang Chi calmly analyzed the situation on the battlefield. For him to attack with Dragon Fang would be the same as suicide.

“Then let me share the pressure with you.” Dragon Fang said.

“No need. You do not excel in defense. If a sword were to become a shield, the effect could be imagined. I can probably withstand another attack like that again. You must seize this chance to attack and settle this match in the next strike!”

As Hang Chi made this decision, Dragon Fang felt like someone had pulled his heart out. He was afraid that something would happen to Hang Chi.

In this duel, although there were elders from both the saints and humans present, that didn’t mean that one side wouldn’t lose their lives. If both sides were to attack with all of their strength, then a consequence was possible death at any moment!

“Don’t worry, I know what I’m doing.” Hang Chi seemed to sense what Dragon Fang was fearing. “Whether it is me or them, none of us will die here, otherwise that will be too stupid. For the true great calamity a thousand years from now, for my Buddhist path, for my road of martial arts, I won’t give up my life here.”

“Good!” Dragon Fang grit his teeth and grasped the Dragon Fang Blade.

At this time, Blacksalt and Witchplume stood up, their light and heavy swords pointed towards Hang Chi and Dragon Fang.

“You’re not bad! To think you can actually wound me. But, too bad for you, there will be no next time! Now go die!”

At this moment, Blacksalt’s body emitted a series of explosive crackling sounds. His four thin limbs, his chest, his stomach, his entire body began to inflate, filling up with thick muscles! His face became wild and fierce and his spine grew from both ends, forming a spike that pierced through his flesh and grew into a vicious tail and a long horn on his head and even many long bone spikes coming out from his back.

His arms became thick and long, turning into sharp claws. His legs became thick and robust. With a single step forwards, the ground shattered beneath him.

“This is…” Many human martial artists were shocked.

“Haha, this is our saints’ body metamorphosis! Some extreme clans within my saint race possess the ability to metamorphosize!”

Among the watching martial artists, a young saint elite began to proudly speak.

“Lord Blacksalt possesses an ancient saint bloodline. After metamorphosing, his body gains a wild and terrible strength!”

The saint race had different metamorphic abilities depending on the various bloodlines they had inherited. They were originally the race with the most powerful mortal body. After metamorphosing their body, they would be able to unlock the latent power deep within themselves and release their ultimate strength.

Of coursing, metamorphosing required a tremendous amount of energy. In the different bloodlines, some metamorphic forms had different strengths, consumed different amounts of energy, and lasted for different durations.

Bang!

Blacksalt’s four limbs smashed into the ground. He bit onto his heavy sword and bolted forwards, like an ancient dinosaur. His body had been magnified by several times, and the thin Witchplume was actually riding on his back.

Witchplume grasped her sword, her two wings blazing with burning black flames.

The combination of a woman and a wild beast hurtled towards Dragon Fang and Hang Chi. Wherever they went, rock cracked open. With every step they took, the entire Ash Blood Mountain seemed to vibrate.

Dragon Fang’s complexion changed. This momentum was far too terrifying!

“Hang Chi! You…”

Before he could speak further, Hang Chi had already stepped forwards to bear the impact of Blacksalt and Witchplume’s attack!

“Samsara domain, Eight Sectioned Stupa!”

With an explosive ringing sound, a giant eight-story pagoda fell down from the skies. This divine pagoda was filled with the aura of the great dao. Each level held a divine being, bursting with divine light!

By using the Eight Sectioned Stupa to suppress the void, when this was combined with the Wheel of Samsara, it formed a divine domain like an iron fortress!

Hang Chi’s complexion was cold as he calmly faced Blacksalt and Witchplume’s all-out attack.

As Dragon Fang saw Hang Chi fearlessly face the combined attack of the two saint geniuses, Dragon Fang felt that something had been touched within his heart. This battle was no longer just a battle between them and the saint race geniuses.

This was a contest between the humans and the saints. In these strange and perilous times, any battle between the saints and humans could increase the morale of either side, helping their chances of victory. This was extremely valuable.

How could they lose here!?

“Eyes of Myriad Blood!”

Dragon Fang’s entire body erupted with energy. His eyes turned blood red; he had opened the third state of the Three Lives Pupils – Eyes of Myriad Blood!

With Dragon Fang’s current strength, wanting to open the Eyes of Myriad Blood was incomparably difficult. However, his only path left was to desperately risk everything on this!

Chi chi chi!

Dragon Fang’s eyes were dyed with blood. Because a massive influx of energy poured into his eyes, the blood vessels in his eyes continuously broke apart, causing tears of blood to roll down his face. He grit his teeth, grasped the Dragon Fang Blade, and then split into 32 forms.

32 spatial mirror images!

By using Eyes of Myriad Blood and forming 32 spatial mirror images, this was Dragon Fang’s ultimate attack!

“Void Extermination!”

32 Dragon Fangs slashed out together. Their brilliant sword lights wove together, shooting outwards!

Chapter 1411 – Lin Ming Arrives

Ca!

The space of the Divine Realm was torn to pieces by this sword light! Poured into this sword strike was Dragon Fang’s complete strength; the limit of his potential!

At this time, Blacksalt and Witchplume had already jumped high into the skies. The blazing black flames and the wild beast that was the body metamorphosized Blacksalt had fused into one, forming a horrific black meteor!

Bang!

With a terrifying explosion, the center area of Ash Blood Mountain was hollowed out!

The Wheel of Samsara and the Eight Sectioned Stupa completely collapsed. Hang Chi spat out a great mouthful of blood. At this crucial moment, he grit his teeth together and smashed his staff into the ground.

Diamond Vajra Sutra!

The moment Hang Chi reached the limit of his physical body, he completely ignored all damage to his meridians and organs to forcefully revolve the Diamond Vajra Sutra and continue resisting.

“Be defeated!”

Dragon Fang howled out into the skies. His eye sockets were dripping with blood as the Dragon Fang Blade in his hand cried out with a keening wail! The black sea of flames was torn asunder by this sword light, cutting straight towards Witchplume’s forehead. Dragon Fang wanted to use this strike to tear through Blacksalt and Witchplume together!

And at this moment, Witchplume took a sudden step backwards. The bone spikes atop Blacksalt’s back rapidly grew forwards like sharp swords, thrusting outwards!

Kacha!

The spikes crashed into the sword light. Three spikes exploded into bits but the weakened sword light still fell down in a wild and raging torrent.

Blacksalt growled. Together with Witchplume, they revolved their astral essence to the limit, resisting this sword strike head on!

Rumble rumble rumble!

Massive chunks of red rock tumbled down. The entire Ash Blood Mountain seemed to melt away like a glacier, completely collapsing!

Even though the surrounding young martial artists were all outstanding elites amongst all elites, they were still thrown away by the maddening waves of energy!

The reason that Ash Blood Mountain was chosen as the battlefield for this fight was because this area was special and the rock was as hard as divine steel. Even so, the terrain still couldn’t withstand this terrifying strength.

The young human elites all paled, their faces changing. How could the fifth and sixth placed martial artists of the saint race’s First Martial Meeting be so fierce!?

What was the result?

As everyone looked towards the center of the battlefield, they only saw Dragon Fang kneeling on the ground, barely hanging on with the support of the Dragon Fang Blade. His eyes were blood red, with blood continuing to drip down.

And not too far behind him, Hang Chi’s protective true essence had completely shattered. He had propped himself up with his staff, standing tall. Behind him, the faint phantom of a golden Buddha was still wavering about. Still, the current Hang Chi’s meridians were a completely jumbled mess and his organs were damaged in several areas; it was impossibly difficult for him to continue standing.

“Dragon Fang! Hang Chi!”

The human martial artists all tensed. And at this time, with a loud crashing sound at the distant ruined rocks, massive stones tumbled down and a bloodsoaked Blacksalt shot out from the wreckage like a wild beast, landing on the ground on all fours. The three longest bone spikes on his back had broken and a horrifying sword wound crossed down his back, stretching from his neck to his tail.

This sword wound was as deep as a ruler and had nearly cut his spine in half. This final sword strike had been caught and rigidly stopped by his powerful mortal body and bones. If it weren’t for him having used his body metamorphosis, this sword strike would have cleaved him in two.

Behind him, a pale Witchplume also rose up from the ruins. The flexible armor all over her body had broken and she used her black flames to form a new set of flexible armor around her. Blacksalt had withstood 60-70% of Dragon Fang’s final attack and she had withstood 30-40% of it. Even though that was so, she had been deeply wounded. Dragon Fang’s attack was far too swift and violent but Blacksalt had still managed to use his mortal body to withstand it. It could only be said that the defensive capabilities of Blacksalt’s mortal body had reached a freakish level.

As Naqi saw this, he smiled. He knew that this fight was over.

Even though the humans and the saints had both received similar levels of injuries, that only meant that the inevitable winners were the saints. This was because the saints’ ability to resist attacks and also regenerate their bodies was far more powerful than the humans’.

In the current situation, Hang Chi’s wounds were the heaviest. Although Dragon Fang hadn’t been wounded, he had still deeply overdrawn his strength. Over half his true essence was used up and his combat efficiency had plummeted to rock bottom.

As Blacksalt emerged from the ruins, he roared. With a slimy wriggling sound, the flesh and blood on his back twisted together, with even new bones growing.

The sound of this flesh and blood wriggling about was clear and loud. Blacksalt was actually regenerating himself! This sort of regenerative ability was appalling!

Blacksalt had withstood Dragon Fang’s sword strike and was still able to restore a portion of his combat strength in a short period of time. The saints were a completely beast-like race; their bodies were too abnormal.

The surrounding human martial artists felt a chill crawl down their spines. In their days here, they had fought with and also slaughtered many saint race martial artists. But, they had never encountered a savage and freakish genius of the saints that was able to undergo bloodline metamorphosis, such as this Blacksalt in front of them. This Blacksalt was more than just a bit stronger than an ordinary saint!

“Hahahaha! My saint race is truly superior to the human race!”

“Stupid humans, what else can the likes of you still say?”

Many saint martial artists shouted out loud. Their stiff and halting Divine Realm language was especially grating to the ears.

Among the humans, some martial artists argued back and some were silent.

They thought of the true elites of the saint race: they likely all had a physique like Blacksalt. This thought left a thick despair surging in their hearts. Could humanity truly overcome this great calamity? If they were defeated then all of humanity would devolve into nothing but slaves.

Was this era truly the time when humanity would perish?

At this time, with the sound of flapping clothes rustling in the wind, a white-robed monk flew into the center of the battlefield. He waved his robes and a Buddhist light wrapped around Hang Chi. This white-robed monk had an ordinary World King realm cultivation.

“High Master, I have shamed the name of Mount Potala…” Hang Chi bitterly smiled.

The white-robed monk sighed, shaking his head as he said, “Apprentice Nephew, you must not be too harsh on yourself. If anyone should be ashamed, it should be us. You did not lose to him in strength or talent, but lost to him in background. You relied on your Empyrean Holy Land background to struggle with a genius from a True Divinity Holy Land to this degree, and for that High Master is more than proud of you. If Mount Potala were also a True Divinity level Holy Land, then we could allow your strength to reach even greater steps. Even if it were just half a step further, this battle would have had a different result.”

As this white-robed monk spoke, he brought Hang Chi with him and flew away.

The third and sixth placed martial artists of the human First Martial Meeting had fought against the fifth and sixth placed martial artists of the saint First Martial Meeting, and the final result was… humanity had been defeated!

Although the saints had won with difficulty, a loss was loss.

“We’ve lost…”

The human martial artists were all silent. They felt a heavy pressure on their hearts.

“They both wounded each other, but we lost to the saint race’s endurance and regenerative ability…”

“Although I don’t want to admit it, the saints are truly stronger than us. They have greater numbers and their inheritances are also better.”

“3.6 billion years ago, humanity had to pay a deep price in order to ensure the survival of our race, the Empyreans nearly died out and 80-90% of our martial arts civilization was destroyed. As for the saints, they were nearly untouched. They still had many large sects that continued to pass their legacy on and there are many saint sects that have a background of 4-5 billion years! Moreover, they even have the support of a True Divinity Holy Land…”

The inheritances and resources of a True Divinity Holy Land far surpassed those of an Empyrean Holy Land, so they were able to raise even more extraordinary geniuses and also had an easier time training Empyreans.

“Hahaha, if any of you still aren’t convinced, then you can come up and fight me!”

Blacksalt’s entire body was covered with wounds but he still gave off such a dreadful momentum!

“To all those young human elites that wish to fight, I alone am more than enough! Pass a message out and inform Lin Ming and Frost Dream to come to the Bright Luster Great World to look for me! There is no need for Senior-apprentice Brother Naqi to do anything, I will defeat them both myself! Especially that fool Lin Ming, the thought that he wishes to challenge my saint race’s Good Fortune Saint Son, my Senior-apprentice Brother Wumo, is just laughable!”

Blacksalt’s body slowly shrank before he turned back into a dark and thin youth.

Who had thought that such a thin body was able to contain that horrifying explosive power!

However Blacksalt shouted, no one came to accept his challenge.

It was impossible for Divine Sea realm geniuses to fight Blacksalt; that was just asking to die.

As for Divine Transformation realm martial artists, Hang Chi and Dragon Fang represented the strongest ones here. After the two of them, everyone else was a level lower. Even if they were to face the extremely wounded Blacksalt, they still wouldn’t be a match.

“The human race has no one? Hahaha!” Blacksalt chortled. “I will wait here for seven days. In these seven days, any young human martial artist can challenge me. I want to fight the entire Bright Luster Great World!”

Blacksalt fused his voice with astral essence, spreading it over everyone present.

“This fellow is too arrogant!”

As the human martial artists heard Blacksalt’s shout, they were all filled with an indignant anger.

“Just who does he think he is!?”

“I really want to defeat him! If I could defeat him, I would be willing to trade that for 60-70% of my lifespan!”

The human martial artists all suppressed a fire in their bellies. Even though Blacksalt was shouting so arrogantly, none of them were able to defeat him.

Blacksalt was true to his words. He really did wait atop Ash Blood Mountain for other young human martial artists to challenge him.

On the first day, no one accepted his challenge. On the second day, several human martial artists stepped into the arena. Even though they knew who they were fighting, they still couldn’t swallow this insult. There were many human martial artists that were brave and daring. They didn’t seek victory, but only wished to punch Blacksalt with their fist or at least slash him with their sword.

The results were as expected. The several martial artists that challenged Blacksalt were all beaten to a pulp, their skeletons and meridians shattered. If it weren’t for the human World Kings saving them, they would have been killed by Blacksalt. Even so, these degrees of injuries were enough to have them recuperating in bed for half a year.

Blacksalt laughed out loud. He spoke once more, telling none of the human trash to come. If they didn’t even possess the qualifications to have him stretch out his bones, then what was the point?

In these days, the saint martial artists had already laid down spirit artifact cave dwellings and mansions. The saint martial artists gathered here, joyfully celebrating, eating big pieces of meat as they drank their fill. This was the scene of a celebration feast.

As heroes of the saint race, Blacksalt and Witchplume received many invitations. For a time, the morale of the saints reached the extreme.

No one knew that on the third day after Blacksalt arrived on the Chaotic Blood Continent, a common-looking palace broke through the void and also arrived.

In these days, countless people had come to the Chaotic Blood Continent. This caused the palace to arouse no one’s attention.

“This is the Chaotic Blood Continent, hm, I wonder just where the duel is happening?”

Lin Ming thought to himself. But, he soon discovered that finding their location was extremely easy. The most powerful martial artists on the Chaotic Blood Continent had all gathered in a single place. Their vivid blood vitality and powerful true essence gathered into a force that shot up into the sky, forming an invisible fountain that erupted into the heavens.

“Looks like it’s over there.” Lin Ming faintly smiled. “It hasn’t finished either; we’ve made it in time.”

Deep within the Magic Cube space, Mo Eversnow nodded. “Mm, the Chaotic Blood Continent is extremely far, placed in the deepest parts of the Bright Luster Great World. Luckily for us, Primordius Heavenly Palace is extremely fast and we’ve made it here in three days. Let’s go and see what’s happening over there.”

Chapter 1413 – Horrifying Weight

As the human and saint martial artists saw Lin Ming and Blacksalt about to start a brutal battle, they both began to crazily shout out.

“Blacksalt! Tear that brat to shreds!”

“Kill him! Ruin him!”

Blacksalt was a top ranked core disciple of a True Divinity Holy Land. His reputation was extremely high.

“Lin Ming, your human body transformation technique simply isn’t a top body transformation technique. It is something that belongs to the dregs of the Concept of the 33 Layered Heavens. Let me show you what the true difference is between our body transformation techniques!”

The Concept of the 33 Layered Heavens were divided into three great categories of essence, energy, and divine. Each category was divided into 11 variations.

Solely the body transformation technique had 11 different methods to practice it. There were those that suited humanity, saints, and there were some variations that suited the monsters and spiritas.

In Blacksalt’s opinion, only the saints’ body transformation technique had the greatest foundation and was also the strongest variation of the body transformation technique.

Blacksalt roared out and wildly hurtled towards Lin Ming! He understood that Lin Ming was extremely strong, but he still had absolute confidence in himself. He wanted to use this battle to become renowned through the universe! If he could challenge the entire human race without being defeated, then he would be a hero of the saints and obtain enormous rewards. Moreover, the more battles he won, the more confidence he would gain and the greater help this would be to his future growth.

Facing Blacksalt’s menacing charge, Lin Ming’s eyes flashed with a vicious light. He grasped the Phoenix Blood Spear and opened all of the Eight Inner Hidden Gates!

With a loud explosive sound, a terrifying shockwave erupted from Lin Ming. The rocks beneath his feet began to crack apart like an expanding spider web!

Lin Ming’s body transformation technique had already touched upon the threshold of the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace. In addition, when Lin Ming had entered Primordius Heavenly Palace, he had directed grandmist energy to enter his body. Using the grandmist energy that was as heavy as a star, he had tempered his own skeleton and muscles, withstanding pain that an ordinary man would not be able to bear.

Empyrean Primordius had sealed a massive amount of grandmist energy within the Primordius Gate. That was no longer elementary grandmist energy, but true grandmist energy!

The intensity of Lin Ming’s mortal body had reached unbelievable degrees.

Without using any true essence, without using any Laws, and by only relying on the mortal strength of his body as well as his astral essence, he welcomed the rampaging Blacksalt!

“Eight Inner Hidden Gates – Hundred Layered Waves!”

Lin Ming shouted out loud, pouring all of his strength into the Phoenix Blood Spear. Lin Ming’s strength had nearly reached a billion jins. Now, as he used the Hundred Layered Waves, it was like an infinitely high tide, smashing through the world!

“Mm!? Lin Ming wants to use his body transformation technique to deal with Blacksalt?”

“The body transformation technique isn’t a domain that humans excel in. Even if Lin Ming dual cultivates in body and energy, his methods aren’t extraordinary. What he excels in the most is the essence gathering system!”

The human martial artists cried out in alarm. As for the saint race martial artists, they repeatedly jeered out loud, waiting for Lin Ming to be sent flying back by Blacksalt.

“You are seeking death!”

Blacksalt roared out and three bone spikes on his back stabbed forwards like a sharp trident. With the support of his bodily strength, astral essence exploded outwards!

In that moment, Lin Ming instantly struck out with a hundred spears. These hundred spears fused together as one, violently crashing into Blacksalt.

Kacha!

A terrifying explosion followed as massive chunks of rock burst into powder. Lin Ming was sent flying backwards and Blacksalt’s form shook. Blacksalt’s barrier of astral essence had shattered, but because of his powerful mortal body, those shockwaves of spear light had been completely withstood by him without any injuries at all.

As for Lin Ming, he was sent flying hundreds of feet backwards by Blacksalt. Although he wasn’t injured, it was still Blacksalt who gained the advantage in this collision.

Even so, Blacksalt couldn’t accept this result. This was because Lin Ming hadn’t used any true essence at all!

“This boy, how could his body transformation technique be so fierce? Then just what degree has his essence gathering system reached?”

“Blacksalt, ruin that boy, wreck him into pieces!” The surrounding saints began to wildly shout out. Blacksalt sending Lin Ming flying back in that strike just now had caused their morale to rapidly rise, shaking like an earthquake.

Weng!

Blacksalt’s body rushed out once more. On his claws, a divine fire seemed to burn. As he slashed out with his claws, the void seemed to shake. It was hard to imagine how powerful this attack was.

Lin Ming flourished the Phoenix Blood Spear, watching Blacksalt hurtle towards him. When he had used the Celestial Tyrant Manual’s Hundred Layered Waves just now to attack Blacksalt, the result was that he hadn’t been able to take the advantage. Blacksalt was a martial artist that specialized in the body transformation technique. If Lin Ming had defeated him there, then his many years of cultivating the body transformation technique would have been nothing but a waste.

However, Lin Ming’s body transformation technique wasn’t as simple as just the Eight Inner Hidden Gates!

“Emerge, grandmist energy!”

A keen light flashed in Lin Ming’s eyes. A wisp of grandmist energy left his inner world, covering Lin Ming’s arms and the Phoenix Blood Spear.

A little bit of grandmist energy was as heavy as a star. With a wisp of grandmist energy attached to Lin Ming’s spear, a single strike was like wielding a thousand mile mountain range!

“You boast that your body transformation is unrivalled, but let me see whether you can withstand the weight of my spear!”

Lin Ming opened the Eight Inner Hidden Gates once more. The Phoenix Blood Spear swept out, crashing down like a blood red divine mountain range!

Blacksalt’s claws smashed together with Lin Ming’s Phoenix Blood Spear.

Kacha!

With a deafening explosion, Blacksalt’s body shook. His protective astral essence shattered beneath the Phoenix Blood Spear as if it were nothing but glass!

“What!?”

Blacksalt was aghast. He knew how durable his protective astral essence was, and yet it had been so easily broken by Lin Ming’s casual spear strike!?

At this time, Lin Ming’s second spear strike came crashing down.

Blacksalt’s complexion changed. He wanted to avoid it, but at this moment a boundless and ancient power enveloped him, surrounding the entire void within a range of a thousand feet. Blacksalt’s movements immediately slowed!

Grandmist space!

“This is bad!”

The speed that Blacksalt was so proud of was bound by the grandmist space. He grit his teeth, erupting his astral essence to the limit as he used the spikes on his back to resist Lin Ming’s attack.

Lin Ming sneered and brought his two arms crashing down. The Phoenix Blood Spear smashed into Blacksalt’s back. This strike directly broke through Blacksalt’s three bone spikes and the Phoenix Blood Spear continued unabated, pounding into him and causing his back to burst apart in a bloody mess before he was sent flying away!

Blacksalt miserably screamed out. He plummeted downwards like a meteor.

Bang!

With a ringing sound, Blacksalt crashed into the ground, sending countless chunks of rock flying up. He was like a comet that crashed into the earth!

“Blacksalt!”

This sudden turn in the tables had surpassed everyone’s expectations. The saint race martial artists all cried out in horror. At this time, Blacksalt emerged from the rubble. The saint race martial artists had an incomparably horrifying defensive power. Even though Blacksalt had received such heavy wounds, he was still able to forcefully bear it.

Blacksalt’s body was covered in blood. His skin and flesh had cracked open. As he looked up to the sky, he found that Lin Ming had disappeared.

Before he could respond, an extremely dreadful weight pressed down on his back.

This strength was as heavy as 10 million mountains. Not even Blacksalt could withstand it.

He miserably coughed, his four limbs shaking.

“You…!”

Blacksalt’s eyes turned blood red. Lin Ming was clearly riding atop Blacksalt’s back. The current metamorphosed Blacksalt was similar in shape to a large tiger. As Lin Ming rode atop his back, it was similar to a man riding his mount.

To Blacksalt this was the ultimate humiliation. As a proud martial artist of the saints, just how arrogant was he? How could he allow a human to ride atop his back?

Blacksalt angrily roared out. He wanted to jump up and throw off Lin Ming, but at this time, Lin Ming fused his grandmist energy onto the Phoenix Blood Spear and brought it pounding down!

Peng!

The Phoenix Blood Spear’s shaft solidly smacked onto Blacksalt’s back. Blacksalt’s ruined back exploded once more. With the terrifying weight still pressing down on him, his body shook and he spat out a mouthful of blood. His knees weakened and he was forced to the ground.

Rocks constantly crumbled beneath them. Underneath this weight, Blacksalt was forced to the ground!

“This… what is going on here?”

“He’s riding on Blacksalt’s back! Some terrifying weight has forced Blacksalt to his knees. It’s impossible for him to do anything, let alone throw off Lin Ming!”

The situation had rapidly reversed. At the start, Blacksalt had won a minor advantage when he sent Lin Ming flying back a few hundred feet. But after that, it was Lin Ming who had beaten down Blacksalt!

Lin Ming grasped the Phoenix Blood Spear and pointed it at Blacksalt’s back. If it weren’t for the barrier of grandmist space, Blacksalt would have already been buried in the ground. Now, he was unable to stand up no matter how much he wanted to. He vomited out great gulps of blood, dying the earth red.

With a human standing on his back and forcing him down with his spear, Blacksalt found this humiliation unbearable. He struggled as hard as he could, but no matter how much he tried, nothing worked.

“Damn! Damn it all!”

Blacksalt had never felt so helpless in his life. He had always been proud of his mortal body, but this current feeling was like squatting on the ground with someone pushing him down with just a single finger, making him unable to stand up.

Many saint martial artists were bewildered. None of them understood just what sort of mysteries were on Lin Ming’s Phoenix Blood Spear and why Blacksalt was pressed down so hard that he couldn’t stand up.

The human martial artists were also confused. But, this didn’t stop them from cheering for Lin Ming. Ever since the great calamity began and the saint race had invaded, the human race had suffered one defeat after another!

The only incident that was able to show the strength of humanity had been the negotiations of Mount Potala and Empyrean Divine Dream completely refusing all of the saint race’s treaty conditions. At the same time, Lin Ming had also jumped a boundary and a half to challenge the Good Fortune Saint Son to a life or death battle in a hundred years. However, when this matter was put in pleasant terms then Lin Ming had courage to face this challenge. But, if it was put in coarser terms then Lin Ming was simply a fool who had bitten off more than he could chew.

In these past days, the humans had been oppressed and mocked by the saints again and again. They desperately needed a victory to boost their morale and confidence!

“Lin Ming! Lin Ming!”

“Make him so that he can’t step ever again!”

The human martial artists all shouted out, releasing all the pressure in their hearts.

And at this time, an indifferent voice sounded out.

“Enough!”

This voice seemed to come from the icy cold nine nether abyss, causing the heated battlefield audience to quiet down.

The young human elites felt their hearts skip a beat as a chill filled the air.

Lin Ming’s mind stirred. He received the Phoenix Blood Spear and looked up at the void.

There, space distorted and a thin, white-clothed youth appeared. His face wasn’t too handsome, but his aura was swift and fierce. He was pale like jade and his eyes were sharp. His entire body exuded an evil atmosphere.

Chapter 1415 – Fighting the Imperial Prince

Strong winds howled. Within the grim and desolate ruins atop Ash Blood Mountain, Naqi’s long hair chaotically whipped about, his clothes flapping around him.

His eyes were as sharp as lightning. His left hand was held behind his back and his right hand grasped a spear. The pitch black nine foot long spear slowly extended outwards as he pointed the tip towards the ground, a cold light sparkling atop it. As this image was joined together with his straight figure, Naqi was like a tall and steady pine tree.

Above the heavens, below the earth, only he was worthy!

Just this aura alone made one subconsciously fall into a submissive state of awe. Just by standing in front of him, one could feel a tremendous pressure, pushing them to the limit.

This was the aura of a future sovereign!

This aura was the superior momentum that Naqi had accumulated over an extremely long period of time. By constantly defeating geniuses at the same level, his confidence had risen again and again. When combined with his terrifying strength, this aura was the manifestation of his being!

“This Naqi is truly extraordinary!”

“There will inevitably be a role for him on the stage of the future great calamity. He might even become one of the leading main characters!”

Even though the human martial artists couldn’t bear Naqi and wanted to bite a chunk out of him, they couldn’t help but acknowledge just how horrifying he was.

This sort of person was a dragon in a pool. As the true war of the great calamity arrived, he would constantly change, evolving until he soared to the heavens.

Facing such a Naqi, Lin Ming’s complexion was cold. He held the Phoenix Blood Spear in one hand, extending it out. The 10 foot Phoenix Blood Spear looked as if it was cast in iron, immovable.

“How amusing!”

Naqi smiled. But suddenly, a cold light burst out from his eyes and the rocks beneath his feet exploded.

Bang!

As the air trembled around him, Naqi made his move!

His speed reached an unimaginable level. The inky black spear was like a bolt of black lightning, thrusting torwards Lin Ming’s throat like a kiss from a death god!

This sudden attack had caught everyone unprepared. This attack had reached the extremes of speed and power; even a peak Divine Lord powerhouse would have been instantly defeated beneath this spear strike without any ability to resist.

In that moment, Lin Ming also moved. His sense locked onto Naqi’s body. From the very instant that astral essence erupted from Naqi’s body, Lin Ming had been prepared.

The Phoenix Blood Spear thrust out. The immense power of thunder and fire that had been saved within the Heretical God Tree burst out, fiercely colliding in the sky.

Bang!

It was like bolts of divine thunder crashed into the ground. Countless crushed stones were raised up and then swept into the sky by a wild vortex of energy. The earth shivered and divine light spilled out in all directions. In the dark skies, a round sun seemed to appear.

Luckily, everyone was already prepared and wasn’t too close to the battlefield. The older martial artists had laid down protective enchantments in front of the juniors, but even then, those protective enchantments were wildly struck by the waves of energy, nearly exploding.

Hu – !

The blinding explosion of thunder and fire continued for several breaths of time before slowly fading away. The skies were filled with immense amounts of rock that had been reduced to sand by the horrifying energy. The rocky sand was lifted up into the skies by the wind, turning the entire Ash Blood Mountain battlefield into a dusky world.

“How terrifying!”

“To think this is a battle between a middle Divine Transformation youth and a late Saint Transformation youth. It’s hard to imagine this is possible… even a battle between Holy Lords can’t compare!”

“This Imperial Prince Naqi and Lin Ming are both geniuses born unto the world of the great calamity. One was born in the saints and one was born in humanity. In a hundred million years, their strength will reach levels that cannot be comprehended by common sense!”

“This will be a fight between dragons and tigers; just who will emerge victorious?”

The human martial artists were originally lacking in confidence, but as they saw Lin Ming’s aura rise like a beam of light, a faint spark of hope ignited in their hearts. If Lin Ming, as the second ranked martial artist of the human First Martial Meeting, could defeat the first place champion of the saint First Martial Meeting, then humanity would truly be lifted up in pride and happiness. Otherwise, they would be cast down. Everyone knew that although Lin Ming had come second, the truth was that he was nearly equal to Frost Dream. No one could tell who was weaker or stronger between the two.

If Lin Ming lost here, that would be equal to all the young elites of humanity losing!

“You can actually receive my probing strike so easily. You indeed possess the qualifications to be my opponent!” As Naqi spoke, his eyes sparkled.

The surrounding martial artists were left speechless. Such a sharp and vicious attack was only a probing strike – this was too ridiculous.

Naqi strode forwards, one step at a time. As he did, flames seemed to burn atop his body. These were not true flames. Rather, because the astral essence within his body was too powerful, it had reached the level of substantializing, thus it appeared as flames around him.

1000 feet, 900 feet, 800 feet…

Like this, Naqi approached Lin Ming, coming closer and closer. The saints’ body transformation excelled in close combat. As for the humans’ essence gathering, that excelled in long distance combat. In these past days, when human martial artists had fought in missions throughout the Bright Luster Great World, the most basic knowledge they learnt was that they could not allow the saints to approach them and engage in a brutal melee. Otherwise, in a situation where both sides had similar levels of strength, there was a 70% chance that they would die!

“Lin Ming, be careful!”

“Get away!”

Many martial artists anxiously cried out. But Lin Ming simply watched as Naqi approached, motionless.

“Oh? You’ve got guts! Could it be that you think your level of body transformation technique has reached a degree comparable to mine?”

As Naqi spoke, he was only 100 feet away from Lin Ming. For a peak master, this mere 100 feet wouldn’t even take a thousandth of a blink of an eye to cross. This was simply the same as no distance at all.

Ka ka ka!

All of the joints in Lin Ming’s body exploded with loud crackling sounds. He had opened the Eight Inner Hidden Gates to the limit. The strength that was hiding within him was like a volcano that could erupt at any moment!

“How interesting! Haha, then let me see just what worth your body transformation technique has!”

Naqi burst out with a horrendous roar as a blazing divine light covered his entire body. Strange runes began to appear all over his face. His hair grew longer and a pair of sharp fangs extended down from the corners of his mouth just like spikes. His elbows and knees lengthened, growing ferocious bone spikes all over, and gold scales emerged from his skin, covering his entire body.

Just 100 feet away from Lin Ming, Naqi completed his body metamorphosis!

Only a small number of people within the saint race possessed this transformation ability.

Although it couldn’t be said that every saint who could metamorphose their body was more powerful than those that couldn’t, the absolute fact was that the several peak members of the saint race all had this ability!

As Naqi transformed his body, a horrifying energy erupted. Even those human martial artists 10 miles away could feel this dark pressure, much less Lin Ming. If Lin Ming was a mere hundred feet away, the pressure he had to withstand could be imagined! If it were a normal martial artist in his shoes, they would fall to the floor trembling, losing all ability to fight!

Many saints fell to their knees, praying towards Imperial Prince Naqi. Although this was a strange sight to humans, something they couldn’t understand, for the saints this was actually a natural response originating from their inborn instincts. For a people that worshipped a powerful mortal body, this was the awe they felt from encountering such a magnificent specimen!

Naqi’s bloodline was one of the peak bloodlines of the saints. He was worthy of their worship!

Facing this Naqi, Lin Ming simply raised the Phoenix Blood Spear, his eyes as cold as ice.

“How brave! An essence gathering system martial artist is actually able to withstand my pressure at such a close distance! Then, let me see whether you are strong or just plain stupid!”

As Naqi laughed out loud, he grasped his long spear and smashed down at Lin Ming!

The might of this spear strike was titanic, as if a 100,000 foot high mountain had been dropped down from the clouds with infinite momentum! Even the void collapsed under this pressure. With the locking in of the surrounding space, no one within 100 feet could escape Naqi’s spear. As long as this spear came pounding down, even if Lin Ming had opened the complete Eight Inner Hidden Gates he would still be wounded to the brink of death!

Many martial artists cried out in fear, waiting to see Lin Ming be smashed to pieces by Naqi’s spear. But, Naqi’s movements suddenly stiffened, slowing down by a great deal.

“What!?”

In this moment, Naqi felt a vast and boundless aura cover the space within 100 feet. All space within this area became heavy, filled with an incomparably terrifying gravitational force, stifling his every motion. And, lingering atop his spear, a trace of gray energy wandered around. This gray energy was as thin as a strand of spider silk, but his spear actually wasn’t able to cut through it. It had caused his spear to slow down to half its speed!

What Lin Ming used was the grandmist space that contained grandmist energy!

True grandmist space was the fusion of the Heavenly Demon, Heavenly Mortal, and Heavenly God martial intents. Simultaneously, the grandmist space also contained true grandmist energy.

Grandmist energy was as heavy as a star. If these thin strands wove together, they formed a giant spider web, and any martial artist that fell into the grandmist space was like a fly caught in a web of grandmist energy, unable to struggle at all!

A single thin strand of grandmist energy was something that even a World King would find difficult to cut apart. If it were twisted into a web, the hardiness of that grandmist energy could be imagined!

Of course, Lin Ming had yet to reach this degree of proficiency. He had simply used the tiniest strand of grandmist energy, but this tiny strand had still caused a massive hindrance to Naqi’s movements.

In that moment when Naqi’s spear was shackled, Lin Ming also thrust out with his own!

The dazzling spear light reached the extreme. A strike that didn’t ask for force, only speed!

Lin Ming wanted to attack Naqi before he regrouped the astral essence he had used and pierce through his defenses!

Lin Ming could imagine that Naqi’s defensive capabilities were truly terrifying. If Naqi were to stimulate his defensive abilities to their limit then Lin Ming’s only ability that could harm him would be Heavenly Dao Judgment.

But, there was no time to use Heavenly Dao Judgment right now. What Lin Ming needed to do was take the initiative and pierce through Naqi’s body as the saint was attacking with all of his strength. Because of Naqi’s powerful mortal body, it was impossible to win with a single spear strike, but he would still be able to heavily wound him!

“Space and Time Laws!”

As the Phoenix Blood Spear thrust out, the surrounding flow of time slowed down. Only that red spear reached an extreme velocity.

With this extreme speed coupled with Lin Ming’s large success comprehensions of the Space and Time Laws, the potential of this strike was overwhelming!

However, just as his spear reached Naqi’s chest, the space around Naqi seemed to fall into a thick darkness. At the same time, time distorted and space drew back. An invisible strength came shrouding down and the slowed down flow of time around Naqi was reverted to normal.

Puff!

Blood splashed out. Naqi retreated a single step back. Although this only seemed like a simple step backwards, the truth was that he had stepped back a thousand feet!

His hand held onto his bloody chest, blood flowing out from between his fingers. As he looked at Lin Ming, a look of astonishment crossed his face.

Chapter 1416 – Naqi’s Power

Naqi was not surprised by Lin Ming’s use of the Time and Space Laws, but by the degree to which he could utilize the grandmist space. When he had approached Lin Ming, Lin Ming hadn’t taken even half a step backwards. The reason that Lin Ming had dared to allow a body transformation martial artist to come close was not because of his own body transformation technique but because of his grandmist space. The smaller the area of the grandmist space was, the greater its might would be!

In other words, from the very start Lin Ming hadn’t feared close combat at all. When Imperial Prince Naqi had approached him he already had a plan laid out. Lin Ming had waited for the moment that Naqi attacked to launch his own counterattack and take him by surprise.

However, the sure-win strike had failed.

Lin Ming was startled. Even though he didn’t underestimate Naqi, he never imagined that Naqi would be able to attain such high comprehension in the Laws as a saint race martial artist.

In that instant, Naqi had utilized three different Laws. In particular, the Space and Time Laws. Although he hadn’t been able to achieve the degree of proficiency that Lin Ming had reached, he had still steadily reached the fifth level Concept. If he used it for just defense then he was only slightly worse than Lin Ming, and this slight difference had caused his chest to be stabbed by the Phoenix Blood Spear.

Naqi’s defensive powerful was horrifying. It was impossible for that light stab to pierce his heart. Even though Lin Ming was able to break apart Naqi’s tough skin that was as hard as divine iron, that was entirely due to the powerful strength brought to him by the Eight Inner Hidden Gates. Otherwise, he wouldn’t even be able to leave behind a flesh wound!

“Naqi is injured!”

Many people noticed the blood leaking out from between Naqi’s fingers. The saint martial artists were so shocked that they couldn’t even speak.

In their minds, Naqi was an invincible existence amongst his peers. The only one that could challenge Naqi was the Good Fortune Saint Son if he had reversed his age by several dozen years!

And yet this Naqi was actually injured.

Everyone could see that the spear strike had only caused a light wound to his skin and flesh that didn’t even affect Naqi’s combat efficient. Even if that strike were to hit a human’s body, it still wouldn’t affect their combat strength, but those saint martial artists found this hard to believe.

This was because Naqi was a legendary existence in their minds!

The human martial artists all gripped their fists, not cheering. They only looked at the battlefield, nervousness in their eyes. In that exchange just now they hadn’t been able to understand anything at all, and the result was an unknown to him.

Naqi looked at his bloodstained hands. He stretched out his tongue and licked his bloodstained fingers, looking like a demonic monster.

“I didn’t expect that not only would you have inherited Empyrean Primordius’ legacy but that you would also have practiced the Grandmist Heavenly Dao to such a degree. I’ve underestimated you.” As Naqi spoke, the muscles on his chest began to wriggle about. The wound that Lin Ming left behind was regenerating at a visible speed.

What an abnormal restorative power!

This sort of regenerative ability was even greater than Lin Ming’s.

Lin Ming watched as the wound he left behind vanished. He coldly said, “I also didn’t think that even though you are a saint you would comprehend the Laws, and also to such a high boundary.”

“Hahaha!” Naqi laughed. “In the 33 Layered Heavens Dao, the essence gathering system has 11 layers. The ‘Seek Nine Falls and find the Nine Divine Shifts’ that humanity practices is only a single variation. In this world there is also an essence gathering system that my saint race can cultivate. Did you think that only you could dual cultivate body and energy and that I could not?

“Yes, whether it is humans or saints, both are equal. The saints excel in body transformation and humans excel in essence gathering. This also means that the ‘Seek Nine Falls and find the Nine Divine Shifts’ that humanity practices is the strongest essence gathering system of the 11 Daos! Now, let us see just who among us is more powerful!”

Whether it was Lin Ming or Naqi, both of them dual cultivated in body and energy. They were both unrivalled geniuses in this aspect, stepping on similar paths as if guided by the hands of fate.

Of course, Lin Ming not only dual cultivated body and energy, but triple cultivated essence, energy, and soul.

He believed that even though following this path of cultivation was difficult, it was necessary if he wished to find the road which led to the peak of martial arts, because that was the most universal truth in the world.

Bang!

Lin Ming and Imperial Prince Naqi collided once more. Their overwhelming momentum caused the earth to shake.

A terrifying shockwave rushed out like a tide, extending to infinity!

Lin Ming and Imperial Prince Naqi both launched into a brutal melee. Each strike was devastating, creating massive craters in the ground and filling the skies with dust. As one looked down from the heavens, they could see a giant bowl-shaped pit being slowly dug out.

In just a moment, the towering Ash Blood Mountain had been reduced to a desert. Countless rocks were turned into powder, crazily sweeping through the world in giant storms.

“Interesting, interesting! You are a match that is worthy for me to be excited about! But what a pity, your grandmist space cannot be filled with grandmist energy at all times, otherwise your true essence cannot endure. I know that stimulating the grandmist energy that is as heavy as stars places a tremendous burden and level of consumption on your body! If this is the limit of your skill then your loss has already been decided!”

Naqi wildly cackled. Atop his spear, a divine fire lit up. This was his astral essence that he was maddeningly burning.

Ka ka ka ka!

Naqi’s joints emitted explosive sounds once more. His body grew again and again until he was a head higher than Lin Ming.

Naqi’s body was originally covered in scales, but now those scales had turned into plates of bone armor!

The hard and fierce bone armor covered Naqi’s entire body. His arms became sturdier and thicker and meridian channels spread through his fingers, twisting about like worms. His entire being filled with strength and even his shoes split apart as clawed feet appeared, similar to a dragon’s.

On his head, curved horns grew out just like a devil. Then, with a flapping sound, a pair of giant wings unfolded behind Naqi’s back. As these two wings spread out, their wingspan was actually 30 feet.

Imperial Prince Naqi had transformed his body once more. This was two body metamorphoses!

“Two body metamorphoses?”

“He can transform his body twice!?”

All of the human martial artists were shocked. A single body metamorphosis ability was already freakishly abnormal, but Naqi was actually able to do so twice.

A terrifying aura exuded from his body. Let alone fighting him, even those people that were watching from ten miles away felt a horrible pressure!

Naqi smashed his claws into the ground and then slowly stood up. His two wings spread out, causing all of the surrounding dust and sand to be swept up into a tornado.

“My clan is one of the most magnificent clans of the saint race. We possess the royal bloodline, and when the most outstanding peak geniuses of my clan step into the realm of True Divinity, they can metamorphose their body three times! This was something that a senior accomplished in the holy war 3.6 billion years ago!

“Currently, I fall far short of that. But in the future, I too will step into such a boundary. I will leave behind the most wonderful legacy in the history of my clan!”

As Naqi spoke, he placed his long spear back into his spatial ring. Then, he extracted a massive heaven-sundering war halberd!

This halberd was 15 feet long; just the head of the halberd was four feet long! The giant halberd edge was cold and bright like a scythe. The shaft was as thick as an arm, and not even a grown man would be able to grasp it in one hand. The entire shaft was carved with images of all sorts of demons, savage and brutal.

But, this massive war halberd was actually perfect for Naqi’s giant body.

Lin Ming didn’t doubt that this halberd was forged with some type of special divine metal. Not only was it hard, but the weight itself could easily crush a mountain range. It was likely tens of millions of jins or even a hundred million jins!

It was hard to imagine just what might this halberd could display when used by Naqi, who had undergone his second metamorphosis.

As the surrounding human martial artists saw Naqi take out this giant war halberd, all of them looked at each other in utter dismay, shocked to the point of speechlessness.

They were all aware that the saints primarily cultivated body transformation, but as for what degree their body transformation technique had reached, no one knew. Now that they saw Naqi, they finally gained a profound understanding of this.

After the body transformation technique was cultivated to the peak, its might was beyond horrifying!

Facing such an enemy, just how would Lin Ming fight?

Naqi wildly laughed. After undergoing two body metamorphoses, even his personality had been influenced. He had become even more savage and arrogant!

“Lin Ming! I said that I will leave behind the most wonderful legacy in my clan! Now, let me start with you!”

Naqi roared out loud and dove towards Lin Ming. His wings spread out as his speed reached incomprehensible degrees! He was like a dragon, hurtling through the endless skies!

Hu – ! Hu – !

The two wings beat in the air, stirring up strong winds that swept up the surrounding sand. Naqi forcefully used the pressure of his flight to leave behind a giant pit in the ground!

That heaven-sundering war halberd came pounding down!

Lin Ming’s eyes widened as his entire body erupted with strength.

Grandmist space!

Hoh – !

The boundless aura of the grandmist space spread out. A strand of grandmist energy spun atop the war halberd. However, Naqi simply grinned, forcefully suppressing this grandmist energy as he struck down at Lin Ming!

“Haha! The Grandmist Heavenly Dao is wonderful, but your comprehension is too weak! Just what do you think a spider thread-thin strand of grandmist energy can do to me!? Now die!”

Within the grandmist space, Naqi’s speed hadn’t diminished at all. He continued rushing towards Lin Ming with his halberd!

In that moment, the space around Lin Ming came under a heavy pressure, nearly collapsing. He was placed in a cage, locked inside!

This was no longer just the Concept of Space, but Naqi also forcefully suppressing space with his powerful strength. Even with Lin Ming’s comprehensions of the Space and Time Laws, it was impossible for him to instantly break through these bindings!

If this halberd struck him, Lin Ming would find it nearly impossible to withstand it, even if he burst out with all of his strength. If there was an accident, he could be crushed to death!

As for Lin Ming using the Phoenix Blood Spear to block, it was simply impossible to block Naqi’s overwhelming momentum.

This was a critical moment!

In a thousandth of an instant in this life or death moment, a tiny blue spear rushed out from between Lin Ming’s eyebrows.

This blue spear split in two, half of it firing towards the war halberd and the other half firing towards Naqi’s forehead.

A terrifyingly exuberant aura emitted from this deep blue spear, similar to the aura of the grandmist space. This little blue spear was Lin Ming’s blue soul battle spirit!

When a battle spirit entered the blue soul realm, its strength would suddenly rise to another level, taking a huge leap upwards!

It had to be known that this step had stopped Lin Ming for a full 10 years!

Even Frost Dream, who studied the Divine Dream Law, had been extremely far from the blue soul battle spirit level in the past. Even the vast majority of peak Holy Lord powerhouses were stuck at this step, unable to make a breakthrough in their lives.

Chapter 1418 – Suppressing the Imperial Prince

In that moment, every ounce of origin energy between the heavens and earth began to crazily gather towards that seed of chaos, forming a dark star black hole!

Then, Lin Ming used the entirety of his strength to thrust this dark star black hole towards Imperial Prince Naqi.

“Dragon Wrestling Art, I’ll blow you up!”

Naqi lifted his hands high, bringing the heaven-sundering war halberd into the air. Then, he smashed down. This strike was used with 120% of his strength. He revolved all of his astral essence to the limit. His muscles bulged outwards as countless blue veins rose up, squirming about like earthworms even as they burst apart beneath the pressure!

The heaven-sundering war halberd came pounding down!

Bang!

With a dreadful explosion, Naqi’s halberd collided with the black hole seed!

In that instant, all the space within 10 miles collapsed!

This was the space of the Divine Void! Underneath the intense collision of Lin Ming and Naqi’s strike, this stable space was as frail as glass!

“A battle between a Divine Transformation and Saint Transformation martial artist can actually cause the space within 10 miles to collapse!”

“These two people are the absolute king amongst kings within their level, no one can compete with them! In front of them, a divine mountain is as frail as a sculpture and space is as thin as paper!”

Everyone cried out in alarm. At this time, the terrifying detonation force created by the black hole began to wantonly spread out.

It was Lin Ming and Naqi that bore the brunt of this terrifying impact.

Naqi’s entire body shook like an earthquake passed through it. The skin and flesh of his arms cracked apart and his palms split open. The bones of his arms cracked to pieces and he almost lost all feeling in his arms!

“What!?”

Naqi never imagined that this ordinary-looking black hole would be unbelievably hard. Not only did it withstand his attack but it also erupted with a terrifying strength.

As the one controlling this black hole, the impact that Lin Ming had to withstand was not light. Even though the black hole couldn’t be destroyed, Lin Ming still received tremendous wounds underneath the reckless surges of energy.

The explosive energy swept over Lin Ming like a wave, forcing him back a thousand feet. Only then was he able to stabilize the restless blood within him.

Naqi’s hands shivered. Blood dripped down his arms, gruesome and alarming. He nearly dropped the heaven-sundering war halberd.

He hadn’t thought that his battle with Lin Ming would reach such a frigid and savage degree.

Naqi had already consumed 60-70% of his astral essence. His strength had also plummeted by a great deal. But, he knew that he couldn’t weaken his momentum right now. Lin Ming definitely wasn’t in a better situation than he was. The victor of this fight would depend on who could hold out the longest.

“Die!”

Naqi roared. He ignored his severely wounded arms and rushed towards Lin Ming once more!

After exhausting so much of his energy, he still didn’t stop for even the slightest moment. He instead hurtled himself into another collision.

No matter how ruthless you are, I can be even more ruthless!

This form of combat caused all the martial artists to suck in a breath of cold air!

Ka ka ka ka!

Fierce and vicious bone spikes shot up from all over Naqi’s body!

As these bone spikes drilled forth from his skin, they brought behind them icky goo and blood. Each spike was four to five feet long, cold and dense just like a spear!

This was not body metamorphosis, but one of Naqi’s attack methods. It was similar to the time that Blacksalt utilized the spikes on his back. This was an ability that came from certain bloodlines of the saint race.

At this time, Naqi’s arms were injured and he couldn’t control his halberd. Thus, he used his body as a weapon to forcefully hurtle himself towards Lin Ming!

Wild Dragon Dash!

Naqi’s speed reached the extreme. Astral essence burned over his body. He was a massive black fireball that shot towards Lin Ming!

At this time, because of the previous collision and him barely suppressing the tumbling blood within him, Lin Ming’s true essence was in a chaotic mess. Even so, he wanted to face Naqi’s crazy rush head on!

The grandmist space couldn’t be used to defend; Lin Ming had trouble summoning it right now. As for his blue soul battle spirit, just that alone was not enough. Even If he tried to use his Phoenix Blood Spear in conjunction with it, that was simply suicide!

For Naqi, this 1000 foot distance took less than an instant to cross!

As the human martial artists saw this, all of them cried out in alarm.

However, Lin Ming actually remained remarkably calm. If Naqi hurtled towards him, although the might was great it would still put him at risk!

In this critical moment, Lin Ming’s pupils shrank. His soul force rushed into his inner world, and in front of Lin Ming, a massive stone gate appeared!

This stone gate emitted an infinite ancient aura. The entire gate was covered with mysterious carvings, as if a separate universe were sealed within it.

This was the Primordius Gate!

In the past, when Empyrean Primordius created this stone gate, he had done so with the highest level of chaos stone and then recorded all of the comprehensions he had gleaned in his lifetime. This included the complete heart mantra to the Primordius martial intent. However, the use of the Primordius Gate was not as simple as recording inheritances – it could also be used as a bafflingly powerful magic weapon!

Lin Ming summoned all the true essence available to him and poured it into the Primordius Gate!

Bang!

Naqi didn’t have time to react at all. He was like a raging bull, solidly smashing into the Primordius Gate!

The several spikes on Naqi’s body disintegrated into dust!

Puff!

Naqi spat out a mouthful of blood as he was sent rolling hundreds of feet away. The dark red Primordius Gate, besides violently shaking a bit as Naqi crashed into it, wasn’t even damaged in the slightest!

“This is…”

The martial artists watching were all shocked. This battle was already at its crescendo. When both Lin Ming and Naqi were nearly spent dry, this strange scene had occurred.

This strike was absolutely adding wounds upon wounds for Naqi!

As the one controlling the Primordius Gate, Lin Ming only had to withstand the traction of energy as Naqi crashed into the gate. His blood restlessly stirred up within him, but the force he withstood was hundreds and thousands of times lighter than Naqi!

“You… you…”

Naqi’s entire body shivered. His body was a mess of blood and flesh, and his muscles were split apart all over his body. Over half the bone armor that covered his body had broken and all of the spikes that jutted out from him had cracked apart. There were even some spikes that had pierced through his own flesh because of that massive impact just now, thrusting into his flesh. His meridians were broken and his organs were severely injured.

As he spoke, he vomited a mouthful of blood. This blood was mixed with fragments of his organs.

The current Naqi couldn’t even be described with just tragic!

If a human had been wounded to this degree, they would have died countless times already.

In that brief exchange just now, Lin Ming had taken a great advantage. But, this was due only to his magic weapon. The power of a weapon was a part of a martial artist’s strength, and Lin Ming currently was only able to stimulate a tiny portion of the Primordius Gate’s true strength; he was far from being able to fully control a treasure of this level. It was only that he had made the correct tactical choice at this moment.

The Primordius Gate had resolved Naqi’s attack while simultaneously causing heavy losses to him!

Naqi was already at the point of collapse.

“Die!”

At this time, Lin Ming opened the Eight Inner Hidden Gates once more. By relying on the Gate of Life he even burnt a part of his blood essence for greater strength. Now that he had the advantage, with Naqi having sustained severe wounds, he absolutely wouldn’t give his opponent any time to catch his breath.

He picked up the Primordius Gate with both hands, and by relying on his formidable bodily strength, he brought this stone gate pounding down at Naqi!

This was an attack using the Primordius Gate as a weapon!

Let alone the human martial artists that were skilled in the essence gathering system and were proficient in using the Laws, or even the saint martial artists that excelled in their bodily physiques, none of them had ever seen someone attack by picking up a massive stone gate and smashing it down on someone else.

The Primordius Gate could shrink and grow. In Lin Ming’s hands, it was 30-40 feet long, 20 feet wide, and a foot thick. As it came smashing down, the momentum and pressure it brought with it could roll over everything!

Imperial Prince Naqi was panic-stricken. Without a care for the agonizing pain in his arms, he brought up the heaven-sundering war halberd to meet this strike!

Facing this massive gate that was as thick as a city wall, the originally large heaven-sundering war halberd seemed like nothing but a child’s toy.

Peng!

With a muffled ring, Imperial Prince Naqi was smashed away by Lin Ming’s Primordius Gate!

Although he had barely managed to use the heaven-sundering war halberd to block this attack, his arms were in complete ruins. How could he withstand Lin Ming’s aggressive onslaught of gate smashes?

Lin Ming stepped forwards. The Primordius Gate that he held in his hands came crashing down once more!

Bang!

Like a fly, Naqi was sent tumbling back by Lin Ming again. He vomited blood in the air and even his war halberd was sent shooting away!

Lin Ming revolved the Space Laws and chased after him!

One step one smash, Naqi vomited blood again and again. No matter how powerful the bodies of the saints were, and even if Naqi had completed two body metamorphoses and he also possessed a heaven-defying king bloodline, he still couldn’t withstand this brutal and savage barrage.

This was complete devastation! Overwhelming and brutal! A beating to the death!

“This… this is…”

“The Imperial Prince… is defeated!?”

The saint martial artists were bewildered. The number one person amongst the younger generation of saints, the one who possessed the king bloodline, the invincible legend that was Imperial Prince Naqi, was actually savagely beaten by a human!

The final victory of humans had not come due to the essence gathering system or use of the Laws, but had relied on Lin Ming’s powerful bodily strength. A stone gate had been used to pulverize Naqi, causing him to vomit out endless amounts of blood.

The saint race martial artists found this impossible to accept!

“Hah!”

Lin Ming roared and struck out once more. With a loud ringing sound, Naqi was brutally struck down and pounded deep into the ground.

The earth caved in. Dust and sand rose up from all over. As the tens of thousands of saint and human martial artists saw this scene on the battlefield, all of them were left in utter silence.

Chapter 1424 – Transmission Accident

A pale white spirit ship rapidly flew through the endless void of the universe. This spirit ship was carved from crystalline stone and was only several hundred feet long. Compared to the massive spirit ships that were thousands or tens of thousands of feet long, this spirit ship was extremely small and delicate. However, its value was hundreds of times greater than those giant spirit ships because its speed was simply not something that those giant spirit ships could hope to compare with.

Even the Primordius Heavenly Palace that Lin Ming possessed couldn’t hold a candle to this tiny crystal spirit ship in terms of speed. This wasn’t because Primordius Heavenly Palace was lacking in value, but because Primordius Heavenly Palace was a dwelling that mainly focused on defensive protections. Acting as a spirit ship was only an auxiliary function.

“We’ve arrived.”

Empyrean Divine Dream’s voice faintly echoed through the spirit ship. In just several days of time, she had brought Lin Ming aboard this crystal spirit ship and had crossed several great worlds of the Divine Realm before arriving at a chaotic nebula.

“This is the entrance to the Asura Road?”

“It can be considered so.” Empyrean Divine Dream nodded. “Rather, it is more accurate to say that the entrance existed here a long time ago. It was said that due to the great calamity 3.6 billion years ago, many entrances leading from the Divine Dream to the Asura Road were destroyed. The ones I know of that are remaining are nothing more than ancient ruins. Normally, it is impossible to enter the Asura Road using this location, but I can rely upon my cultivation to forcefully sunder open the void and form a transmission channel to let you through.

“After you enter this transmission channel, a unique serial number will be implanted into your body. This number will follow you through every smelting trial that you complete within the Asura Road, and it will only vanish when you leave or upon your death. This number will also become the only marking from which the Asura Road’s Heavenly Dao rule will recognize you.”

“I understand. Then, when Dragon Fang entered the Asura Road in the past, was it also Three Lives Old Man that helped him open a portal?”

“Yes. Within the entire Divine Realm there aren’t many people that can open a portal like this; there are probably around 20-30 people that can. Although Three Lives Old Man is nearing the end of his lifespan, he still remains horrifyingly powerful. He is the most senior person in the entire Divine Realm. 280 million years ago, he had already become an extreme Empyrean.”

Lin Ming said, “If so, then aren’t the conditions for opening the transmission channel to the Asura Road too high? There shouldn’t have been many young geniuses that were able to enter the Asura Road in these past years to temper themselves.”

“Mm… indeed, there haven’t been many at all.” Empyrean Divine Dream nodded. “Not entering the Asura Road isn’t necessarily a disadvantage. Even extreme geniuses have a chance of perishing within the Asura Road.

“In addition, besides having an Empyrean open a portal to allow martial artists to enter the Asura Road, there is also another method. Before the last great calamity, there were many Asura Commands that existed in the Divine Realm. If you can find an Asura Command then there is no need for you to take a transmission channel; you can rely upon that Asura Command to directly enter the Asura Road. Moreover, this Asura Command is also a necessary item to leave the Asura Road and return to the Divine Realm.”

“Asura Command?” Lin Ming’s mind stirred. It seemed that if he couldn’t complete the smelting trials of the Asura Road, the only way he would be able to leave was to find an Asura Command.

“Alright. Lin Ming, I shall send you there now. Let me give you a word of caution, do not try to thoroughly complete the trials of the Asura Road. The difficulties of these trials are too great, far too great. If you can complete a part of it and obtain just a portion of the rewards, that alone is already rare. You should take safety into consideration before you do anything. As long as there is life, there will be hope, and you should value your life as the most precious treasure!”

Divine Dream earnestly warned Lin Ming. Lin Ming nodded, “I understand.”

“Mm… also, I want to speak to you about that 100 year duel you have decided on with the Good Fortune Saint Son. I know that you did so in order to intentionally place pressure on yourself to grow, but just because there is pressure on you doesn’t mean that you will succeed. What I want to say is that if that time truly comes and you are certain that it is impossible for you to defeat the Good Fortune Saint Son, I possess a last resort. I can unbind your heart demon oath, but there will be a high price to pay.”

Lin Ming’s heart skipped a beat as he heard Empyrean Divine Dream casually speaking. Pay a price to unbind his heart demon oath?

His heart demon oath was especially formed by a transcendent divine might used to form contracts. The most terrifying aspect was that it used a martial artist’s heart demons. Everyone had heart demons, and the higher a martial artist’s cultivation was, the more powerful their heart demons were.

Thus, whether it was young heroic elites, Holy Lords, World Kings, or Empyreans, all of them could be bound by heart demon oaths. Even True Divinities feared their own heart demons.

If someone tried to unbind the heart demon oath of another, they would be forced to endure a counterattack of their own heart demons. Now, Empyrean Divine Dream had said that she had a last resort she could use to help Lin Ming resolve his heart demon oath. There had to be a price paid, but as for what this price was, he had no idea.

Lin Ming knew that even if Empyrean Divine Dream had astonishing attainments in the domain of the soul, and she also comprehended heart demons to a high degree, this price couldn’t be light at all.

Such a promise was an extremely heavy graciousness to Lin Ming. After all, in the eyes of nearly all high level figures in the Divine Realm, although Lin Ming was talented, it was almost the idiotic babblings of a retard to think that he could overtake the realm and a half advantage that the Good Fortune Saint Son had over him in a mere hundred years.

“Senior Divine Dream, this junior will carve this graciousness in his mind. A hundred years from now, I will not disappoint you.”

Lin Ming grit his teeth. He had to squeeze out every single drop of his potential; there was no path of retreat for him.

“Mm, you have never done anything you don’t have confidence in. I hope that this time is the same.”

As Divine Dream spoke she extended her right hand. Because of the movements of her arm, a beautiful, white pure arm as smooth as jade stretched out from her long white sleeve.

This arm seemed supple and flexible but it contained an incomparably terrifying power. With just a tiny tap, the void shattered like a frail ice crystal, completely disintegrating.

Ka ka ka ka ka!

This crack spread out like a growing spider web. In just an instant, it covered the heavens, blotting out the world!

“Step back a little.”

Empyrean Divine Dream faintly said. Lin Ming quickly flew back to the spirit ship.

Empyrean Divine Dream rapidly moved her fingers, forming a series of seals. The entire area began to spin around, forming a giant vortex in space. Endless heaven and earth origin energy began rolling up towards this vortex, swept up into it. Empyrean Divine Dream had actually forcefully created a black hole vortex.

This sort of action left Lin Ming shocked. With the slightest of gestures, Empyrean Divine Dream had broken apart all space for a hundred miles and forcefully opened up a spatial transmission channel.

This was the power of the most extreme Empyrean.

“You may enter now. I have already reformed the space channel. Through this channel you can directly enter the Asura Road. Also, this space channel is limited by certain rules. Only you alone are allowed to pass through; it is impossible for you to bring along incarnations of powerhouses, otherwise I could have produced several of them to help protect you in critical moments.”

“Oh, what happens if I violate these rules?” Lin Ming suddenly asked.

“Not much. You will be shot back out with some minor injuries, but you can re-enter afterwards.”

“I see…” Lin Ming nodded. “Then Senior Divine Dream, this junior will be on his way.”

As Lin Ming spoke, he took a deep breath and then turned into a beam of light as he dove into that black hole vortex!

The moment he entered that black hole vortex, Lin Ming felt a massive resistance. This resistance began to rapidly increase. In just the blink of an eye, it became an overwhelming momentum that formed an impregnable iron wall, rushing towards Lin Ming!

“Mm?”

Lin Ming was startled. Before he could respond he was struck by this horrifying strength. He was slapped backwards as if he were struck by a mountain.

Woosh!

Lin Ming flew out from the black hole at an even faster speed than he entered. The terrifying strike of energy caused Lin Ming to feel as if all his bones almost shattered. A coppery rush swelled up his throat as he spat out a mouthful of blood and nearly fainted where he was.

“What… what happened…” Lin Ming’s entire body was in severe pain. The energy within him was restlessly moving and his organs felt discombobulated.

Before he entered the Asura Road transmission channel, he had asked Divine Dream what would happen if he violated the rules. If the punishment were to be exterminated like a rabid dog then that sort of death would be far too unjust.

Afterwards, Empyrean Divine Dream had said that the punishment wasn’t too great so Lin Ming didn’t mind much after that. Or, to be more accurate, he didn’t think that the Asura Road would recognize that he violated these rules.

However, Lin Ming had indeed violated the rules. Within the Magic Cube space there were two people. One was Mo Eversnow and the other was the gluttonous and sleep-loving Fishy.

In Lin Ming’s opinion, the Magic Cube was an existence that surpassed the scope of the Heavenly Dao Laws. It was impossible for anyone to see the Magic Cube that was deeply slumbering within his body.

In the past, Lin Ming had encountered various mystic realms which also had various restrictions when crossing into them, but none of them were able to block the Magic Cube. This was the same when Lin Ming returned to the Sky Spill Continent. The Sky Spill Planet had the protective enchantment of Empyrean Primordius, making it so that no non-native martial artists with a cultivation above the Divine Sea realm could enter. But, this hadn’t been able to stop the Magic Cube.

Only today had he ever encountered problems!

This was something that Lin Ming never imagined possible. This Asura Road was far too strange.

Even the Magic Cube was unable to skirt around its rules!

“Lin Ming, you…” Empyrean Divine Dream looked at Lin Ming, puzzled, “Do you have an incarnation jade slip on your body? Was it given to you by one of Mount Potala’s eminent monks?”

Lin Ming ruefully smiled. He certainly didn’t have an incarnation jade slip on his body to explain his current predicament. If he couldn’t bring Fishy and Mo Eversnow with him, then he would need to explain this to Empyrean Divine Dream.

Empyrean Divine Dream had helped him far too many times. At Demondawn World, she had also saved his life. Lin Ming’s emotional and mental inhibitions towards Divine Dream had fallen to the lowest limit.

Lin Ming hesitated for a moment and then truthfully said, “It isn’t an incarnation jade slip… on this junior’s body is… Senior, please take a look.”

As Lin Ming spoke, his thoughts moved and both Mo Eversnow and Fishy were teleported out from the Magic Cube space. Although Mo Eversnow was residing in the Magic Cube space, she also had an approximate understanding of what was happening. She looked towards Lin Ming and also looked towards Empyrean Divine Dream. This sort of situation was completely beyond her realm of expectations. With everything happening so suddenly she was a bit embarrassed and also a bit cautious, although she knew there was no point keeping her guard up in front of Empyrean Divine Dream.

As for Fishy, she rubbed her large and sleepy eyes. She looked around, her eyes blurry, like she didn’t know what was happening.

As Empyrean Divine Dream saw Mo Eversnow and Fishy suddenly appear, she was shocked. Hiding within Lin Ming’s body were two women? And from beginning to end, she had never seen through it!

Chapter 1428 – Spiritas Slave

The entire Asura Road consisted of a massive continent. This central continent was in the shape of a giant rectangular strip. The Asura Road was over 100 quadrillion miles long, but it was actually only a billion miles wide.

This strangely-shaped continent was countless times longer than it was wide; this caused the entire land to look like a straight road.

In addition, countless slaughters took place on this continent, just like an Asura battlefield.

The name of the Asura Road had been derived from these two aspects.

The Asura Road was divided into three sections: the outer section, middle section, and inner section. The deeper one went down the Asura Road the more intense the slaughter would become and also the more dangerous it would be. If one wanted to emerge from the depths of the Asura Road, that would be extremely difficult!

Currently, Lin Ming was on the outermost section of the Asura Road.

Asura Road, City of Discord –

This was the first large city on the edges of the Asura Road’s outer section.

The skies above the City of Discord looked like a giant grey curtain. The air was overflowing with chaotic origin energy and deep pulses of killing intent appeared frequently.

Here, countless masters roamed the lands and countless influences were caught up in intrigue; it was a perilous city in constant chaos.

In the city itself, the thugs of the various influences still had some level of restraint. However, in the outskirts of the city, murdering others and stealing their goods was far too common.

“A fat sheep has come.”

“Mm? A human martial artist? His cultivation is a bit low but it’s rare to have such a deep foundation. He must be some genius that came here to temper himself. Hehe, this sort of person is usually extremely wealthy.”

In a jungle on the outskirts of the City of Discord, seven or eight demon race martial artists were gathered together. They all wore black clothes and they were tall, with powerful and robust figures. Their bodies were healthy and corded with muscles. They were a bit similar to the Sky Spill Continent’s Giant Demon race but slightly shorter.

In addition, there was someone completely wrapped in a thick black robe with a bamboo hat covering his face. His entire body exuded dark demonic energies and he seemed ethereal. He gave off an extremely dangerous feeling.

“Be careful, this person is strong. Although his cultivation isn’t high, do not underestimate him.” The black-robed man said in a coarse voice. It seemed he had a high status amongst these people.

“We understand, Mister. We’ve been in this line of work for 20 years and we’ve already had over a hundred of us brothers die, so we’ve long understood such a truth. Even if the person in front of us is only a normal Divine Transformation youth we still won’t take him lightly and will use everything we have. Even a lion must try its best to capture a rabbit.”

The leader of these black-clothed people said. The black-robed man they called mister was already sufficient to explain his status. He should be considered the strategist of this bunch.

The several black-clothed martial artists looked at each other. Then, the captain of these demon martial artists waved his hand, saying, “Go!”

Of these seven or eight martial artists, the weakest were equal to late Divine Transformation martial artists. At this time, they all rushed out together, hurtling towards their prey!

“More robbers…”

Flying in the air, Lin Ming had long ago discovered this group of people. Although he couldn’t understand their cultivation and thus couldn’t see their exact boundary, he could still discern their relative strength through their auras.

Lin Ming discovered that in the Asura Road, his own cultivation had become his lucky charm.

Of course, Lin Ming didn’t think he was invincible in the Asura Road. In fact, there were some people here that could kill him without much effort at all.

However, the strength Lin Ming revealed on the outside was far too low, only at the Divine Transformation realm. Those people with strength equal to the late Holy Lord realm simply wouldn’t bother wasting their time on robbing someone at the Divine Transformation realm. Those that would do such a thing were usually at the Divine Transformation or Divine Lord realm in strength. And, these people weren’t able to pose a threat to Lin Ming.

As Lin Ming saw these people shoot towards him he sneered. He didn’t retreat. Rather, he suddenly accelerated, breaking through the air directly at them!

“Mm? This brat!”

The captain demon martial artist was shocked. He never thought that not only would his prey not run away but he would actually accelerate towards them. There were only two possibilities for such a situation. The first was that this youth was a fool and the second was that this youth had absolute confidence in his own strength.

For a youth that dared to enter the Asura Road smelting trial and also have such a solid foundation, there was almost a zero chance for the first possibility.

That meant it could only be the second!

As the black-clothed demon captain thought of this, he viciously smiled, “If that’s the case, let’s see just who is more ruthless!”

“Kill!”

A roar shook the heavens. The seven or eight demon martial artists attacked together. Lin Ming flung his hand forwards and thrust out the Phoenix Blood Spear. A divine light of thunder and fire twined together, slicing through the void, causing a horrifying wave of energy to sweep forwards!

Rumble rumble rumble!

With a series of terrifying explosions, the red and purple spear light covered all the demon martial artists.

In an instant, blood rained down as anguished voices cried out! The three demon martial artists in the front that bore the brunt of the attack immediately exploded into pieces from the brutal power of thunder and fire! Up until these people died, their faces were still covered with expressions of absolute disbelief.

The demon captain was panic-stricken. He would never have dreamt this was possible. He had already given this human youth an extremely high appraisal in strength, but his true strength was as different from his thoughts as the heavens and earth! If this youth wasn’t concealing his cultivation then perhaps only the greatest genius of a universe could be so ridiculously strong!

“How… could… such… bad luck…”

The was the demon captain’s last thought. In the next moment, all of the demon robbers had been completely exterminated by Lin Ming!

The entire battle had lasted for less than a single breath of time. The Phoenix Blood Spear was still held slanted in Lin Ming’s hand, the spearpoint not stained with a single drop of blood.

Lin Ming’s complexion was still indifferent like before. And in that jungle area, there was still the black-robed man. His entire body shook; it was clear that he was shaking in fear.

“That human… is simply a devil!”

This black-robed strategist hid behind a giant rock, hiding his aura as much as possible. A force field made from his soul force appeared around him, isolating out all fluctuations of life.

In terms of concealing his aura, only a soul form could do this in the most perfect way possible.

But at this time, with a slight swishing sound, a human youth appeared right in front of him like ghosts and gods.

“Ahh!”

Fortunately, the black-robed man was used to seeing life or death scenes or he would have already fainted in fear.

Lin Ming had appeared too suddenly without any indication at all.

“The last one…”

Lin Ming raised the Phoenix Blood Spear, killing intent flowing out from him.

Against these people that murdered and robbed others, he wouldn’t give them any quarter at all. He would kill all them without a shred of mercy.

“Wait… wait!”

The black-robed man shakily spoke out words of the Divine Realm.

In these past days within the Asura Road, Lin Ming discovered that there were three main languages used. One of them was the language of the Divine Realm, mostly used by humans and demons. However, because there weren’t many humans in the Asura Road, the Divine Realm language was mostly spoken by the demon race.

This black-robed man clearly wasn’t from the demon race. Lin Ming could feel a very powerful soul aura coming from this man’s body. As for the blood vitality of his body, it was far, far too little, approaching almost zero.

“Spiritas?”

A thought lit up in Lin Ming’s mind. This was the first time he had seen a martial artist of the soul race.

The soul race was one of the peak races of the 33 Layered Heavens. Their strength was an unknown to him, but they shouldn’t be any worse than the saints.

“Yes… I am a spiritas. Do not kill me, I am willing to give you all my god runes and be your slave.”

As the black-robed spiritas spoke, he took off his robe, revealing a sparkling body. This spiritas wore a set of armor that shimmered with a great light. It seemed as if he wasn’t a solid entity at all.

The man knelt down on his knees, showing absolute submission.

“Mm? Be my slave?” Lin Ming’s thoughts stirred. When he first arrived the Asura Road, he had encountered two robbers that possessed god slave seals.

Ordinarily, many people would rather die than become a slave. This was because after becoming a slave, they would lose all sense of personality and turn into a mindless puppet without any awareness at all; this was no different from death. They would be controlled by others and lose any and all dignity.

Unless a master lifted the seal on their own initiative, they would be a slave until death.

“You would rather be a slave than die?” Lin Ming still hadn’t retracted his spear.

“Yes, because of some reasons I still do not wish to die yet. Moreover, you are extremely strong. If I follow you I will quickly lose value, and perhaps you might let me go at that time.”

“Lose value? Then tell me just what value you have for me now.” Lin Ming’s coldly said. In terms of strength, this spiritas in front of him was nothing at all.

“Information!” The spiritas martial artist said. “In addition, I can refine pills and draw inscriptions. You might not know, but the best alchemists and god rune masters in the Asura Road are all spiritas! In the achievements of these two skills, my soul race is several times stronger than the other races combined! There is just no comparison!”

“Oh?” Lin Ming’s mind stirred. “Inscription?”

Within the Divine Realm, when one reached a high enough cultivation, the role that inscription technique could play was extremely small. But in the Asura Road, the inscriptions that this spiritas martial artist spoke about were obviously not as simple as the Divine Realm inscription technique.

What he said was – god rune master.

This likely had something to do with god runes.

And, the spiritas martial artist’s next words confirmed Lin Ming’s thoughts.

The spiritas said, “In the Asura Road, if god runes are combined with inscription technique then they can produce incredible changes. Here, god runes are nearly equal to the highest Laws. Moreover, the truth is that these Laws can even be used in the outside world; all of that depends on whether or not you can receive the permission of the Asura Road’s Heavenly Dao. If you can spare my life then I can do inscription or alchemy for you. Even if there is some alchemy or inscription mission that I cannot help complete, I can still recommend to you spiritas grandmasters. Once you control me with a god rune, I will be absolutely loyal to you and you will not need to suspect me at all. Moreover, the god runes are the highest Laws so no one can unravel them but you.

“And, you can ask me any questions you have about the smelting trials and unknown lands of the Asura Road!”

The conditions that the spiritas martial artist put forth were very tempting, especially the last one. Indeed, Lin Ming knew far too little about the Asura Road. He didn’t even know how to complete any of the Asura Road’s smelting trials.

Lin Ming looked at the spiritas martial artist, “You seemed to know that I’m a newcomer to the Asura Road. How do you know this?”

“That is because I can approximately feel the strength of the god runes within your body, and… they are too weak… far too weak. Not only is there an extremely small quantity but the quality is also very low. If you were weak then this would be reasonable, but you are extremely strong. This proves that you are likely a newcomer. Moreover, even if you weren’t a newcomer, your understandings of the Asura Road shouldn’t surpass mine because I have already lived here for several hundred years and have collected a great deal of information.”

“Very well, it’s a deal!”

Lin Ming agreed. Killing this spiritas martial artist was meaningless to him, but keeping him around would indeed be a bit useful.

Chapter 1429 – The Final Trial

A gray-blue rune shimmered in the air before slowly sinking into the spiritas martial artist’s forehead. The spiritas’ face twitched as he grit his teeth and withstood the pain.

For a moment, the pupils of the spiritas were filled with chaos before suddenly being restored to pure brightness. Now, as he looked towards Lin Ming his eyes were filled with awe and respect.

“Old slave Soulwhite greets Master.”

“Good. Soulwhite, I do not need you to follow me for too long. When I leave the Asura Road I will return your freedom to you. Now, I want to ask you, how can I be considered as having passed the smelting trials of the Asura Road?”

“Reporting to Master, this Asura Road, in the mind of this servant, is like a game created by a supreme god. We are placed in this game and made to play it. For the winners, unimaginable rewards await, but for losers, there is nothing but death.”

“In the Asura Road the Heavenly Dao rules that govern this world are incomparably strange. Many things have already been set in stone. Trial challengers can find god runes through certain lucky chances, and once you collect the required specific sets of god runes then that will trigger a chance to enter the final smelting trial. Through this smelting trial, you will be able to obtain the rewards of the Asura Road’s Heavenly Dao! This is because the person who created the Asura Road is an unimaginable existence. There are even those who speculate that this unknown existence is the master of the 33 Layered Heavens. In short, the rewards of the Asura Road are extremely rich!”

“Collect the sets of god runes?”

Lin Ming’s mind stirred.

“Yes. Only those god runes that can form complete sets are considered the most useful. There are some individual scattered god runes, for instance, the slave seal rune that master used on this servant, that do not have much significance. Currently, there are known to be over a thousand sets of complete god runes. But, these god rune sets are mostly focused within the bronze level and silver level. A small number are in the gold level and even less are in the blue soul level. Beyond that, any complete sets at the zenith black level are simply a legend. In order to qualify for the final smelting trial, there are 36 sets of god runes required.

“A complete set of god runes is ten times, a hundred times, or even a thousand times more valuable than runes of the same grade that aren’t complete. Moreover, runes that can form complete sets will not fuse with the blood and flesh of a martial artist. Once martial artists are killed, these god runes will escape from their bodies where they can be obtained by the killer!”

“So that’s how it is…” Lin Ming said to himself, suddenly aware. When he entered the Asura Road he had killed two robbers, and one of them had dropped a god rune called the Mournful Spirit’s Right Hand. This god rune was part of a set, and now it seemed that this wasn’t a coincidence at all. It seemed that only these god runes were able to be dropped from others.

And as Soulwhite had said, if one wanted to pass the smelting trial, the first condition was to collect enough complete sets of god runes. Only like this would he have the chance to go through the smelting trial. Otherwise, he wouldn’t be able to enter at all.

Moreover, every time a set of god runes was gathered, it could greatly enhance a martial artist’s strength. From this, one could see that they were much more valuable than ordinary god runes.

Even so, not even a complete set of god runes would bind with the flesh and blood of a martial artist. Once a martial artist was killed, these god runes would fall out. These god runes would inevitably become objects that countless martial artists struggled over, treasures that would start a storm of blood and war!

This was especially true for extremely high level god runes. Let alone a set, if only a single one were to appear in the world, that was still enough for everyone to crazily struggle for it. Who knew just how many rivers of blood would have to flow?

If this Asura Road was really a game created by a supreme god, then the original intention of this game was to make the trial challengers here slaughter each other, and then use this trial of blood and death to select the most outstanding individual from the mountain of corpses!

“Soulwhite, tell me something, through all these years, just how many people have thoroughly completed the Asura Road’s smelting trial?”

Lin Ming could imagine that wanting to complete the smelting trial was more difficult than ascending to heaven. But, according to Divine Dream, the Asura Road had already existed for countless hundreds of millions of years; it was a world that had existed far beyond the last great calamity. In all of these years, more geniuses had emerged than there were grains of sand in an endless desert. In addition, with the increasing number of martial artists that were native to the Asura Road, there should have been someone capable of passing the smelting trial.

Soulwhite said, “Reporting to Master, the Asura Road’s smelting trial is simply far too difficult. In history, there are indeed martial artists who have crossed the smelting trial, but their era is far too remote for our imaginations. These people once left behind endless numbers of legends in the past, but these legends were watered down over the generations, evolving into numerous versions that are impossible to verify.

“To thoroughly pass the smelting trial is a near impossibility. But, if it is only collecting the 36 sets of god runes required to enter the final trial, and then surviving and completing a part of the trial and correspondingly collecting a part of the rewards, then that is a bit more simple.

“Of course, this is simple only in the context of the massive number of martial artists in the Asura Road. With so many people, there will always be those that possess strength that defies the heavens or luck that defies the heavens and are thus able to collect the required god runes. I believe the master is also one of these people.

“However, if Master enters the final trial, Master must be careful, because this final trial has an extremely high mortality rate. Master must not be greedy for more rewards and choose a path that cannot be completed; that will only result in dying in vain. In these last 100 million years, out of all the martial artists that have started the final trial, the one with the highest completion has only reached an 83% completion rate.”

“Oh?” Lin Ming thought out loud, “83%? You know this exact number?”

“Of course. This is because after the Asura Road’s final trial ends, the Asura Road’s Heavenly Dao will inform every existence in this world about the results of those martial artists that have completed above 70%. The Heavenly Dao will also inform the world of their name and cause their name to rise to fame! In the last 100 million years, only two people have managed to surpass 80% in the final trial. One of them is a saint race martial artist and the other is a soul race martial artist, one a man and the other a woman. Coincidentally, both of them appeared 30 years ago. The saint martial artist had an 81% completion rate and the young spiritas girl had an 83% completion rate. Afterwards, both of them earned unimaginable rewards. It is said that the two of them were the top geniuses of their respective races.

As Whitesoul spoke to here, Lin Ming was startled.

Number one top talent? 30 years ago?

Lin Ming didn’t ask about who that spiritas girl was – he certainly wouldn’t know her. But, that saint martial artist…

“What is the name of that saint martial artist?” A light flashed in Lin Ming’s eyes.

“That person’s name was Wumo.”

Whitesoul spoke as if this was something everything knew about.

As Lin Ming heard this name he sucked in a deep breath. Wumo! The Good Fortune Saint Son, Wumo!

“It really was him!”

As he thought, before entering the Asura Road, the Good Fortune Saint Son had yet to obtain his title. At that time, he was only known as Wumo.

But, after leaving the Asura Road and also completing 81% of the final trial, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had bestowed a title upon him – the Good Fortune Saint Son, the official title for the next Saint Sovereign!

The next time that he appeared in the world, he naturally was referred to as the Good Fortune Saint Son. Then, that title had become his name.

“So that’s how it is… Wumo also once entered the Asura Road!”

Lin Ming didn’t think this was strange. In the Divine Realm, because of the broken transmission arrays, only those skilled Empyrean descendants would be able to come to this Asura Road smelting trial. As for the other races, this sort of trial was likely much more common. If the Good Fortune Saint Son was such an extraordinary person, how could he miss out on this opportunity?

“He participated in the smelting trial 30 years ago and obtained an 81% completion rate. That makes him one of the top ranked martial artists in the last 100 million years! And, this compares all the geniuses of the 33 Layered Heavens. If Wumo can accomplish this, it’s no wonder he’s so arrogant.”

With such an achievement under his belt, it was no surprise that he didn’t care for Lin Ming.

Not only did the Good Fortune Saint Son believe that Lin Ming’s talent was inferior to his, but to make up the disparity of dozens of years was easier said than done!

“In the turmoil of the world, the soul race is really overflowing with talent! That spiritas genius was actually able to suppress Wumo! It’s unbelievable. In the 33 Layered Heavens, powerhouses are like clouds. There is no limit in this universe; there is always a higher mountain and a stronger person.”

As Lin Ming was thinking this, he felt his heated blood boiling within him. Out of all the upcoming heroes of the 33 Layered Heavens, he was sure to be one of them, and also an important one!

The Good Fortune Saint Son had completed his smelting trial 30 years ago. But, he had likely entered the Asura Road at least 40 years ago. In other words, the disparity between Lin Ming and the Good Fortune Saint Son was around 40 years. In the next 100 years, Lin Ming had to overcome this disparity of 40 years!

If he was chasing after an ordinary genius then this would be simple. But, the one he was chasing after was the second most talented genius in the last 100 million years of the 33 Layered Heavens!

This required that Lin Ming grew over 50% faster than he did!

“Grow 50% faster…” Lin Ming gripped his fists, a smile crowding his face. “I don’t think that’s too bad!”

Now that he had a clear goal in his heart, he felt his fighting spirit roused.

He had to overtake the Good Fortune Saint Son and reveal his skill in the future. Now, his quest to do so would begin at the Asura Road!

No matter what, Lin Ming’s degree of completion had to surpass that of the Good Fortune Saint Son as well as that spiritas girl!

Lin Ming subconsciously gripped his fists. But, as his fighting spirit was seething, he didn’t know that a trillion miles away at one of the countless other entrances to the Asura Road, a team of martial artists had entered.

These people were all saint martial artists; there were several hundred of them in total.

Without a doubt, each and every one of them was a genius. If they were placed in the Divine Realm it was likely that they could reach the top 100 of the First Martial Meeting finals.

The leader of these people was a tall youth. This youth was Imperial Prince Naqi, who had been defeated by Lin Ming.

After several months of recuperation, Naqi’s shattered body had healed from his savage beating by Lin Ming. After all, In terms of recovering, Naqi surpassed even Lin Ming.

“Asura Road! Hehe, we’ve finally arrived to complete this trial! Just wait for me Lin Ming. During our battle at the Chaotic Blood Continent, you used some strange move to summon a stone gate carved from chaos stones and had me smash into it, severely wounding and even defeating me! That loss was due to a tactical mistake on my part and not because I was lacking in strength. I refuse to accept that battle. We still haven’t truly compared just who amongst us is stronger and weaker!

“Now that I have come to this Asura Road, my ultimate goal is to complete over 80% of the final trial and have my name carved down on the divine tablet for the next 100 million years! At that time, I will obtain incredible advantages and then I will fight you again, ruining your body and soul, destroying your confidence until you never dare to fight me again!”

Chapter 1435 – Many Wolves, Little Meat

“They’re here… one… two… three… four, four waves of people. It seems I’m really welcome here.” Lin Ming mockingly said. Out of all the trial challengers, Lin Ming had the lowest cultivation. In the eyes of the others, he was like a piece of meat that could be butchered however they pleased.

Out of the four different waves of people that were coming, two were alone and two were in groups. One of the groups was the Black Iron Ghost Triad and the other was a couple.

When they passed through the portal they had held hands and gone together. Like this, they wouldn’t be separated in the space transmission passage.

Woosh!

The couple was the first to arrive. A monster youth followed close behind them.

This monster youth had pale skin and sharp, pointed ears. Although he could be called a youth, he was actually around a hundred years old. His nickname was Charming. With his outstanding strength and fair yet handsome appearance, he was well-received by the many women within the City of Discord.

“Hehe, do you want to eat everything yourself?” The monster youth grinned.

“There are too many wolves and too little meat. Just a single skull badge and there are even more people catching up here. Who can obtain this skull badge will all depend on your ability!”

The husband and wife couple in front of the monster youth drew their weapons, as if they wanted to compete for Lin Ming’s skull badge. To them, Lin Ming’s badge was already a piece of fat placed in the pot. The only question right now was who had the ability to eat it.

Shua! Shua!

Right after, two more waves of people arrived. The Black Iron Ghost Triad was amongst them. For a time, besides Lin Ming, there were seven people here in total.

It was said that when enemies met, eyes would turn red. When the Black Iron Ghost third brother saw Lin Ming, he demonically grinned as he kneaded his fists again and again.

“Brat, heaven’s path was there but you chose not to take it, and instead you would rather break through the gates of hell! Although we won’t kill you today because of the rules, we will still beat you into a cripple. Once we leave, we’ll tidy you up some more. We’ll shatter your bones and meridians until you’re crawling like a dead dog on the streets! Hahaha!”

“A pack of wolves surrounding a single piece of meat. There’s just one skull badge and so many of us here. It will be impossible for us to divide it. Do you really think we should fight each other over a single skull badge?”

The monster youth glanced over at the Black Iron Ghost Triad and also looked at Lin Ming, his voice calm. If he dared to operate by himself in the City of Discord, he inevitably had a strong foundation of his own. If they were to really fight here, he would not be weaker than any of the other three parties.

“Hehe, everyone, give him to us brothers.” The Black Iron Ghost Triad boss spoke up. “Us brothers already have a grudge against this boy and we just happened to want to settle it here today. As for that skull badge, it isn’t too important to us. Honestly speaking, out of everyone here, none of us really have a chance of passing the game checkpoints. In my opinion, aren’t most of you here to gain some experience to prepare yourself for next time?”

“Haha, none of that matters to me. I’ve long since had the strength to become a one-star Asura but I simply didn’t have the time for it. I’m really thinking I should stay here to collect the 50 skull badges and complete this trial!” The monster youth confidently said, his arrogant voice passing out far and wide.

The Black Iron Ghost Triad boss’ eyebrows shot up. This monster fellow was far too rampant. Just what sort of awesome hero did he think he was?

Although the boss found this unbearable, he didn’t dispute those words. Instead, the Black Iron Triad boss said, “Fine, you can pass whatever you want. We’ll let you have the skull badge; we don’t want it.”

“Haha, what a wonderful idea, It’s a deal!” The monster youth smiled wide. Of course, if he wanted the skull badge he also had to obtain the agreement of the other two parties.

“However….” The monster youth paused for a moment. He suddenly turned to Lin Ming, an interested look in his eyes. “Before anything happens, I have something I want to ask you. I’ve been curious; why were you flying through the skies? In this Hunter Game, no matter how I see it, only a mentally retarded child would do something like that. Even a fool knows what consequences flying through the skies will bring. Even so, you seemed to have done so intentionally. Was it to draw us to you? You have succeeded, but… just what is your motive?”

“Hehe, that’s simple. He probably understands that is is impossible for him to pass the checkpoint, thus he deliberately attracted a group of people to him so that they would somehow engage in a group melee. Then, he would be able to take advantage of the chaos. This idea of yours was far too dumb!” One of the Black Iron Ghosts sarcastically mocked.

Lin Ming chuckled, and his chuckle was very calm. “There is no other reason I did so than to draw you all here. I flew through the sky and exposed myself on purpose to save myself a great deal of trouble.”

“Eh, how interesting!” The monster youth rubbed his chin, his wide and large eyes shining as he stared at Lin Ming as if he wanted to see through his body. “The more I know, the less I understand. This is the world of the Hunter Game and also the first time you have come here, so it’s impossible for you to have set up any traps beforehand to deal with us. Could it be that you actually thought you could deal with all of us by yourself?”

“Correct.” Lin Ming snapped his fingers. “Your presence here increases the difficulty of the game by a great deal. I admit that with all of you here, I lack confidence to be able to pass the checkpoint, thus I made the decision to send all of you out and reduce the difficulty.”

“What!?”

As Lin Ming spoke, the monster race youth as well as everyone else was left completely dumbfounded. Was this boy insane? Where did he get the crazy idea of eliminating all of them?

“Well, to put it in simpler terms…” Lin Ming took out the Phoenix Blood Spear. On the spear point, the power of thunder and fire began weaving together. “My strength, is greater than all of yours combined!”

As Lin Ming spoke, his figure vanished like ghosts and demons in the night.

“This is bad!”

“Be careful!”

The sudden change left everyone panic-stricken. All of them began to immediately retreat.

And at this time, the Black Iron Ghost third brother suddenly felt a chill crawl down his back. A thick killing intent had quietly appeared from behind him, locking onto his entire body!

Reflexively he took out a saber from his spatial ring to slash behind him, however… Lin Ming’s speed was far too fast, a level that surpassed his ability to respond to. The moment the third brother slashed out, he felt a cool feeling at his back and a sharp pain as a spear thrust through his chest like a viper, sticking outwards.

Blood sparkled on the spear point, dazzling to the eyes.

The Black Iron Ghost Triad’s third brother was pierced through by Lin Ming’s spear! The tough body of a saint race martial artist was sliced apart like raw beef beneath the Phoenix Blood Spear!

“The hell!?”

Just 200 feet away, the monster youth was able to clearly see everything that happened. To him, Lin Ming’s speed was not much different from teleportation!

These were the Space Laws! Only a human martial artist could use the Laws to the extreme! Although saints were fast, they couldn’t be faster than the Laws!

And there was also that casual and light spear strike. Without any grand martial skill behind it and only some true essence poured into the attack, that spear had been able to pierce through the body of the Black Iron Ghosts’ third brother. This striking force left the monster youth frightened. Although the Black Iron Ghosts’ third brother only had ordinary strength, he was still a saint race martial artist and his martial arts came from tempering his body. No matter how weak he was, since he had cultivated to the Saint Lord realm, his flesh and bones should be as hard as divine iron. In addition, there was also astral essence protecting his body, and yet he had still been so easily pierced through by Lin Ming’s spear. Just what sort of explosive force was behind that attack!?

“First!”

Lin Ming suddenly pulled out the Phoenix Blood Spear. The reason that his attack had so easily pierced through the Black Iron Ghosts’ third brother was because of his true essence and because his mortal strength had reached several hundred million jins after he opened the Eight Inner Hidden Gates. And, another reason was that Lin Ming had poured his battle spirit into the Phoenix Blood Spear. Towards the saint race martial artists that were weak in the aspect of the soul, a battle spirit was a great advantage of humans.

“Die!”

Lin Ming coldly shouted. He smashed his palm into the Black Iron Ghost third brother’s chest. This simple palm strike was actually the most insidious martial skill in Lin Ming’s arsenal – the Pulse Cutting Palm!

After not using this attack for so many years, this martial skill now struck the Black Iron Ghost third brother. Lin Ming didn’t hold back at all. With a light cracking sound, true essence violently crashed into the Black Iron Ghost third brother’s meridians and bones, instantly severing them and cutting off his blood vitality!

Killing was discouraged in this game through loss of skull badges. Thus, Lin Ming decided to follow the choice that the Black Iron Ghost Triad had taken. He wouldn’t kill them, but, he would completely cripple them. To a martial artist this was a fate far worse than death, especially for the Black Iron Ghost Triad that had done all sorts of evil acts. The three of them had made innumerable enemies in the City of Discord. If they were to lose their cultivations then their fates could be imagined!

“His attack is so strong and ruthless!”

The monster youth was bewildered. In just two moves, this human youth had completely wasted the Black Iron Ghost third brother’s martial arts. This sort of clean and merciless strike was definitely not something that a frail and flowery youth raised in the safety of a great family could do. This was something that only someone who constantly walked on the edge of life and death could accomplish, someone who had killed countless opponents. His skill was extraordinary and the terrifying strength and killing intent hiding within his body was nearly limitless. Although this youth seemed like a modest gentleman most of the time, once he erupted, he was like a bloodthirsty tyrannical beast, savage and brutal!

“Run!”

This thought instantly appeared in the monster youth’s mind. He could no longer care about why Lin Ming was so strong at such a low cultivation. All he knew was that if he didn’t run away right now he would absolutely suffer the same fate as the Black Iron Ghost third brother!

However, as soon as the monster youth made this decision he felt his body shake. An invisible strength had struck him like an arrow and entered into his body, marking his bones and meridians.

“What is this?”

The monster youth was shocked but immediately reacted. “Is this a tracking god rune?”

In the Asura Road, there were many auxiliary god runes; tracking god runes were one of these. Once they were planted they were extremely difficult to resolve. But now, the monster youth could feel that what Lin Ming planted inside his body was not one of these god runes but a self-created tracking mark.

“It isn’t a rune… it is a battle spirit mark, but the effects are the same!”

The monster youth instantly understood what happened. Lin Ming had planted a tracking mark in his body to hunt him down – this was a true Hunter Game! Unfortunately for them who had participated in this game, they were not hunters, they were the prey!

As a monster race martial artist, although his talent in battle spirits couldn’t compare to a human’s, he was still far superior to a saint. He immediately reacted, wanting to erase this battle spirit mark.

However, just as his sense touched upon the battle spirit mark he felt his arms and feet turn cold. This battle spirit mark flickered with a deep blue light, like the purest of blue jades.

This was clearly… a blue soul battle spirit!

“Blue soul battle spirit? Are you fucking joking with me?” The monster youth was horrified. His own battle spirit was only at the elementary gold level and yet he had bumped into a blue soul battle spirit. This couldn’t even be described as hitting a stone with an egg.

Chapter 1437 – One-star Asura

Lin Ming looked at the green furred martial artist. This martial artist looked like a monkey with lustrous green skin that shined like moss. His body was thin and unremarkable. Compared to the handsome monster youth before, this monkey-like martial artist was far less pleasing to the eye. Even so, Lin Ming felt an unusual atmosphere from him.

Lin Ming fell to the ground. The two of them were only a hundred feet away, and they had both locked tightly locked onto each other.

The monster youth’s face was extremely grim. He was revolving his aura to the limit.

“You actually managed to find me…what a freak…”

This monster youth had been hiding in the tall grass from the very start. He had restrained his aura and he was also exceptionally skilled at camouflage, concealment, and sneak attacks. He had long seen Lin Ming flying in the sky, but he hadn’t chased after him. Instead, he hid beneath Lin Ming and waited for the other trial challengers to arrive and circle Lin Ming.

His plan had been to use Lin Ming as bait and tempt more people to gather here. Then, once they were all exhausted from fighting each other, he would enter the fray and take all the profits.

This was the so-called ‘the mantis stalks the cicada while unaware of the bird behind’. The green furred monster youth had made the correct choice and also the wisest choice, however, his one mistake was that he never imagined Lin Ming would be this strong. This Lin Ming had exterminated the Black Iron Ghost Triad at the very start, and his ruthless and merciless tactics left one scared.

Not just that, but Lin Ming had also left a tracking mark on everyone else’s body. This green furred monster was originally a skilled assassin that specializing in concealing himself and tracking others. He naturally recognized that the tracking mark Lin Ming left behind was extremely difficult to undo thus he had remained motionless.

Even so, he had been detected by Lin Ming.

“You’ve been watching for a long time already.” Lin Ming waved the Phoenix Blood Spear. He had already noticed this green furred monster martial artist at the start but had simply been feigning ignorance.

“My concealment technique is difficult to detect for even a Holy Lord or half-step World King…how could you have such sharp perception?”

The green furred monster youth tightly clutched onto a nearly transparent weapon.

This weapon seemed to merge with the space around it, hidden in the void. If one didn’t look carefully it would be difficult to spot.

This was a dagger.

From watching this small monster martial artist fellow in front of him, Lin Ming could feel the deep killing intend hiding in his body. This monster youth was likely some sort of master assassin.

“You’re an assassin? You’re aura is quite strong, much stronger than those seven other people just now. I heard that there was a one-star Asura that participated in this trial; was it you?”

The green furred monster youth remained silent, not answering.

But, Lin Ming was certain that this green furred monster was the sole one-star Asura out of everyone that had come.

In the Asura Road, every person who possessed the title of Asura was strong in their own right. Moreover, the title itself could directly increase their strength.

A one-star Asura could increase a martial artist’s strength by a small boundary.

In other words, a late Divine Lord one-star Asura would be equal to a half-step Holy Lord.

“Very good! I’ve long been wanting to experience just what sort of strength the title of a one-star Asura can grant you. This Hunter Game is something that I must win no matter what.”

Lin Ming didn’t plan on sparing anyone here. Out of the ten plus trial challengers here, he would eliminate them all one at a time, leaving no behind!

Hu – !

Behind Lin Ming, the phantom of the Heretical God Tree appeared. Atop the Heretical God Tree, thunder and flame wove together as a wild energy howled through the air.

A deep blue light lit up on Lin Ming’s Phoenix Blood Spear; this was the light of a blue soul battle spirit.

“Sixth level of the Thunder and Fire Laws as well as a blue soul battle spirit….” The green furred monster youth’s face darkened. If this human youth was truly at the middle Divine Transformation realm, then perhaps he was the top genius of a great race.

The monster race martial artist simply didn’t have enough time to react. Lin Ming was already rushing towards him. Lin Ming’s spear thrust out, causing a terrifying wave of thunder and flame to rise up.

The void shook. The winds and clouds shifted. In an instant, all the tall grass around the green furred monster youth turned into ash and even the swamp around him was scorched black.

Heavenly Dao Judgment!

Bang!

A terrifying explosion swallowed the entirety of space for ten miles. A brilliant flare lit up the heavens, becoming the only light between the heavens and the earth. The monster youth wanted to dodge, but he was caught up and twisted in this horrifying power. His flesh and blood was unable to resist the tyrannical power of thunder and fire and his entire body ignited. In the next moment, he split apart!

“Mm?”

Lin Ming was startled. This green furred monster youth was quite strong; Lin Ming didn’t believe that a single strike would b e able to kill him. Moreover, when that green furred monster youth’s body had blown up in the explosion of thunder and fire, Lin Ming hadn’t felt his soul aura at all.

“This is…a substitute?”

This thought instantly flashed through Lin Ming’s mind. At the same time, he felt a deep killing intent hone in on him. This killing intent was like a sharp needle. Although it seemed common it was incomparably sharp as if it were about to pierce through Lin Ming’s protective true essence.

Without thinking, Lin Ming recklessly released grandmist energy from his inner world.

Grandmist space!

Bang!

As the heavy grandmist energy spread outwards, all space for a radius of a hundred feet turned into an impregnable fortress of absolute space. If an ordinary martial artist were to try to enter they would be directly pressed into goo by the immense pressure of the grandmist space, let alone have any chance to attack.

Ka ka ka!

The monster youth’s dagger slashed out like the claws of a death god. However, after it only cut through three tiny wisps of grandmist energy the speed of his attack rapidly fell and his striking power had also mostly dissipated.

“What!?”

The monster youth was panic-stricken. And at this time, Lin Ming had already reached him.

“There is no place for you to run!”

Xiu!

A brilliant spear light enveloped the monster youth, swallowing all…

…..

…..

At this time, on the second level of Black God Fort, many martial artists were gathered. Some were meditating, some were talking, and some of them were even crowding around Dugu Li, congratulating him.

Dugu Li had an extremely high status. He was close to becoming a two-star Asura, and now that he passed the Hunter Game, his reputation had risen even further.

Just now, a Silver Snow Guard had spoken privately with Dugu Li. For this sort of situation to appear, that likely meant that the City of Discord’s City Lord had extended an offer towards Dugu Li.

Because of Dugu Li’s performance, the City Lord wanted him to enter the Silver Snow Corps!

Once Dugu Li became a direct subordinate of the City Lord then he would be able to receive a salary of origin energy runes every year. This was a wealth that many people were envious of!

Moreover, those from the Silver Snow Guard would be given a free residence within the City of Discord. As long as they didn’t betray the City Lord or didn’t accidently die somewhere, this residence would be theirs for the rest of their lives.

This was a level of treatment that many people could only long for in their dreams.

“Haha, congratulations brother Dugu Li, it seems you will become a Silver Snow Guard soon!”

“Brother Dugu Li, when you enter the City Lord Mansion in the future you must live well. Eat delicious food, drink great wine, and make sure to look after this little brother.”

Many people who were acquaintances of Dugu Li began flattering him en masse. Today, Dugu Li was undoubtedly the hero. As for those other trial challengers that entered the Hunter Game, such as the Black Iron Ghosts, they were only a small entertaining interlude. People looked towards them for some lively fun, but the true attention wasn’t on them.

However, no one thought that at this time, the portal leading to the Hunter Game would suddenly wildly fluctuate.

“Mm? Are some people coming out?”

“How could it be so quick? Not even an incense stick of time has passed since they entered and yet someone’s been eliminated?”

Originally, many people didn’t have much faith in the martial artists that entered the trial. Wanting to pass the checkpoint of the Hunter game was simply far too hard. Now, there was someone that came out in less than an incense stick of time. That absolutely meant that they were eliminated.

Wanting to pass the trial would normally take 14-16 hours.

“Who is it? Is it that human boy with the lowest cultivation…that is just too sad!”

“It might not be him. Sometimes, strength matters less then luck does. There are those that immediately run into some difficult beast as soon as they enter the game world, or they might have their skull badges taken away by another trial challenger and then be directly eliminated.”

Everyone looked towards the portal. Lights flashed from within the portal, then, someone’s figure was shot out.

This person fell straight to the floor like a dead dog, even tumbling for several hundred feet as they left a trail of blood.

The Silver Snow Guard’s figure flashed and he appeared right in front of this person. As soon as the person stopped tumbling, everyone’s eyes fixed onto them. This person’s entire body was wet with blood, their hair was a mess, a large hole was in their chest, and their organs were a utter mess.

“This is…”

“This is too miserable!”

In the City of Discord, there were deaths occurring all day long. The martial artists present had already been long accustomed to these sights so they weren’t surprised at all.

But, after seeing someone enter the Hunter Game in high spirits and with a smug expression, and then seeing them suddenly end up like this, the visual impact of it was very large.

“His clothes are tatters and blood is covering his face. Even his hair is matted with blood. Just who is he? Could he be that Divine Transformation realm human….”

“I recognize him, he’s the Black Iron Ghost Triad’s third brother!”

“It really is the Black Iron third brother! How could it be him!?”

“He’s hanging onto a single breath of life but all of his meridians have shattered and he’s been utterly crippled.” A martial artist said after walking up to check on the Black Iron third brother’s current state.

Looking at the Black Iron third brother’s chest, one could see a massive hole had been pierced through it and the surrounding flesh and skin had been twisted. This was enough to reveal the terrifying strength behind this strike. It could be imagined that when the Black Iron third brother had been struck, this attack had ripped through his protective astral essence and mortal body like wet paper without any resistance at all!

Out of the dozen some people that entered, there were indeed some strong individuals amongst them. However, none of them were strong enough to accomplish this and leave such heavy wounds. It was hard to imagine just what happened.

“It isn’t a beast attack; it is definitely another trial challenger. A beast wouldn’t break someone’s meridians like this.” Someone judged based on the attack technique.

Everyone looked at each other in confusion, not sure what was happening. But at this time, the light of the portal flashed again and a second person was ejected.

“Someone else is coming out!”

Everyone looked over. This second person was in an even more pathetic state then the Black Iron third child. It was like someone had pulled out his spine. This person collapsed on the floor in a puddle as if they were made of liquid meat.

“What a cruel and ruthless technique. His entire spine has been shattered!”

“This person is….mm!? The Black Iron boss!? First it was the Black Iron third brother and now it is the boss…could it be that the Black Iron Ghost Triad offended someone so they were purposefully targeted?”

“The Black Iron boss was already left in such a horrible state with a single strike. The difference in strength was far too great. This other party was truly ruthless; they had the intention of crippling him from the start!”

Chapter 1438 – Clear Out the Trash

“These two have been crippled. The one who did this used some sort of specialized martial skill to break all their meridians and vital points. Even if they have top medicines it will be impossible for them to recover from this.”

As everyone was speaking, the portal flashed again and another person was sent tumbling out.

This was the most miserable-looking person so far.

His entire body was dried up like he had aged to the end of his years. His hair was as thin and sparse as weeds and all of his blood vitality was sucked out.

“Another one! Could this be the Black Iron Ghost Triad’s second brother!?”

“Yes, it seems it’s him.”

The Black Iron Ghost Triad brothers had each come out looking worse than the last. The Black Iron second brother’s entire body was a mess and he seemed as if he would die at any moment. There was only a tiny bit of astral essence in his body that was barely maintaining his life.

“The Black Iron second brother tried to use the Saint Demon Disintegration Art to perish together with his enemy, but for some unknown reason his technique failed and he was the one ruined instead.”

“This is too tragic. Someone must have been targeting the Black Iron Ghost Triad and was likely their personal enemy. This enemy was too strong for them and no matter if they tried to escape or if they tried a suicide attack, nothing they attempted worked.”

“The Black Iron Ghost Triad has made far too many enemies but they wouldn’t be stupid enough to offend someone so strong. Just who could it be?”

As everyone was wondering, the portal flashed for a fourth time.

There was still someone else!?

Everyone looked towards the portal in surprise. The trial had only begun a short time ago and yet people were already being eliminated one after another.

At this time, there was no blood splashing on the floor. The martial artist who was ejected from the portal wasn’t seriously injured. He was still able to walk and had a little bit of combat strength left.

But after seeing who this person was, everyone was shocked speechless.

This person was the only Asura in the dozen some trial challengers.

The one-star Asura – Viper.

He came from a sect of assassins and his nickname in the City of Discord was Viper. This was because he was similar to a viper in his actions. When he decided to kill someone, he would first hide from his prey and then make a fatal strike at the most opportune time. Even those that were stronger than he was weren’t willing to needlessly provoke him because no one wanted to be targeted every day and have to be vigilant against ambushes at all times.

But this person was actually eliminated from the trial in less than two incense sticks of time.

“Viper, you…”

Dugu Li felt this all too unbelievable. “Who defeated you?”

That green-furred monster martial artist called Viper took a deep breath. He seemed as if he didn’t want to speak about what happened, but after a moment of silence he said, “It was that Divine Transformation realm human youth. Under his hands, I wasn’t even able to last for five moves. If he didn’t show mercy towards me then perhaps I would have suffered the same fate as the Black Iron Ghost Triad…”

“Human youth, that Divine Transformation realm human youth?” Dugu Li was left dumbfounded. He couldn’t believe his own ears.

A bit after Viper said these words, he turned around and strode out of Black God Fort without saying a single word more.

Everyone who was left behind had their mouths dropped open, not closing for a long time.

They never thought that four people would be continuously defeated in such a short period of time. And, the one who did so was only a middle Divine Transformation martial artist, the most improbable fellow of all…

……….

At this time, in the dimensional realm where the Hunter Game was being held, three martial artists were floating beneath the gray and dimly lit skies.

Strong winds howled through the world, carrying along the roars of wild beasts. Of these three martial artists, one was Lin Ming and the other two were the couple that had taken him for prey earlier and had wanted to take his skull badge.

Currently, the couple had an extremely ugly expression on their faces, unsightly to the extreme. Although they hadn’t planned on passing the checkpoint this time, they still thought they could experience the Hunter Game and be better prepared for next time. However, they didn’t imagine they would run into this dark star known as Lin Ming, causing them to be eliminated at the very start of the game. Now, those 200,000 origin energy runes were basically wasted.

“Do you want to fight, or will you withdraw yourself?”

Lin Ming calmly said. His voice exuded a great pressure on the couple.

“Che, you are ruthless enough.”

The man unwillingly tossed his spatial ring with the skull badge towards Lin Ming. His wife bit her lips and also followed suit. Like this, the total number of skull badges they had was zero.

After a brief moment, this couple was directly sent out from the dimensional realm and eliminated from the game.

“Seven…”

Lin Ming whispered as he received the skull badges in his hand. He was 93 away from reaching his goal.

As Lin Ming chased the couple he had seen a great number of beasts beneath him that were considered the ‘prey’ of this Hunter Game. Although these prey were extremely weak, he didn’t doubt that they would grow increasingly strong as he gathered more skull badges.

“There is still that monster youth as well as an imp martial artist. Their position is still within my control…”

Lin Ming closed his eyes. Then, his figure flashed as he flew dozens of miles away.

This rapid flight caused a dreadful sonic boom to follow him. The tall grass beneath him was crushed by this tremendous pressure.

“Eighth!”

Lin Ming’s eyes flashed with a cold light and he extracted the Phoenix Blood Spear. Just ten miles away from him was a white-clothed monster youth – Charming.

Charming already knew that Lin Ming would reach him sooner or later. He grasped a four foot long sword, waiting for Lin Ming to come.

“You don’t plan on giving up?” Lin Ming was a bit surprised. Facing his overwhelming killing intent, this Charming was still releasing a powerful fighting spirit.

“If I don’t fight you then how can I be willing to give up! Demon Subduing Killing Array!”

The monster youth waved the long sword in his hands and a massive array formation appeared for several miles around him. He knew that Lin Ming had left a tracking mark in his body thus he had prepared this array formation beforehand.

This idea was quite good. Unfortunately, his opponent was Lin Ming. With a disparity of absolute strength dividing them, this array formation was meaningless.

“Grandmist space, break!”

The moment that Lin Ming rushed into the array formation, the aura of the Grandmist Great Dao erupted from his body, wildly surging outwards.

The star-heavy grandmist energy tore through the array formation’s seals. Lin Ming pushed his way through!

Rumble rumble rumble!

With a horrifying explosion, the giant array formation’s seals were shattered by Lin Ming.

With the protection of the array formation, the monster youth fought with Lin Ming in a fierce battle. But even though he had the advantage of the battlefield, he was barely managing to keep up with Lin Ming’s onslaught.

After all, the array formation he laid down was far inferior to the profundity of the grandmist space.

After exchanging four or five moves, the monster youth was struck by Lin Ming, causing his blood vitality to tumble and make the energy within his body feel as if it wanted to explode.

And then, behind Lin Ming, the phantom of the Heretical God Tree appeared. The crazy power of thunder and fire fell down in torrents, completely tearing the array formation to shreds!

Heavenly Dao Judgment!

Lin Ming’s spear cut out, breaking through space.

In this moment, the monster youth knew that he had lost; the difference in strength was far too great. This wasn’t something that could be made up for with a hastily laid down array formation.

He was originally confident that he could pass this trial during his first attempt, but now, he wasn’t even able to see the shadow of a second skull badge. After being targeted by this dark star Lin Ming, he had been eliminated from the trial…

………

Hu – !

In Black God Fort, the light of the transmission array portal flashed once more. A dejected-looking monster youth left the transmission array. Although he wasn’t injured heavily, his self-confidence had come under tremendous attack.

Lin Ming was far stronger than him and much younger than him. There was no comparing their talent.

As the gathered martial artists saw the monster youth emerge, they were left flabbergasted.

Whether it was the crippled Black Iron Ghost Triad that were on the verge of death or the only one-star Asura, Viper, all of them were more noticeable than this monster youth.

And after that monster youth came out, another person was eliminated in less than half an incense stick of time.

Like this, when the Black Iron Ghost Triad, Viper, and the couple were added together, there were now eight trial challengers that had been eliminated from the Hunter Game!

In other words, within the Hunter Game, besides Lin Ming himself, there were only two or three people left.

The game had only begun a quarter hour ago and just a bit more than two hours had passed in the game world. Yet during this time, eight people had been eliminated. This rate of elimination was far too terrifying.

“This boy cannot possibly be at the Divine Transformation realm.” Someone said. Many martial artists of the Asura Road were limited by what they could see in their own world. They simply didn’t know what levels of talent the peak genius of a race could achieve.

“He truly is at the Divine Transformation realm…” Charming said, shaking his head like he didn’t want to acknowledge this. “It is because he is at the Divine Transformation realm that he decided to eliminate everyone else when the Hunter Game started. That is because our existence there drags the game difficulty to a much higher degree and he doesn’t have the confidence to complete it at such high difficulties… of course, his goal might not just be the blue soul level checkpoint…”

As Charming spoke to here, the several martial artists around him were stunned. If his goal wasn’t the blue soul level checkpoint, then, could it be… the zenith black level checkpoint?

Chapter 1441 – Weakness

36 warriors appeared in front of Lin Ming once more. But this time, they were taller and larger, each of them around 10 feet high. Their golden armor was also a darker, mellower hue, and the strength percolating in their bodies had increased by several times.

Their cultivation was similar to Lin Ming’s, each of them equal to a middle Divine Transformation human martial artist. Not just that, but they had a solid foundation and their blood vitality was booming. If any one of them were chosen, they could have joined the Divine Realm First Martial Meeting and easily advanced into the top 20 spots of the finals.

If these characters were alone then Lin Ming could easily defeat them, even instantly kill them.

But when 36 of them were gathered together to form a large battle array formation, their combat strength increased by many times over. This caused Lin Ming to feel that this situation was becoming increasingly tricky.

Origin energy runes continued to cascade from the skies, burning down all around him.

Then, suddenly, Lin Ming hurtled forwards, the Phoenix Blood Spear in his hands thrusting outwards.

He didn’t wait for these 36 golden-armored warriors to suck up all the power from the burning origin energy runes. He immediately attacked, his target still the same essence gathering system warriors.

The phantom of the Heretical God Tree reappeared behind him. The power of thunder and fire wove together – this first attack was one of his killing moves, Heavenly Dao Judgment!

Spear light split through the void, emitting a horrifying screeching sound. A roiling wave of thunder and fire rolled up all around him, swept around by his spear, forming a massive red and purple vortex as it shot towards a golden-armored warrior!

This golden-armored warrior did not hurry at all. The array diagram beneath his feet began to spin as power poured into his body. At the same time, the 11 other golden-armored warriors behind him stepped forwards, their hands reaching towards the first golden-armored warrior’s back as they pooled their strength together to resist Lin Ming’s spear strike!

Bang!

A crazy collision rang out. The earth shook and cracked, causing countless stones to fly into the skies before they were dissolved into powder by the chaotic energy.

By coordinating their strength, the 12 golden-armored warriors forcefully resisted Lin Ming’s attack.

As Lin Ming saw this, his mind turned cold. He didn’t think it was strange that his Heavenly Dao Judgment wouldn’t be able to break through the array formation; how could this second, stronger version be so easily broken?

But for just 12 golden-armored warriors to resist his attack, this caused a deep sense of crisis to rise in Lin Ming’s heart.

Hu – hu – hu –

At this time, Lin Ming felt the wind behind him begin to howl, killing intent rising from all around him. The other two groups of golden-armored warriors attacked Lin Ming together.

The array diagram sparkled beneath their feet as countless Law runes spun around. Lin Ming grimaced. If he had to receive both of these attacks at once then it would be extremely hard.

The power of space distorted beneath his feet. He instantly used the Space Laws, wanting to teleport away from here.

But at this time, a terrifying power covered him. Lin Ming felt the power of space around him be immediately locked down, rending his Space Laws useless!

“What?”

Lin Ming was surprised. He immediately realised that this strength was the domain he had felt before!

During the first battle this domain had also existed. But, it was completely suppressed by Lin Ming’s grandmist space and was unable to be used.

But during this second battle, this domain was far stronger than before. Even though Lin Ming was using the grandmist space, he still wasn’t able to completely nullify it.

In this critical moment, this domain had bound Lin Ming’s ability to flee through space.

“Damn!”

Seeing two terrifying beams of strength hurtle towards him, Lin Ming grit his teeth and erupted his energy to the limit. The Eight Inner Gates were opened all at once and he used the grandmist space to protect his body. For a time, Lin Ming’s body emitted an endless string of popping explosions as the phantom of an Azure Dragon materialized behind him. With a loud shout, Lin Ming smashed out with his spear, forcefully resisting these two attacks!

Bang!

The void shook, nearly collapsing. Even the star-heavy grandmist energy was torn apart by the terrifying energy. In the final moment, Lin Ming had used the Phoenix Blood Spear to defend against one attack. Then, he used a barrier of protective astral essence and his powerful body granted by the Eight Inner Hidden Gates to withstand the other!

Without any fancy collision, Lin Ming was sent flying hundreds of feet away. Blood tumbled within him, his armor was torn apart, and he was injured all over!

“What a strong attack!”

Lin Ming wiped the blood from the corners of his lips. By relying on his formidable mortal body he had only received minor wounds in that strike just now. But if this were to continue, he simply wouldn’t be a match for the 36 golden-armored warriors.

These small wounds would slowly accumulate over time as his physical strength was exhausted.

As for the golden-armored warriors and their array formation, the origin energy runes burning all around them would constantly supply them with additional energy. Perhaps they could never be exhausted. If he couldn’t break through their formation then no matter how tenacious Lin Ming was or how fast he restored himself, he still wouldn’t be able to avoid defeat.

“This array formation must have a weakness.”

This thought flashed through Lin Ming’s mind. His own Heavenly Dao Judgment had already been blocked by just one group of the golden-armored warriors.

Lin Ming was confident that although his striking power might not be the absolute highest amongst all the top young geniuses of the various races, it was close to that level. If even his attacks didn’t have any effect, just what could anyone else do?

Woosh! Woosh! Woosh!

The 36 golden-armored warriors attacked once more. And at this time, Lin Ming didn’t meet them in a head-on collision. He began to distance himself, relying on his speed to avoid them. As long as he didn’t fall into their domain then it wouldn’t be a problem for him to use his Space Laws to avoid their attacks.

Before he found out the method to break their array formation, Lin Ming didn’t want to waste any more strength.

Like this, the trial had turned into a protracted battle.

And at this time, in the outside world, a full four hours had passed.

Even if Lin Ming’s final battle was in a deadlock, he still used far less time than the other martial artists had.

Lin Ming wasn’t in a hurry. As he dodged, he began to adjust his breathing and frequency at which he absorbed heaven and earth origin energy, reaching a balance between consumption and replenishment.

Slowly, Lin Ming discovered that although these 36 golden-armored warriors belonged to the three great cultivation systems of essence, energy, and divine, there were still different cultivation methods used between all of them.

Amongst the body transformation technique group, there was the saint race’s body transformation technique, the Nine Saint Transformations, the human race’s body transformation technique, the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, and also the monster race’s body transformation technique, Nirvanic Rebirth.

Although the 12 body transformation technique warriors each belonged to a different race, there were differences among each one of them.

Their cultivation methods were each a single one of the Concept of the 33 Layered Heavens. As for these puppets’ attacks, they matched with the postcelestial dao diagram beneath their feet, complementing each other in an impregnable and impeccable manner.

“What wonderful skills. To form this type of array, perhaps the one who did so was the supreme elder who created the Asura Road. They must have mastered 33 types of cultivation Laws, or perhaps… it was 36 kinds!”

Lin Ming focused his eyes on the leaders of the three groups of golden-armored warriors. His original assumption had been that the saints, humans, and spiritas were the strongest of the three great system thus they had to be the leaders. But now, it seemed that he was wrong.

The leader of the body transformation system warriors was not a saint and the leader of the essence gathering system warriors was not a human. The three leaders among the 36 golden-armored warriors were an even purer form of energy than the rest.

This was particularly true for the golden-armored warrior that led the soul forging system group. Lin Ming could feel a familiar aura from him…

It seemed as if this were… mm?

Lin Ming was shocked. This aura actually seemed similar to the Magic Cube!

This thought flashed through Lin Ming’s mind. Then, after several more breaths of time, he finally understood. The reason that the golden-armored warrior array formation was composed of 36 individuals and not 33 individuals was because not only did this array formation represent the foundation of the 33 Layered Heavens, but also the Magic Cube, Demon Bead, and the mysterious Purple Card that he had yet to hear any news about.

Within the 33 Layered Heavens, essence, energy, and divine each corresponded to 11 different Heavens. Moreover, there was a divine object that corresponded to them too. These were the Magic Cube, Demon Bead, and Purple Card. According to what Divine Dream had said, the Magic Cube, Demon Bead, and Purple Card each represented a single layered heaven, a universe unto itself.

It was only that these divine objects had yet to evolve. They were considered ‘universe seeds’!

If these three divine objects could evolve into a true universe, then there might be 36 Layered Heavens instead. This was the principle which this array formation came from.

Thus, the three leading warriors of the three groups did not belong to any race, but were instead pure energy bodies.

After realizing all of this and looking at the array formation of the 36 golden-armored warriors once more, Lin Ming suddenly had an inspiration. If he wasn’t wrong, then even though these three leading warriors were the strongest points of the array formation, they were also where its weakness lay.

As long as he could block these three warriors from interacting with the other 33 warriors, then Lin Ming would only need a single breath of time.

After realizing this, Lin Ming’s blood began to boil over with fighting spirit.

After he dodged several continuous attacks, he then hurtled himself towards these three groups.

This time, the one he targeted was the not essence gathering system group, but the soul forging group! This was also the group which resonated with the Magic Cube!

Amongst the three groups of golden-armored warriors, Lin Ming was most familiar with the essence gathering system. But in terms of only the leader, Lin Ming’s familiarity with the Magic Cube had reached the same as his own flesh and blood.

“God Forbidding Seal!”

In just a fraction of an instant, Lin Ming formed thousands of seals!

The black hole seed was summoned by Lin Ming. The surrounding heaven and earth origin energy began to rush towards him, forming a dark gray vortex. Tens of thousands of God Forbidding Seals began hurtling towards the 12 warriors of the soul forging system!

Lin Ming no longer attacked the golden-armored warriors themselves but the energy connections between them. He could already see that they were freely exchanging energy through the array diagram beneath their feet. As long as he could sunder this connection, he could instantly strike down the leader of the soul forging system warriors.

“Seal!”

The God Forbidding Seals were in essence miniature black holes. They had the ability to swallow all and seal away all. For a time, countless energy routes were severed between the golden-armored warriors!

But these golden-armored warriors clearly had some sort of wisdom. They seemed to understand Lin Ming’s plan and began to immediately attack the God Forbidding Seals, wanting to destroy them all.

At the same time, the other two groups of golden-armored warriors also attacked Lin Ming!

Lin Ming ignored them all. From within his inner world, a gray stone door appeared.

This stone door was originally the size of a book, but as it appeared it began to rapidly increase in size. Above the stone door, a series of mystical patterns and runes appeared, circulating all around it as if they contained the most ancient of secrets.

This was the Primordius Gate.

“Suppression!” Lin Ming shouted out loud. With a loud explosive sound, the massive Primordius Gate came slamming down, cutting off the energy connections and also resisting a great number of attacks.

The attacks of the many golden-armored warriors were originally extremely fierce and sharp. But as these attacks struck the Primordius Gate they were like hail striking a steel plate, unable to do anything at all.

At the same time, Lin Ming attacked. His target was the leader of the soul forging system warriors!

Chapter 1442 – Clearing the Trial

Lin Ming’s attack was deliberately and carefully planned. He poured in all of his strength, even opening the Gate of Life and burning his blood essence without hesitation. With the Gate of Life as a foundation he could freely burn a part of his blood essence without permanent loss. However, this only lasted for a short period of time, and after he did this he wouldn’t be able to use it for a long time afterwards, otherwise he would permanently damage himself.

Thus, Lin Ming wouldn’t use this move unless he had to. And now, Lin Ming had used this ability to allow his striking power to reach the limit, in order to achieve a one-shot kill!

He only had one chance to attack. This was because he could feel that these golden-armored warriors had a mind of their own. After one defeat, they would be on guard for his attack and wouldn’t fall for it a second time.

Ca!

Seven or eight energy channels were disrupted by the God Forbidding Seals!

And the Primordius Gate also blocked the attacks of the other two groups of golden-armored warriors.

Like this, the golden-armored warrior leader in front of him fell into an isolated state, cut off from most others. There was less than a handful of other golden-armored warriors that were able to help him.

Beneath the golden-armored warrior leader’s helmet, a flash of cold brilliance shined from his eyes. With a howling sound, a viridian soul sword shot out from between his eyebrows!

This soul sword seemed to consume a great deal of the golden-armored warrior leader’s strength. After bringing forth this soul sword his eyes dimmed downed to near darkness.

At the same time, Lin Ming had already summoned the black hole seed from within his inner world. In that instant, all of the surrounding heaven and earth origin energy began crazily gathering towards this black hole seed!

Even the origin energy runes that were providing power to the array formation were sucked into the black hole seed.

Eternal Darkness!

Ka ka ka ka!

The earth ruptured as countless rocks were swept up by wild waves of energy, shooting into the skies. This was the strongest attack Lin Ming could currently use.

Underneath the impact of this tyrannical energy, the Magic Cube within Lin Ming’s body began to faintly stir.

After reaching the Divine Transformation realm Lin Ming had gained the ability to partially activate the Magic Cube. Now, as he used Eternal Darkness, he also began to activate the Magic Cube’s power!

Lin Ming’s target was the soul forging system warrior, and the Magic Cube was the ultimate nemesis of all souls and minds!

The Magic Cube itself didn’t appear, but the aura that belonged to it spread out, covering the 12 golden-armored warriors!

The golden-armored warrior leader suddenly shook and the soul sword that he had shot towards Lin Ming exploded into flashing shards before vanishing. Not just that, but the golden-armored warrior seemed to suffer some sort of massive backlash as the light that surrounded its body began to wildly fluctuate.

Without the support of its fellow warriors, the golden-armored warrior leader was far weaker than Lin Ming, much less now that Lin Ming was also using the Magic Cube!

“It’s over!”

Lin Ming coldly shouted. The Phoenix Blood Spear as well as the black hole seed came crashing down.

Peng!

With a loud explosion, the golden-armored warrior shattered into countless fragments. And these fragments were also swept up by the black hole seed, disappearing from sight!

He had broken through!

Lin Ming let out a long breath. Now that he had struck down that golden-armored warrior, it basically meant he had thoroughly won and completed this trial.

Just as Lin Ming was about to follow up his attacks, he suddenly paused. After the black hole seed absorbed all those broken light fragments, those light fragments actually gathered together to form deep blue god runes that separated from the black hole seed, slowly spinning in the air.

A black hole had infinite gravitational strength; it was even able to swallow light. At a black hole singularity, space and time also came to a terminal end. It could be said that the Black Hole Laws dominated these Laws.

But, these blue god runes calmly floated out from the black hole seed. This entire scene appeared simple and easy, as if the massive gravitational force of the black hole seed didn’t even exist.

This caused Lin Ming to suck in a cold breath of air. He had no idea what boundary the senior who created the Asura Road had reached, but even after billions of years or tens of billions of years, the god runes he casually left behind as a legacy actually contained such wonderful principles behind them.

However, he had no time to probe these Laws further. The battle had still not ended!

Lin Ming revolved his strength to the limit, stimulating the Magic Cube once more as he attacked the soul forging system warriors!

Now that they had lost their leader, the remaining 11 golden-armored warriors were in a state of disorganized chaos.

At this time, the power of Lin Ming’s burnt blood essence had yet to disappear. With the Magic Cube supporting him, he was like a tiger amongst a flock of sheep!

The Phoenix Blood Spear swept out as the black hole seed recklessly swallowed all energy.

One by one, the golden-armored warriors were swept up in his attacks and shattered into fragments. These fragments of light slowly gathered, forming god runes.

These god runes were all blue, meaning they were blue soul level god runes.

The second group of golden-armored warriors was much stronger than the first. Even though their array formation was torn apart, their individual strength couldn’t be looked down upon.

Lin Ming opened the Eight Inner Hidden Gates once more. With the power of the black hole seed he was able to engage in a fierce melee with them. He went on a complete offensive barrage, resisting the attacks of the other golden-armored warriors with his body. Every time he attacked he would aim for their weakest point, instantly killing them!

Less and less golden-armored warriors remained, and more and more god runes floated in the air.

Most of the names of these god runes had a prefix – the 33 Layered Heavens.

“33 Layered Heavens’ Nine Stars of the Dao Palace!”

“33 Layered Heavens’ Nine Divine Shifts!”

“33 Layered Heavens’ Nirvanic Rebirth!”

“33 Layered Heavens’ Nine Revolution Rebirth!”

…..

Each Concept condensed into a single rune. After Lin Ming killed off the remaining golden-armored warriors, all of them had become runes!

There were a total of 36 runes.

These 36 runes were all blue in color. They slowly floated in the air before dividing into two groups.

One group had 33 runes, and one group had three runes.

These two groups of runes began to fuse together in the sky, condensing into their final rune forms.

And the center of these runes were a deep black-red color. In other words, they were zenith black runes!

This was just like Soulwhite had said. When a complete set of runes combined together, they could sometimes rise to an even higher level.

These two runes, without any indication, began to fall down towards Lin Ming.

Woosh! Woosh!

The runes entered Lin Ming’s body without him resisting at all. He allowed it to freely occur. The moment that these runes fused into his flesh and blood, Lin Ming felt as if his soul was touched. Then, the complete information of these two god runes was transmitted to his mind.

These two runes were respectively called the Protection of God and the Blessing of God.

The former came about by fusing 33 runes together. This god rune could directly increase a martial artist’s combat strength.

As for the latter, its function was quite unique. It didn’t increase one’s combat strength, but its usefulness far surpassed the first god rune. This second god rune was used to increase the height of one’s destiny. If one possessed it, then one could turn the dangers of mystic realms into fortunes, turning bad luck into good.

“This Blessing of God…”

As Lin Ming realized what the use of this Blessing of God was, his thoughts stirred. He had some faint associations in his mind…

Chapter 1446 – Ancient Jade

After the events at Black God Fort, the entire City of Discord was placed on high alert.

When the City Lord learned that Lin Ming had escaped, he used a thousand mile sound transmission to inform the guards to start the great array formation and seal up the city.

The City Lord did this because he thought Lin Ming might not have necessarily left the City of Discord. If he searched the city he might be able to make some gains.

And, more importantly, the City Lord wanted to place a total blockade on all news. He then scanned the log book for that day in Black God Fort and captured all the martial artists that had appeared there, imprisoning them all!

Then, each one of these people had soul searching god runes used on them to comb through their memories. If any one of them had passed on news to others, those other people would also be equally captured and imprisoned. Then, they would have memory sealing god runes placed within them.

This sort of crazy method reflected the tyrannical rules of the Asura Road. Here, strength was everything. With strength, one could ignore all public opinion and do whatever they wished. As for things like mercy or benevolence, that was simply a joke.

The reason for blocking this news was to prevent other top masters from joining the hunt for Lin Ming.

Normal martial artists wouldn’t know just how valuable the thing Lin Ming obtained was. They only went to look for the fun of it; even the silver-armored guard captain was the same. Although he knew that what Lin Ming obtained was rare, he didn’t know just what it meant.

But, just because these ordinary martial artists didn’t know what it meant didn’t mean that the other City Lords didn’t. If this news spread out and other City Lords decided to join in on the action, it would be far more difficult for the City of Discord’s City Lord to capture Lin Ming.

At this time, Lin Ming was completely unaware of all the changes occurring within the City of Discord. He had already fled 50,000 miles north.

Here was a forested mountain range. Lin Ming carved his own cave dwelling in this mountain range and temporarily went into seclusion.

He had already changed to a completely different appearance.

He wore a black robe made from energy, and he was of medium height with average, ordinary looks. His complexion was a bit yellower and his chin a bit pointier. His eyes drooped a little and he looked completely common, like someone you wouldn’t notice in a crowd.

Now that he needed to escape, the more low key his appearance was the better.

The reason Lin Ming was able to flee this calamity was all because he cultivated the Divine Dream Law’s Bodily Rebirth Technique to a high enough boundary. Not only could he easily change his appearance but he could also change the aura of his soul. Even a Great World King wouldn’t be able to easily see through his camouflage.

When he had planned to leave Divine Dream Heavenly Palace to go on an adventure and temper himself, the first place he chose was not the Asura Road but the Saint Convocation Heaven where the saint race ruled supreme!

Lin Ming had dared to go to the Saint Convocation Heaven because he was able to rely on the Bodily Rebirth Technique.

Just from this alone, Lin Ming felt a heartfelt admiration towards Divine Dream. She had actually managed to research the soul forging system to such a refined degree and establish her profound Divine Dream Law.

Of course, that ordinary Holy Lord level spiritas guard captain wasn’t able to easily see through Lin Ming’s disguise, and part of the reason for that was also because of the Magic Cube. The Magic Cube had allowed Lin Ming to understand the Divine Dream Law to such a degree that he nearly reached Frost Dream’s level of talent.

“It looks I won’t be able to use my original appearance anymore. Then, I’ll use this appearance to continue participating in the Asura Road trials. It should be safe enough.”

Lin Ming had confidence in his own appearance changing technique. Even if he were to stand in front of the City Lord himself, the City Lord wouldn’t be able to recognize him. Only an Empyrean would be able to see through his disguise.

Now that the dangers had abated, Lin Ming focused on his right hand. He wanted to see just what it was he drew.

Whatever it was, he had risked his life to obtain it. Moreover, it was something that hadn’t been seen for several hundreds of millions of years. It shouldn’t be too bad.

A faint green light appeared in Lin Ming’s right hand, slowly gathering together. Finally, it formed a green jade.

Lin Ming looked at this jade. It was a deep green and the size of a baby’s palm, just like a jade pendant.

The surface of the jade had strange carvings on it. Compared to the complex language of the Divine Realm or saint race, this sort of writing was far simpler, only comprised of four strokes.

Lin Ming looked at the jade for half a day. He couldn’t recall anything about these characters.

“Just what is this… there isn’t any explanation at all…”

Lin Ming couldn’t understand just what effect this ancient jade had. All he could feel from this ancient jade was a vague primal aura, as if it had existed for countless years. However, even after hundreds of millions or even billions of years, this jade remained clean and bright. As he held it in his hands, there was even a slightly warm feeling.

“Perhaps it can be used when opening the final trial?”

Lin Ming thought out loud. Just as he was preparing to place it in the Magic Cube space, a sudden spiritual message flashed in his mind. This message had no words, but it still managed to transmit some blurry information to him.

Lin Ming’s mind stirred and he poured his divine sense into the ancient jade. Immediately, he could see some faint lines within the ancient jade. These lines formed a complex design. As Lin Ming looked at it, he could feel that it was somewhat similar to a map.

And all around this map were blurry comments. As for these words, Lin Ming was able to understand them. They consisted of the Divine Realm’s language as well as the saint race’s language.

During the period of time after Lin Ming came into contact with the saints and the spiritas, he slowly studied their language. A martial artist had photographic memory and it wasn’t too much of a hassle to learn a new language, especially for someone with peerless perception like Lin Ming.

“Great Desolate God Trove…”

Lin Ming slowly read the words, one at a time.

“Soulwhite, do you know what the Great Desolate God Trove is?”

Soulwhite emerged from Lin Ming’s Extreme Violet Ring, slightly startled. “Great Desolate God Trove? This old servant does not know, but I have heard of the Great Desolate before. That is an extremely large area in the Asura Road, a completely wild and savage wilderness region. Many martial artists go there to temper themselves, but even they only journey around the edges. As for the depths of the Great Desolate, no one dares to go that far. In its depths, there are powerful ancient desolate beasts and even God Beasts. Moreover, there is quite a number of them!

“It is said that there are numerous rare and hidden treasures in the Great Desolate. If one is lucky enough, if your destiny defies the heavens, then you may even find bones of long dead God Beasts. That is a land filled with immense lucky chances but it is also extremely dangerous. Those who go there are always hanging onto life by a thread, with nine chances of death and only one chance of survival.”

Lin Ming sucked in a cold breath as he heard Soulwhite’s description.

God Beast…

Up until now, Lin Ming had only seen two God Beasts with his own eyes.

The first was the Black Dragon in the Eternal Demon Abyss, and the second was Empyrean Demondawn’s contract beast.

A normal God Beast was slightly weaker than an Empyrean. But, there were some God beasts with powerful bloodlines and inherited strengths that were able to compare favorably with peak Empyrean powerhouses!

In terms of strength, Empyrean Demondawn’s God Beast and the Black Dragon in the Eternal Demon Abyss were on completely different levels.

Although Lin Ming had never seen the Black Dragon within the Eternal Demon Abyss fight, he could confirm that it was no weaker than Empyrean Primordius was in the past. Otherwise, it would have been impossible for the Black Dragon to fight side-by-side with Empyrean Primordius.

In this Great Desolate there really might be a god trove. And, the lines in this ancient jade might be the map to that ancient ruin.

As Soulwhite saw Lin Ming develop the idea of going to the Great Desolate, he hurriedly discouraged him. “Master, with your cultivation it is far too early for you to go to the Great Desolate. That place is different from the world of the Hunter Game. The Hunter Game is only a trial and its difficulty is determined by your cultivation. However, the Great Desolate is different. That is the true world, where only your strength matters. I believe that master should instead look at that rare blue soul level mission first. Still, a blue soul level mission isn’t easy to complete either. There are many two-star Asuras that form teams in order to complete blue soul level missions.

“Mm…”

Lin Ming nodded. It was true; his strength was a bit too low right now. He might as well finish the rare blue soul level mission first.

Lin Ming took out the blue soul level mission badge and poured his divine sense into it. Then, a piece of information spread through his mind.

“Precipice Cliff, leave a name upon the Emperor Stone.”

This short sentence was the so-called mission.

“What sort of place is Precipice Cliff?” Lin Ming asked.

Soulwhite ruefully smiled as he heard this. He said, “What a coincidence. Precipice Cliff is also at the Great Desolate, but it is located at the edges. It isn’t too dangerous there.”

“Oh? So it seems no matter what, I’ll need to take a trip to the Great Desolate. Is this Emperor Stone located on this Precipice Cliff?”

The aim of this mission was clearly to have Lin Ming go to the Great Desolate and leave his name upon the Emperor Stone. At the very least he had to leave some sort of symbol.

Lin Ming guessed that this Emperor Stone likely had some sort of array formation. Once this array formation came into contact with his mission badge, the mission badge would turn into a god rune, the rare blue soul level god rune he would obtain from this mission.

After Lin Ming understood the mission details, he spent several days in his cave dwelling adjusting himself. After he reached his best state, he left.

Destination – the Great Desolate!

Chapter 1450 – This Place Shall be Your Grave

In Xiao Moxian’s mind, the figure of Lin Ming inevitably appeared. Whether it was the power of thunder and fire or the Grandmist Laws, those were all abilities utilized by Lin Ming. This was especially true for the Grandmist Laws; very few people understood them. If one wished to learn them they would need an abnormally high perception in order to perceive the Grandmist Laws from chaos stones. After all, in this universe grandmist energy had nearly disappeared.

Even so, Xiao Moxian couldn’t confirm that this youth in front of her was Lin Ming based on those abilities alone. In the end, this was the Asura Road and not the Divine Realm.

Xiao Moxian didn’t know that Lin Ming had come to the Asura Road, and that Divine Dream, in order to protect Lin Ming, had kept his whereabouts an absolute secret. In addition, there were countless martial artists from the various universes here that studied every Law possible, so someone appearing that was similar to Lin Ming could occur.

Lin Ming’s attacks became increasingly ruthless. He revolved his strength to the limit with every move, each move bearing down more and each move aiming to take a life. He was even stronger than Xiao Moxian. By himself in a one against three situation, he managed to suppress the three Wave Saints!

In terms of striking power the Four Wave Saints were powerful, and if they were to fight three against one, they shouldn’t have been placed in such a disadvantageous position. However, Lin Ming had the Primordius Gate withstanding attacks for him.

The Primordius Gate was like an indestructible aegis. No matter how wild or brutal the attacks were, the impact would only cause a slight tremble.

“Let’s break through this gate first!” The Wave Boss shouted out with a true essence sound transmission.

“How do we break it? Even a World King wouldn’t be able to do anything to it. This stone gate must be an Empyrean spirit treasure!” Another one of the Wave Saints said. Out of the three of them still standing, their Third Wave Brother had already been severely wounded by Lin Ming’s Heavenly Dao Judgment. Even speaking caused him to vomit blood.

“That’s right, it is because it is an Empyrean spirit treasure that this boy shouldn’t have been able to completely refine it! According to common sense, it should also be impossible for him to move this stone gate. It must be because this stone gate has a spirit of its own that is allowing the boy to control it. Even so, without the absolute control of a martial artist, this stone gate is in the end nothing but a lifeless object. As long as we can overcome this stone gate then we will win!”

The Wave Boss said. Then, he suddenly pulled out a black ghost banner and tossed it into the skies.

This ghost banner rose up with the wind, drawing demonic words in the air!

Wu – wu – wu –

Sad and shrill cries echoed out from the ghost banner. All sorts of resentful spirits began to stream out it. These spirits were personally killed by the Wave Boss and enslaved by him before being sealed into the ghost banner. Once they were taken out, their pained resentment soared to the heavens.

These resentful spirits gushed out like a tide. They didn’t attack Lin Ming but instead rushed towards the Primordius Gate!

“Mm?”

Lin Ming’s eyebrows shot up. This sort of tactic was a bit surprising.

Hu –

A massive number of tortured spirits screamed out, hurtling towards the stone gate without a care for their existence!

The Primordius Gate contained the aura of the Grandmist Laws. Once these spirits rushed towards it they would be torn apart by the Grandmist Laws. However, they continued on no matter the cost, tens and hundreds of thousands of them wrapping around the Primordius Gate!

As the Wave Boss saw the resentful spirits he refined perishing in droves, he felt his heart drip with blood. But at this time, he didn’t have the luxury to care about it anymore.

As long as he killed this youth, he could obtain his treasures. Moreover, he would be able to obtain that charming young woman and her zenith black level reward!

This was a great temptation. With these treasures he could leap up to the heavens in a single bound!

“Take this opportunity to attack him!”

The Wave Saints shouted out loud. Runes began to shimmer all over their bodies; these were the god runes unique to the Asura Road!

The god runes of the Asura Road, besides the special functions they had, could greatly increase a martial artist’s strength every time a complete set was gathered.

“Master, be careful! These people have gathered three sets of gold runes and half a set of blue soul runes. They are considered the highest peak two-star Asuras and can enjoy the blessings of heightened strength from the Asura Road!”

Soulwhite warned from within Lin Ming’s spatial ring.

Lin Ming’s eyebrows arched up. This situation was becoming somewhat tricky. These Wave Saints were originally skilled to begin with, and now with the god runes increasing their strength they would become even more difficult to deal with. It wasn’t a problem for Lin Ming to fight a weak Holy Lord, but now there were three of them, all stronger than average. If Lin Ming wanted to kill them all off then that would be difficult.

After all, as long as they separated and escaped then there wouldn’t be anything that he could do. If he couldn’t eliminate them all here then they would reveal Xiao Moxian’s location, bringing about even greater troubles!

Dealing with several weak Holy Lords was already Lin Ming’s limit. If he had to deal with a World King then there was no chance for him to win.

Moreover, because those resentful spirits had wrapped themselves around the Primordius Gate, it would be hard for him to move it for some time. This was the weakness of him being unable to completely refine the Primordius Gate. Because of that, he was only able to treat the Primordius Gate as a shield and not as the immeasurably powerful Empyrean spirit treasure that it was. Otherwise, if Lin Ming had fully refined it then he would have been able to erupt the energy contained within with just a thought and cause all those hateful spirits to disintegrate instantly.

“Master, you also have god runes. Although they aren’t complete they are still zenith black level runes. If you summon their power within your body with an arcane technique then you can also increase your strength. Rising half a small boundary in strength shouldn’t be a problem at all.

“Oh?”

Lin Ming was surprised. The two runes could increase his strength by half a small boundary?

Lin Ming was already at the peak of the middle Divine Transformation realm. If he increased his cultivation by half a small boundary then that would almost be the equivalent of entering the late Divine Transformation realm!

“The Asura Road takes god runes as manifestations of the Laws and they are things created by the Asura Road Master. The zenith black runes that Master obtained are extremely rare. Using them to rise half a small boundary shouldn’t be a problem at all.”

As Soulwhite spoke, Lin Ming had already started pouring his true essence into the god runes. For a time, from between his eyebrows and on his right hand, faint red-black runes began to shine.

Black and red were the colors of zenith black runes!

As the Wave Saints saw Lin Ming’s body began to radiate a black and red light, they were shocked.

“This is…”

“Zenith black runes? How is that possible!?”

Zenith black runes were normally something that only City Lord level characters possessed. Moreover, the zenith black runes they had were usually of a lower realm. But, the two zenith black runes shining on Lin Ming’s body both blazed with a divine light, emitting an extraordinary and terrifying aura.

Behind Lin Ming, Xiao Moxian also saw the bright shimmer of these zenith black runes. She had already been at the Asura Road for long enough that she understood what this red and black light meant.

“Who is he?”

Xiao Moxian’s large eyes widened until they were like brilliant black gems. She couldn’t stop looking at Lin Ming as she took an increasing interest towards him.

She really wanted to know what the answers to her questions were but she didn’t ask. Xiao Moxian had a childlike innocence and naiveté. The more she wanted to know something the less she would ask about it. Instead, she would investigate herself; only then was it fun.

“This brat!”

The Wave Saints felt the situation become increasingly messy. This boy was so young and yet he possessed zenith black level runes. They suspected that Lin Ming had an unfathomably deep background.

However, they had already tossed their lives into the ring and it was impossible for them to retreat. The greater background a person had the more ruthless they had to be in utterly exterminating them. They didn’t even think that Lin Ming would ever let them go.

“Attack together! We must kill him!”

The Wave Saints drew out their sabers and attacked. Three sabers gathered as one, their strength instantly increasing by several times. They joined together the power from the god runes as they attacked Lin Ming; this was their strongest attack!

“Line of the Deep Sea!”

A terrifying power erupted, rushing forth like a raging tsunami. From behind the Wave Saints, the sea monster phantom that attacked Xiao Moxian appeared once more, hurtling towards Lin Ming.

“Master, be careful!”

Soulwhite cried out in alarm. Although Lin Ming was talented, his cultivation was simply too low. If he had to resist the strongest attack of these Wave Saints that were two large boundaries higher in cultivation than he was, then that was simply a crazy decision.

Xiao Moxian was also worried for Lin Ming. Without caring for the exhaustion that wracked her body, she slashed out her whip, hoping to reduce the pressure on him.

As for Lin Min Ming, he remained calm and unhurried.

His soul force reached into his inner world and a dark gray light howled out!

“Your tactics were good, but unfortunately, I have more than this stone gate.”

As Lin Ming spoke, there was a loud metallic ring, a gong that originated from the most primeval era, bringing with it the endless breath of the Great Dao Laws. A heavy and ancient bell suddenly fell down from up high, covering Lin Ming within it.

This ancient bell exuded a vast and boundless aura. The surface of the bell was carved with images of flowers and creatures, phoenixes and dragons, leviathans and rocs, and even dao patterns similar to those of chaos stones.

This was the Primordius Bell, another one of the Empyrean spirit treasures that Empyrean Primordius had left behind for Lin Ming. When Lin Ming first entered Primordius Palace, he had knelt in front of this ancient bell for three years, fully perceiving the highest truths of the Great Dao contained within, using this bell to directly refine the Primordius martial intent!

The attacks of the Wave Saints completely fell onto the Primordius Bell!

Clang!

The Primordius Bell was rung by the attacks of the three people. A visible sound wave radiated out in response, causing space to tremble. Within this horrifying bell sound, everything was crushed.

Wherever the sound wave went, the ground collapsed and mountains were destroyed. The Wave Saints bore the brunt of this attack. Their blood swelled up within their bodies, tumbling about, nearly causing them to fall from the skies!

Their saber lights as well as that roaring sea monster had all completely exploded into bits, turning into nothing.

Not only had their attacks failed against Lin Ming, but they had been struck by the sound wave of the Primordius Bell, causing them to suffer a severe wound from the backlash!

“What do we do!”

“What kind of magic tool is this!?”

A trace of blood spilled out of the Wave Boss’ mouth. With great difficulty he suppressed the roiling blood within his body. But at this time, he saw a giant bell come falling down on him from above.

In the next moment, they were all covered inside of that ancient bell.

“This is bad!”

The Wave Boss was bewildered. Without a doubt, this ancient bell was also an Empyrean spirit treasure!

Just by attacking it, the reverberating shockwave had caused such massive damage. If someone were actually able to activate this ancient bell then they could likely extinguish a person’s body and soul!

“Push away this bell and fly away! It’s impossible for this human boy to truly control this bell; it must also be a lifeless object! As long as we don’t strike it we won’t suffer a backlash.”

The Wave Boss instantly judged. As a Holy Lord level powerhouse, he had a rich depth of combat experience.

But at this moment, the space in front of them distorted and a black-caped youth stepped out!

Lin Ming had actually entered the space covered by the Primordius Bell. Now, within this mere 100 foot radius of space, there were four people!

What sort of concept was 100 feet to a top master? That was the same as being face to face!

“None of you will leave here! This place shall be your graveyard!”

Lin Ming’s expression was coldly indifferent as he raised the Phoenix Blood Spear.

Chapter 1456 – This Is It?

Precipice Cliff. As the name suggested, it was a precipice on the edge of the Great Desolate.

This precipice was 36 miles high and as smooth as a mirror, without any curve at all.

The only roughness on this precipice were the marks left behind by other powerhouses.

If one wished to leave behind their mark on Precipice Cliff, it required more than cultivation alone. They had to be an outstanding genius amongst all geniuses.

At this time it was the thick of night. The silver moon hung high in the sky, reflecting a crystalline sheen upon the smooth wall of Precipice Cliff, as if the entire land was shrouded in liquid mercury. It was a beautiful sight.

This was an important stop at the Great Desolate because Precipice Cliff itself was a wonderful safe zone. It exuded a faint pressure and aura of a great emperor, making it so that no vicious beasts dared to approach. Because of this, many martial artists came to Precipice Cliff to rest and adjust their condition.

This was one of the few safe zones in the entire Great Desolate.

“Haha, we’ve finally arrived at Precipice Cliff.

Monster Prince Duyu smiled. “This Precipice Cliff is a divine treasure of the Great Desolate; it is said that it is related to the Asura Road Master. If one can leave their mark upon Precipice Cliff then they can obtain the destiny of an emperor; it will be greatly beneficial to your future growth. Junior-apprentice Sister, since we’re here, we must leave our mark upon Precipice Cliff so it can be recorded for all posterity.”

As Monster Prince Duyu spoke, he readied himself to fly up Precipice Cliff. However, he was stopped by Lin Ming.

“Hold on.”

“Mm? What are you doing?” Monster Prince Duyu frowned, looking towards Lin Ming.

“I think it might be better if you change your appearance. Although you said no one knows where you are, this is Precipice Cliff, one of the common trial areas for new young elites in the Asura Road. Don’t you think there might be an ambush here? With so many people around, you might be noticed by some more ambitious individuals.”

Xiao Moxian didn’t tell Lin Ming just why she was being chased by others. Although she didn’t state it, he had already guessed the approximate reason.

“Appearance changing? Have you?”

Xiao Moxian’s thoughts stirred. A sly look entered her large eyes as she glanced over at Lin Ming.

As Lin Ming saw that interest flash through Xiao Moxian’s eyes, he was a bit embarrassed. He knew that Xiao Moxian had some guesses about who he was, or at least suspected it.

“Why are you looking at me like that?” Lin Ming awkwardly said after Xiao Moxian stared at him for a full ten breaths of time.

Beside Xiao Moxian, Monster Prince Duyu was actually filled with jealousy. Although this junior-apprentice sister of his never disregarded the opposite sex, she had never revealed such interest in anyone. This Lin Lanjian was ordinary in appearance and background, so what qualifications did he have to attract his junior-apprentice sister?

“I’m looking at you because you remind me of someone.”

Xiao Moxian blinked her eyes, her gaze still locked onto Lin Ming’s face.

“Oh? Are they your friend?” Lin Ming abashedly replied. In truth, he didn’t have any deliberate plan to conceal his identity from Xiao Moxian. But, Xiao Moxian didn’t seem to be the most reliable of people, and there was also the hostile Monster Prince Duyu. With him here, he definitely couldn’t reveal himself.

“Not a friend. I wouldn’t mind beating him up if I saw him, but maybe… I wouldn’t be able to beat him.”

Xiao Moxian giggled, revealing her cute little canines.

“Uh…” Lin Ming was dumbfounded. He wasn’t sure if Xiao Moxian was joking or not, but it seemed that she still held her defeat at the First Martial Meeting close to her heart.

Then, there was a small interlude as Lin Ming helped Xiao Moxian and Monster Prince Duyu change their appearance. His Bodily Rebirth Technique was itself a sort of spiritual illusion that could be applied to others. However, when he performed it on others he could only change their appearance and not their soul aura. It wouldn’t be enough to conceal them from a Great World King.

However, Lin Ming also believed that the World King level City Lords wouldn’t personally run out from their cities to lie in ambush for Xiao Moxian.

After reaching the bottom of Precipice Cliff, Lin Ming discovered that there were three or four groups of people already waiting.

The Asura Road was extremely large and yet there was only a single Precipice Cliff. Every day there would be many martial artists coming here in order to try and leave their name.

“It is said that it is common for people to receive missions to leave a name on Precipice Cliff, but there actually aren’t many who can do this.”

A martial artist said from the base of Precipice Cliff.

“Hey, what do you mean it is common? Leaving a name on Precipice Cliff is a rare mission and many people can’t obtain such a mission badge. Those that can are definitely ruthless individuals with considerable abilities. It’s only because the Asura Road is so large that there are people coming here every day, making it seem that this mission is a bit more common.”

“Even outstanding individuals might not be able to leave their name behind.”

As everyone was speaking, they were looking up at the high Precipice Cliff. However, no one actually moved.

After all, they only had a single chance. Once they failed, it was over for them, thus no one would recklessly begin. Once they tried and failed, they would have used their mission badge in vain.

Lin Ming carefully observed the area.

He discovered that the 36 mile high Precipice Cliff had many marks, but the truth was that there were massive differences even between these marks.

Some marks were deep and some marks were shallow. Some people left behind their name and some people left behind runes. Between these marks, the greatest difference was in their heights.

The higher one went up Precipice Cliff, the fewer marks there were. At the very top of Precipice Cliff was a giant purple boulder, and this purple boulder had the least marks of all. However, every mark on it revealed a devastatingly breathtaking aura.

“What is that purple boulder?”

Before Lin Ming could ask Soulwhite this question, the eager and high-spirited Monster Prince Duyu suddenly spoke first.

The ones that were asked seemed a bit annoyed. “That is the Emperor Stone, didn’t you know? The Emperor Stone is at the summit of Precipice Cliff. If you can leave a mark on the Emperor Stone then you can obtain extra rewards, but leaving behind a mark on Precipice Cliff itself is difficult to begin with and trying to leave behind a mark on the Emperor Stone is ten times as difficult. It’s simply impossible for commoners.”

As this random traveler spoke, Lin Ming remembered that the contents of his mission was to leave a name on Precipice Cliff’s Emperor Stone.

The mission had specifically stated the Emperor Stone and not Precipice Cliff. It seemed that the Asura Road really thought highly of him. Could this even still be considered a blue soul level mission?

Lin Ming looked up at the Emperor Stone. There were only several dozen marks on it, including sword marks, saber marks, fist marks, runes, spear holes, and so forth. All of these different marks contained the aura of Laws, and they felt as if they had existed since the most ancient of times.

“Only several dozen marks? In all the endless years of the Asura Road, only several dozen people have been able to leave behind their own marks? That means on average there isn’t even one mark every several hundred million years, right?”

Lin Ming asked Soulwhite. Soulwhite responded, “Master, even the marks left behind on the Emperor Stone will not last forever. They will eventually slowly fade away. Only by leaving by a deep mark will it remain for a long time. For instance, that sword mark at the highest point was left behind 100 million years ago by the ancient Evil Sword Duke using his Evil Divine Sword. When he left behind that sword mark he had a Divine Lord level cultivation.

The sword mark that Soulwhite mentioned was in truth a bit blurry, because 100 million years of time was simply too far off in the distance. There was only a single character carved there – ‘Evil’.

Lin Ming was basking in the concepts left behind in this ‘Evil’ character when he heard some people arguing.

“Fine, then let’s have a little competition. Our Blue Sword Faction isn’t afraid of you at all.”

“Haha, your Blue Sword Faction has already been left breathless these past years by the suppression of the Snow Moon Holy Lands. Do you really think you can defeat our Chalk Family? Let’s see just whose disciples are more amazing.”

As the two sides of people were arguing, someone from the Blue Sword Faction group suddenly flew up. He was like a giant bird as he flew up more than 10,000 feet high. Once he arrived at a blank area on Precipice Cliff, he revolved all the energy within his body and poured it into his sword. Then, with a loud shout, he slashed downwards.

Kacha!

With an echoing sound of metal on stone, some stone chips were cut away by this person.

Then, that person fell back down to the ground. His movements were steady; it was clear he had exhausted a considerable amount of his energy.

Everyone looked up. They saw that 10,000 feet up Precipice Cliff, there was a bowl-sized mark. This was a Law mark left behind by two sword strokes. Because of the lack of strength, the mark wasn’t drawn perfectly so it seemed a bit rough.

“Success!”

“Amazing!”

The youth that dropped to the ground returned to the cheers of his group.

But on the other side, the White Chalk Family group seemed to think little of it. “You weren’t even able to leave behind your name and only a tiny Law mark, so what are you all so happy about? White Shun, it’s your turn.”

With those words, a person from the White Chalk Family flew up. This person also flew up around 10,000 feet, reaching a position several feet above the height that the Blue Sword Faction disciple reached. Then, he carved his own mark right above the mark left behind by the Blue Sword Faction disciple.

The weapon he used was a dagger. This dagger was like a divine brush. With the sound of wind and the chipping of stone, bits of rock fell down. Then, this disciple floated to the ground.

Everyone looked up to see that this White Chalk Family’s White Shun had left behind a character on Precipice Cliff – ‘White’.

A character was certainly much more complex than a two stroke Law mark. In order to carve this into Precipice Cliff it required a far greater amount of strength. It wasn’t something that the average person could hope to accomplish.

Moreover, this ‘White’ character was several feet above the mark left behind by the Blue Sword Faction disciple, making it seem as if the lower mark was suppressed. This caused the Blue Sword Faction disciple to be extremely depressed.

The people from the White Chalk Family began to cheer in abundance.

On the other side, the Blue Sword Faction people had extremely ugly complexions. They were indeed inferior in the first round. “Third Junior-apprentice Brother, it’s your turn.”

The Blue Sword Faction side sent yet another person up.

A competition between two great influences had the other martial artists at the base of Precipice Cliff enjoying the show.

“This is a close struggle between dragons and tigers!”

“They really do have many geniuses. Whether it is the Blue Sword Faction or White Chalk Family, both of them are different from us. It’s already amazing if we have anyone able to leave their mark, but everyone in their groups can do it.”

Not too far away from Lin Ming, some martial artists began to vividly discuss what was happening, their eyes filled with admiration.

But just as they had spoken, a contemptuous voice spoke out. “This is it? How mediocre. Out of those in both their groups there isn’t a single one worth mentioning.”

This person’s voice was loud and martial artists had extremely sharp hearing. The one speaking immediately attracted the gaze of many present.

The one who was speaking was Monster Prince Duyu, who had travelled here with Lin Ming.

Monster Prince Duyu’s arms were folded against his chest. There was a proud and cocky smile gracing his face. In his opinion, this level of ability was really just too pathetic.

Chapter 1457 – Emperor Stone

[*Chinese miles and feet are different from imperial standards*]

Monster Prince Duyu’s words immediately aroused the anger of everyone.

Not to mention those young elites of great sects that were spoken down to by Monster Prince Duyu, even the commoner martial artists were annoyed.

To obtain a mission badge of this level required a certain standard. Mostly, they were one-star Asuras. As a result, after arriving here they had seen the geniuses of great influences show off, and they were left sighing in awe.

But at this time, these geniuses of great influences were called ‘mediocre’ by Monster Prince Duyu. Didn’t this mean that everyone else was even worse than mediocre?

How could they feel good about this?

“Who the hell are you?”

“You’re not as awesome as you think you are!”

Some martial artists glared at Monster Prince Duyu.

Monster Prince Duyu sneered and slowly uncrossed his arms. He clenched his fists together, causing crackling popping sounds to echo in the air. “What? You lot are so weak and yet others can’t mention it?”

“Interesting! How interesting!” Near the White Chalk Family, a middle-aged man leading their group looked towards Monster Prince Duyu. “If you have such confidence, do you think you can amaze everyone here with your achievements? Really, a newborn calf doesn’t fear the tiger at all. If you want then you can try yourself!”

“Elder White Glory, he is simply running his mouth off! If he comes up then I’ll suppress him for you!” A nearby junior disciple said. All of these heroic young elites were arrogant individuals and none of them wished to accept they were naturally inferior.

Monster Prince Duyu continued smiling. Towards the mission of leaving his name upon Precipice Cliff, he had full confidence.

From the attempts of the White Chalk Family and the Blue Sword Faction he could see the approximate difficulty of the mission. Precipice Cliff looked like a singularly smooth wall, but this simple wall actually contained the aura of outstanding individuals since time immemorial!

Even if the marks these outstanding individuals left behind had vanished, their auras would still be preserved within Precipice Cliff. Slowly, over time, these countless auras condensed into a horrifying force field. If one wasn’t a truly amazing individual it would be impossible to obtain the approval of Precipice Cliff.

The higher one went up Precipice Cliff, the more intense the aura would be and the greater the pressure. The higher one wished to go, the more pressure they would have to withstand.

Meanwhile, carving a mark into Precipice Cliff was also challenge. The larger the mark one left, the more strokes there were, the deeper the writing was, then the greater the difficulty would be.

To leave behind an extremely deep and profound mark on Precipice Cliff while withstanding the tremendous suppression of the aura there wasn’t simple at all.

When the martial artists of the White Chalk Family and Blue Sword Faction had tried, they had flown up just a bit more than 10,000 feet and the marks they left behind were very simple; there was no need to mention how deep their carvings were. To Monster Prince Duyu, they were simply far too weak.

Monster race martial artists tended to be outspoken and brash, speaking out however they wished. As Monster Prince Duyu saw such a poor performance from these people, he simply spoke out his thoughts.

The result was that he had caused everyone to be angry with him.

Of course, Monster Prince Duyu didn’t care about whether or not these people were angry. In his eyes, these people were nothing more than ants. In the future their achievements would end at the Holy Lord realm, but he himself would be an Empyrean level character.

After stepping below Precipice Cliff, he looked up and lazily said, “Of course I’ll give it a try. The reason I came to Precipice Cliff is to complete a mission. Is there anyone stronger amongst you lot? Is there anyone willing to leave a mark on Precipice Cliff with me?”

The corner of Monster Prince Duyu’s lips tugged up as he swept his eyes over everyone.

“Heh, this fool doesn’t know what death or danger are.”

Two people walked forwards. One was a tall young man and the other was an ordinary-looking dark-skinned woman.

These people came from the White Chalk Family and the Blue Sword Faction. Their auras were restrained and their foundations were solid. One could immediately see that they were outstanding martial artists of their generation.

“Peak Holy Land geniuses.”

Lin Ming judged from not too far away. From the point that Monster Prince Duyu had spoken out to this sudden conflict, Lin Ming hadn’t spoken at all. He had only stood on the sidelines, watching.

“Let’s begin!”

Monster Prince Duyu licked his lips, eagerness in his eyes. He seemed impatient to start, as if he were confident that he would be able to go very high.

As for the other two people, their eyes were dignified, secretly competing with everyone around them. They could feel that this brash fellow wasn’t bluffing; he really did have the ability to back up his boasts.

This wasn’t any casual competition. They could not afford to lose, because losing meant disgracing the honor of their sect and family.

“I will go first. Do you think you can keep up?” As Monster Prince Duyu spoke, he flew straight up. His speed was fast as he flew upwards like an arrow.

The other two refused to be outdone. Both of the leapt up, the repulsion force causing the ground to explode beneath them. The three of them leapt upwards like mighty tigers, unstoppable!

“How fierce!”

Seeing Monster Prince Duyu be so fierce and strong in his actions, all the angry commoner martial artists were silenced. They clearly weren’t his match.

10,000 feet passed in the blink of an eye. At this height, Monster Prince Duyu hadn’t slowed down at all, all the way up to 20,000 feet. At this point, the other two people seemed to be weakening.

30,000 feet! 40,000 feet!

With 1500 feet to a mile, Monster Prince Duyu had already gone up more than 20 miles!

At this height, Monster Prince Duyu was still calm and relaxed, his flight easy. As for the other two, they had reached their limit.

This height was already pushing their limits.

The pressure of Precipice Cliff was terrifying, especially when one went higher. The closer one approached to the Emperor Stone, the greater the pressure they would have to bear; it was impossible for them to withstand.

For those that lacked talent, it was impossible to obtain the recognition of the Emperor Stone!

If they continued to fly upwards they could still go several thousand feet, but they would have consumed far too much energy by then. It would be impossible for them to leave any mark on Precipice Cliff at that point.

How could this be… the disparity was too great!

The two of them found this unbelievable. They originally felt that Monster Prince Duyu was some talented character, but they didn’t think he would be above them by so much!

At this point, the two of them could not longer ponder what to do. They had to stop where they were to leave a mark behind on Precipice Cliff.

Saber and sword crossed. The young man from the White Chalk Family was just barely able to leave behind the simple mark of his family on the wall.

As for the young woman from the Blue Sword Faction, she was only able to leave behind a single shallow sword mark; she didn’t have the strength to leave behind another stroke.

Then, the two of them began to fall beneath the weight of the massive pressure. As for Monster Prince Duyu, he rose even higher!

“What!?”

“How could this be?”

The surrounding martial artists were all left dumbfounded. This disparity was not minor at all!

The Elders of the White Chalk Family and Blue Sword Faction also had extremely ugly expressions.

Several miles away from Precipice Cliff, Lin Ming shook his head. “The peak geniuses of Holy Land level influences simply cannot compare at all to outstanding Empyrean descendants. This sort of competition is only a one-sided stomp.”

He had expected this result from the start. After all, a peak Empyrean descendant wasn’t a common cabbage. In the entire Divine Realm, there were no more than 10 such characters.

Now, Monster Prince Duyu had casually come to a little corner of the Asura Road. To ordinary common geniuses, he was an unfathomable existence.

As everyone saw Monster Prince Duyu reach just under 30 miles, all of them were clear what this meant. Even if he didn’t leave behind a mark on Precipice Cliff, just reaching this height was as difficult as ascending to heaven. But Monster Prince Duyu clearly had plenty of strength left over. Was he planning to shoot straight to the Emperor Stone?

Many martial artists had guessed correctly. Monster Prince Duyu’s goal was indeed the Emperor Stone!

He was the number one young genius of the Divine Realm monster race. He had sufficient pride in his status. As the great calamity arrived, he had to give an even greater performance than all previous geniuses so he could show his worth.

What he needed was to be recognized! He needed to prove just how amazing the young geniuses of the monster race were!

Of course, it was also convenient for him to reveal his wondrous strength in front of Xiao Moxian.

At a height of 33 miles, Monster Prince Duyu began to truly feel the pressure. The closer he reached to the Emperor Stone, the more terrifying the pressure became.

“This is more difficult than I thought it would be.”

Monster Prince Duyu forcefully summoned true essence and rose another mile.

Precipice Cliff was 36 miles tall, but the Emperor Stone was a mile in diameter itself. In other words, as long as he could fly up 35 miles he could leave behind his mark on the Emperor Stone.

By this time, Monster Prince Duyu had consumed a considerable amount of strength. He estimated that even if he were to succeed in flying up 35 miles, he likely wouldn’t have the strength to leave behind a character.

“How could this be so hard! I have to go all-out!”

Monster Prince Duyu roared out loud. His bones began to emit loud cracking sounds. His body became larger and more solid, and scales covered his neck and cheeks.

This was the monster race’s body metamorphosis. Monster Prince Duyu had activated his monster bloodline to forcefully fly up yet another mile and reach a height of 35 miles.

Now, he had finally arrived in front of the Emperor Stone.

“I’m here!”

All of Monster Prince Duyu’s blood was tumbling in his body and the energy within him was chaotically raging about. He had reached his limit. If he tried to continue upwards beneath the dual pressure and restless energy within himself then he would likely suffer broken organs and even his meridians would be damaged. However, he continued to release trues essence. Once he stopped it would be impossible for him to leave behind any mark on the Emperor Stone.

“Monster Prince Descends!”

Monster Prince Duyu clawed at the Emperor Stone without any reservations!

After completing his body metamorphosis, his hands had become like dragon claws. Moreover, there was a fierce and savage-looking gauntlet covering his hands. These gauntlets were Monster Prince Duyu’s weapons. In terms of sharpness, it was no worse than a sword or saber.

Monster Prince Duyu had poured all of his remaining true essence into this strike. As his claw came slashing down, his monster blood boiled over.

Kacha!

The Emperor Stone exploded with a burst of sound. A tiny amount of stone fragments were torn off by Monster Prince Duyu.

Although this was only a slight trace, Monster Prince Duyu had indeed left behind a shallow mark on the Emperor Stone. He had succeeded!

This strike exhausted all of his strength. Beneath the heavy pressure his body began plummeting to the ground. In midair, he forcefully suppressed his tumbling blood and swallowed down a pill to restore some origin energy. Only then was he able to stumble back onto the ground.

All around Monster Prince Duyu, the many martial artists were shocked speechless.

This fellow had actually managed to leave behind a mark on the Emperor Stone. Although it was only a tiny shallow mark, it was still the Emperor Stone! Compared to Precipice Cliff, it was on a completely different level.

Monster Prince Duyu looked up at the little marks he left behind. Out of his five fingers, only his thumb, index finger, middle finger, and ring finger had left behind small traces. His pinky didn’t have any strength left to chip the Emperor Stone. Moreover, the traces were very shallow.

“The Emperor Stone lives up to its reputation. It isn’t easy at all…”

As Monster Prince Duyu thought out loud, he turned towards Xiao Moxian and Lin Ming, a smile on his face. He wanted to see just what it would be like when Lin Ming tried to complete this mission.

Chapter 1458 – Prize

At the base of Precipice Cliff, dozens of martial artists looked up at the mark left behind on the Emperor Stone. Although Monster Prince Duyu had left behind only the shallowest of marks, this mark still left behind a profound impression as it reflected within everyone’s eyes.

“That monster youth can actually leave behind a mark on the Emperor Stone, but we can’t even fly higher than 20 miles… the difference is too great…”

“This could be called a scene that isn’t encountered even in 10,000 years.”

“It’s not as much as 10,000 years. The trace he left behind is a bit shallow, so it should be a 1000 year event. Even so, a thousand year event is shocking enough. After all, the Asura Road is comprised of numerous geniuses of the 33 Layered Heavens.”

The ones who were angry because of Monster Prince Duyu’s overly arrogant and provocative attitude were all left silent. The White Chalk Family and Blue Sword Faction also felt ashamed of their own inferiority. But to them it still wasn’t a disgrace to lose to such an outstanding individual. The difference was simply too great at the start.

“This monster youth might be an Empyrean descendant!”

Someone said in whispered hushes. The reason that the Emperor Stone was called the Emperor Stone was that those who could leave behind a mark on it could become an Empyrean in the future, an absolute emperor of the people.

An Empyrean… that level of existence left far too great an impact on the average person.

As everyone was speaking, Monster Prince Duyu only faintly smiled, not thinking much about it.

As for the White Chalk Family and Blue Sword Faction that had instigated a competition with him, he didn’t bother with them anymore. He had already defeated them miserably enough.

Rather, it should be said that slapping these people in the face didn’t mean anything to Monster Prince Duyu. The face he wanted to slap belonged to Lin Lanjian; he had long been sick of seeing that brat.

Thus, he sent Xiao Moxian and Lin Ming a true essence sound transmission, “Junior-apprentice Sister, I only displayed a humble showing of my skills just now. It should be your turn to give it a try. And you too, Lin Lanjian, you should try to complete your mission as well. Come and give it a try, do you think you can reach 30 miles at least?”

As Monster Prince Duyu spoke, the cunning light in his eyes grew even brighter.

Xiao Moxian didn’t reply to Monster Prince Duyu’s true essence sound transmission. At this time, her wide and blinking eyes were staring at Lin Ming.

“Hey, what mission do you have?” Xiao Moxian lifted her own mission badge and stuck out her slender neck like a curious child, wanting to see just what Lin Ming’s mission badge was.

“Precipice Cliff, leave a name upon the Emperor Stone.” Lin Ming lightly said.

As Xiao Moxian heard this, she revealed an expression as if she had already expected this. “So it really was the Emperor Stone. I have the same mission. It seems we’ll fail this mission if we can’t leave our mark on the Emperor Stone.”

“Mm.” Lin Ming nodded. Xiao Moxian’s mission was the same as his. This proved that she too had been approved by the Asura Road’s Heavenly Dao.

“Hehe, I’ve already been wanting to compete with you.”

As Xiao Moxian said these words, her liquid eyes flashed with a playful light. “If we were to fight directly I’d probably lose, but… aren’t you older than me? Hehe, since I can’t beat you up let’s compare our talent and potential instead. Just who is better than whom in the end?”

As Xiao Moxian spoke, Lin Ming’s mind stirred. Indeed, this impish little enchantress’ words had aroused his fighting spirit.

What Xiao Moxian said was right. In terms of individual strength, she was slightly worse than he was. But in terms of talent and potential, that was a completely separate matter!

Xiao Moxian’s glorious name had already spread throughout the entire Divine Realm!

Whether it was before the First Martial Meeting or after the First Martial Meeting, Xiao Moxian had been recognized as the one possessing the most talent in the entire Divine Realm!

Even though Lin Ming and Frost Dream had the most dazzling performances in the First Martial Meeting and had taken first and second place, they still weren’t able to shake Xiao Moxian’s status as the number one most talented individual in the entire Divine Realm!

The physique of a God Beast was formidable enough to stir the anger of the heavens. Just by growing up, she would reach a level close to an Empyrean. And beyond her God Beast physique, she also possessed a ridiculously high perception and had inherited Empyrean Demondawn’s martial talent. Moreover, she had nearly unlimited top resources at her disposal. For her, becoming an extreme Empyrean was the most basic accomplishment she would have. There was a high chance she could step into the realm of True Divinity!

Lin Ming also wanted to know just how his own potential was compared to Xiao Moxian’s.

“Okay, then let’s compete a bit.” Ever since Lin Ming arrived at the Asura Road, he could feel that there were far too many powerhouses in the world; it was impossible to know where the peak of martial arts was. In his life, nearly every person he met could be an opponent of his. During the First Martial Meeting, Lin Ming had defeated Xiao Moxian, but he always felt that this victory was wrong because of his advantage in age. But now, he could fairly compete with Xiao Moxian.

Hearing Lin Ming agree, Xiao Moxian chuckled, “Great!”

The two still used true essence sound transmissions to speak. Not too far away, Monster Prince Duyu’s complexion was ugly. He spoke to the two of them and yet neither of them had responded to him. Instead, they spoke to each other and also seemed to be having some fun and interesting conversation. This made him feel as if he were being treated as empty air.

“Hey, don’t you think it would be a bit more fun if we had a little prize? Without some type of prize, it’s a bit of a boring competition, don’t you think?” Xiao Moxian asked, full of enthusiasm, completely not noticing Monster Prince Duyu’s expression.

Lin Ming faintly smiled. “It’s only a casual competition. What sort of prize do you want?”

“If I win, you undo your appearance changing technique and let me see just who you are?” Xiao Moxian ground her teeth together, her eyes shining with challenge. She was trying to goad Lin Ming into agreeing, however no matter how contemptuous she tried to be, it only looked as if she were having a great deal of fun.

“Alright.” Lin Ming agreed. In his opinion, revealing his status to Xiao Moxian wasn’t anything at all. He only needed to hide the truth from Monster Prince Duyu.

Xiao Moxian smiled, and she did so dazzlingly. She thought to herself, “Little guy, I’ll be sure to defeat you this time!”

In terms of strength, even Xiao Moxian wouldn’t call herself the top young elite of the entire Divine Realm. But in terms of potential and talent, she was confident she wouldn’t lose to anyone. This was her pride, her road of martial arts. She wanted to become a True Divinity!

“How do you know I am using an appearance changing technique?” Lin Ming asked with a laugh.

“Ha! A woman’s intuition!” Xiao Moxian said with a great deal of self-satisfaction. Lin Ming didn’t know whether to laugh or to cry. In his eyes, Xiao Moxian was a young girl. For her to call herself a ‘woman’ was a bit funny.

As the two spoke they had already reached the base of Precipice Cliff. Looking up, they could see the 36 mile high Precipice Cliff stabbing straight into the night sky like a divine sword.

“This Asura Road Master seems to really like the number 36.”

After Lin Ming entered the Asura Road, he discovered that many places used the number 36. Even the Hunter Game had an array formation of 36 people at the end.

He looked towards Xiao Moxian and grinned. “And if you lose?”

“You can make any request you want!” Xiao Moxian proudly and briskly waved her hand. “Oh, yes, but in advance let me tell you that sacrificing my body or anything like that is an absolute no-go!”

“Uh…” A strange color flashed over Lin Ming’s face as he heard this; just what was going on in this girl’s brain? “My only request is… if… if something were to happen to me in the future, then I hope that you can look after several people for me and guarantee that they can live their lives in peace…” Lin Ming said after a deep period of thought. His request left Xiao Moxian a bit surprised.

The road of martial arts was filled hardships and dangers. Moreover, in this great calamity, it was impossible to tell which way the tide would turn. Also, Lin Ming still had a showdown with the Good Fortune Saint Son. Although he believed in his own ability to grow enough to challenge him in the future, there was no saying what would happen…

“Alright.” Xiao Moxian thoughtfully nodded. “Now, let’s begin. Shall we go together?”

“Okay, we’ll start together!”

Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian stood a hundred feet away from each other. The position they chose at the base of Precipice Cliff was just beneath the Emperor Stone.

As for the other martial artists, they were still lost in the shocking scene that Monster Prince Duyu had created. Although they saw Xiao Moxian and Lin Ming, they didn’t care too much about them.

Some influences had already dispatched representatives to pay their respects to Monster Prince Duyu. Although they knew it was impossible for Monster Prince Duyu to join their side, forming a good relationship with him wasn’t bad either.

Monster Prince Duyu was disinclined to bother with these people. He coldly sneered as he looked at Precipice Cliff. He never imagined that Lin Ming would be so reckless and blind as to compete with someone like Xiao Moxian. Even he had to confess that he was flung miles away by Xiao Moxian. In terms of talent, she was fully deserving of being known as number one within the Divine Realm.

A cold breeze blew past. Lin Ming immediately soared upwards. His movements were smooth and calm. Although he didn’t seem to be going too fast, he was like a stream of water that ascended upwards, as comfortable and free as a horse racing through the grasslands.

The pressure of Precipice Cliff wasn’t able to affect him at all.

And beside Lin Ming, Xiao Moxian was also enjoying this relaxing trip up. She was like a black butterfly soaring through a bush of flowers. Her movements were brisk and light as she shot straight up to the top!

These actions immediately attracted the attention of many people.

“There are more masters going up!”

Not many people knew that Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian had arrived together with Monster Prince Duyu, thus no one paid attention to them. But now, as they looked at the pair’s movements, they could tell that these two certainly weren’t ordinary young elites.

“It shouldn’t be. What is going on with today that there are so many masters?”

“Look at their movements. It seems they are also capable of flying above 30 miles!”

To the current martial artists, 30 miles was an astounding result.

And as they were speaking, Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian had already easily and swiftly crossed 20 miles. Without either of them falling behind, both of them flew straight towards the 30 mile mark.

As Monster Prince Duyu saw this, he frowned. He wasn’t surprised that Lin Ming could reach this height, but what he was surprised about was that Lin Ming remained as calm as Xiao Moxian.

25 miles…

27 miles…

29 miles…

Lin Ming smoothly broke through the 30 mile mark, keeping pace with Xiao Moxian throughout.

Xiao Moxian looked at Lin Ming and smirked. Her speed suddenly ramped up. Lin Ming merely faintly smiled in response and followed her pace.

As the martial artists below saw this, all of them were shocked to the point that their jaws dropped. At over 30 miles the pressure of the Emperor Stone was obvious to anyone, but not only did they not slow down, they instead increased their speed. Just how were they doing this?

As everyone was dumbfounded, Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian had broken through the 33 miles line!

33 miles represented the 33 Layered Heavens; this could be considered a dividing boundary. At this height, Lin Ming suddenly felt a deep resistance push down on him as if he had fallen into a swamp. Every time he rose up another ten feet he would have to consume a good deal of energy; it made advancing upwards far more difficult.

However, this was only a bit more difficult. He continued to rise, unstoppable. The Emperor Stone was already within reach.

Chapter 1465 – Heavendevil City

Naqi wished with all his soul that he could ruin those two characters, but the moment he was only 200-300 feet from reaching the peak of the Emperor Stone his mortal body had reached its limits; many of his blood vessels had burst apart!

Bang!

Naqi reluctantly punched outwards, attacking through space to strike the Lin character on the Emperor Stone!

However, he had very little strength remaining to begin with, and underneath the suppressive pressure of the Emperor Stone, his attack diminished to nearly nothing. He simply wasn’t able to mar the Emperor Stone at all.

That Lin character’s aura remained as swift and fierce as before, looking down at him from its unharmed perfection as if it were taunting his own incompetence.

“Your Highness, don’t force yourself!”

At the base of Precipice Cliff, the old saint man shouted out anxiously. Everyone could see that Naqi had reached his limit; it was impossible for him to reach the top of the Emperor Stone.

Many people had a taunting look on their faces. Naqi was less than 200 feet away from reaching the top of the Emperor Stone. To anyone else, this would have been a result to be proud of, but when this result was combined with his previous words, it actually caused people to want to mock him.

“Hehe, to think he wanted to destroy the characters left behind by that man and woman and leave behind his own. Just who the hell does he think he is? Those two were true monstrous geniuses that had reached the limits of potential. Normally, even an extreme Empyrean descendant couldn’t hope to reach the peak of the Emperor Stone.”

“Desperately persisting just because he wants to save face is simply a death wish. I want to see just how he ends up.”

“Shh, stop using sound transmissions, if you’re not careful they’ll notice you.”

Several martial artists were using sound transmissions to quietly discuss what was happening. Currently Imperial Prince Naqi was only 10 feet from reaching the top of the Emperor Stone. However, all of his blood was nearly stagnant; he had reached his absolute limit.

“How could it be like this!”

Imperial Prince Naqi felt a deep shame.

He didn’t think that he was weaker than Lin Ming. In fact, during their battle at the Chaotic Blood Continent, he hadn’t truly lost to Lin Ming. Yet now, on the Emperor Stone, he was completely unable to compare.

This meant that although his strength wasn’t inferior to Lin Ming’s, his potential was actually extremely far off!

“My potential is worse than his!?”

Imperial Prince Naqi couldn’t accept this. Underneath Precipice Cliff, that old man Mister Zhou heaved a deep sigh. In the battle of the Chaotic Blood Continent, Naqi and Lin Ming were nearly the same.

Because their strength was close, this caused everyone to overlook something. It was that Naqi had been at the late Saint Transformation realm, but Lin Ming was only at the middle Divine Transformation realm!

Lin Ming had leapt up a small boundary to suppress Imperial Prince Naqi!

To extreme geniuses, overcoming a small boundary to fight was as easy as drinking water. But when this small boundary was between peak martial artists, both of them unrivalled geniuses of their generation, then that was truly terrifying!

Every time a peak genius rose a small boundary in their cultivation their strength would experience a massive increase.

“This Lin Ming is indeed a horrifying person. But luckily my saint race will launch a full-on invasion of the Divine Realm before long. He will not have the space to grow, otherwise if he did, he might become a character like Empyrean Divine Seal of 3.6 billion years ago!”

As Mister Zhou was thinking about this, he felt that it was prudent to kill off Lin Ming as soon as possible. To cull the weeds he needed to destroy the roots!

And at this time, on the Emperor Stone, Naqi was finally unable to continue. The closer he reached to the top, the more terrifying the pressure became. Although this was only a minor 10 foot distance, it was as great as the earth and heavens.

The opportunity to challenge the Emperor Stone only came once in a lifetime. Once he failed his mission badge would break apart. Naqi knew that reaching the top of the Emperor Stone was no longer possible. With a raging hatred simmering in his eyes, he struck out a claw eight feet from the top.

Kacha!

With an explosive sound, Naqi tore out a chunk of stone.

This last claw strike comprised all of Naqi’s remaining energy. After this strike, he was no longer able to support himself. His body plummeted straight down like a broken kite.

Hu - !

Mister Zhou flew up high to grab the severely wounded Naqi. As he looked up to look at the mark Naqi left behind, Mister Zhou shook his head.

Naqi’s last claw strike had left behind a three inch long mark. But in terms of depth, it was no deeper than the marks left behind by Monster Prince Duyu. And beyond that, this mark was extremely rough. One could barely make out the symbol of the saint race, and this symbol didn’t contain any Concepts at all.

This was because Naqi was already completely exhausted, a lamp without oil, thus he didn’t have the ability to leave behind any Concepts.

If Naqi hadn’t insisted on trying to forcefully push himself up the last 100 feet of the Emperor Stone then he could have left behind a perfect mark. But now, the mark he left behind was no different from one that a dog would leave.

Beside Mister Zhou, the other saint disciples were also looking at each other in disappointment. None of them knew what to say.

And not too far away, the other martial artists had also quietly departed. They were afraid that Imperial Prince Naqi would take out his anger on them in a fit of indignant shame after he recovered.

“Rest for a moment and then we’ll embark deeper into the Great Desolate!” Mister Zhou issued an order. As he did so a cold brightness shined in his eyes. He was wondering just how he could assassinate Lin Ming.

………

In the vast expanse of the Great Desolate, there was a 10,000 foot high precipice. This precipice continued for several hundred miles, as sharp and steep as if someone had carved it with a saber. Above this precipice towered a grand and magnificent city. The city walls themselves were a thousand feet high and held together with incomparably firm array formations. Looking from afar, it looked like a mountain range hidden in the horizon. The wonders of this city left one shocked with awe.

This city was Heavendevil City.

Heavendevil City was over 10 times larger than the City of Discord and also the largest city on the edge of the Great Desolate. Many martial artists who planned to participate in the trials in the Great Desolate stopped here. Because of the constant stream of people, Heavendevil City was always bustling.

Lin Ming and his group walked down the streets of Heavendevil City. Both sides of the streets were lined with a variety of shops. The martial artists that walked down the roads were mostly youths. Moreover, each one had a solid foundation with extraordinary skill; they were all heroic young elites!

This was also well within reason. After all, whether it was the martial artists who came here to adventure in the Great Desolate or the people who lived in Heavendevil City, they needed the ability to face the ancient vicious beasts that surrounded the city. Otherwise, they would end up as nothing but food for those vicious beasts.

This was originally a land where powerhouses gathered. In addition to the constant slaughter that occurred year-round, the strong survived and the weak were continuously weeded out. In terms of average quality, Heavendevil City far surpassed the other cities on the outer edge of the Asura Road.

Xiao Moxian was extremely inquisitive as she walked into the city. This was a scene she hadn’t seen before in the Divine Realm.

In the Divine Realm, masters were normally gathered in large sects and Holy Lands. In the cities, there were usually only low level martial artists. After all, a city was a place where one lived, and masters would usually go into their sect to cultivate in seclusion.

But the Asura Road was different. Here, most martial artists came to engage in life or death battles and enter challenging smelting trials. Those that established sects to cultivate were instead in the minority.

“Master, if you wish to find information you can go to Heaven’s Secret. Heaven’s Secret is an extremely renowned intelligence network that operates on the edge of the Asura Road. As long as you have sufficient wealth you can find out a great deal of secret news.”

“Heaven’s Secret? There’s no need to hurry. Information about the map in the emperor jade shouldn’t be directly inquired into. It needs to be separately investigated.”

Lin Ming already made his plans. He would split the information of the emperor jade into a dozen plus pieces and slowly investigate it.

Chapter 1477 – Separate

Even though Lin Ming was strong, such words were far too bristling. Monster Prince Duyu was especially angered.

“We’ll die faster if we return? Aren’t you just speaking nonsense? If it weren’t for you, why would I have come to this damned land to begin with!? If you want to die then you can stay here yourself, the rest of us are going back!”

Monster Prince Duyu breathlessly shouted out, his voice shaking with anger. He had already been driven past the limits of all tolerance by Lin Ming. The other martial artists were also unhappy with what Lin Ming said just now. It was true that Lin Ming was strong, but his understanding of God Burying Ridge wasn’t necessarily any better than that of the rest of them and he certainly didn’t have the necessary experience to evaluate situations that Fatty Zhou said. Thus, Lin Ming’s claims were all based on nothing.

Dragon Cloud hesitated for a moment before saying, “Brother Lin, you said that we would die even quicker if we were to return, do you have a reason for this claim?”

Lin Ming replied, “At the entrance there will be some people that will stop us. They might have a World King powerhouse with them…”

“Mm?” Lin Ming’s words caused all the martial artists to freeze in cold fear. When Fatty Zhou had spoken about the entrances to the inner ridge, in truth there was only a single one; the rest were mere decorations. In other words, if they were to leave through a single exit it would be easy for anyone to lay an ambush for them.

“Why would there be a World King hunting us? Aren’t you just thinking about this too much!?”

Many martial artists said. They simply didn’t believe that they were worth a World King level powerhouse chasing them all the way here.

But Dragon Cloud seemed to suddenly remember something. He turned towards Fatty Zhou and said, “Sage Zhou, you said that someone attacked us with a curse technique and that is the reason your force field shattered?”

Fatty Zhou nodded. “This technique likely stems from the work of the Spider Brothers. Among the various guides of God Burying Ridge, they excel the most at curses.”

“Why would they do such a thing? Do they have a grudge against you? Or are they trying to kill us to steal our treasures? We haven’t even obtained any god burying stones yet.”

“There is no grudge between us at all!” Fatty Zhou shook his head. “River water does not interfere with well water; we mind our own business without interfering with each other!”

“Then that is really too strange…” Dragon Cloud couldn’t understand why the attack occurred.

“Perhaps someone hired them.” Lin Ming suddenly said.

“Hired them?” Dragon Cloud was stunned. He looked towards Lin Ming, “It seems your background is deeper than I thought…”

Thinking about it carefully, Lin Ming wasn’t surprised by this assassination attempt at all, and he had even said they would die quicker if they tried to return, as if he already knew someone had come here to hunt him down. With his tone, it was like he knew that a World King powerhouse lying in ambush was not just a speculation but a reality!

In other words, their situation was far worse than anyone could have imagined!

“Do you recognize those that are hunting us down?” Dragon Cloud asked. He was an intelligent young man; his words were already very close to the truth.

Everyone looked towards Lin Ming, waiting for his reply.

Lin Ming was silent for a brief moment. Then, he slowly and clearly said, “Without a doubt, they are coming here for me.”

“What!?”

Hearing Lin Ming say this, Dragon Cloud and Fatty Zhou were still barely able to maintain their calm, however, everyone else began to seethe with rage. Monster Prince Duyu in particular was angered to the extreme.

He suddenly strode forwards and grabbed the collar of Lin Ming’s clothes. “So it was you who sent us tumbling into this hell hole. Even if you are being fucking hunted by someone you shouldn’t drag us down with you! Just what have we done to you that you would harm us like this!?”

Monster Prince Duyu was frantic, nearly about to attack. But at this time, he felt a thick killing intent surge out from Lin Ming!

This terrifying killing intent locked onto his entire body, drowning him in an icy bath of despair as if he would die in the next moment!

Monster Prince Duyu bounced backwards as if he had been bitten by a snake. His complexion was grim as he glared at Lin Ming, licking his lips as he said, “How about all of us attack him together and subdue him. Then, we can take him to his enemy! If we do that then we’ll be able to escape here safely.”

As Monster Prince Duyu spoke these words he felt the pleasure of revenge. At this time it was assured that Lin Ming would become the target for everyone else!

He felt that Lin Ming was far too stupid. This was a matter that everyone clearly wasn’t aware of and yet he deliberately chose to speak out about it. No one liked being dragged into a mess by others.

“If you really wish to do so, then I’ll play with you.” Lin Ming’s voice was indifferent. As he looked at Monster Prince Duyu, the killing intent in his eyes became increasingly thick.

“Everyone calm down!”

Fatty Zhou shouted out. But, there were very few people able to calm down at this time. According to Fatty Zhou, even if they safely returned a number of them would still die.

“How can you ask us to remain calm at a moment like this? We are being hunted by a World King powerhouse!”

No matter what world it was, a World King wasn’t some random cabbage. They were able to control and overawe their own domain.

“We cannot be involved with him any longer. Let’s ditch him here and continue by ourselves. At the very least we won’t be sneak attacked anymore.”

Some martial artists proposed.

“Well said. We’re already showing him extreme forbearance by not haggling over the disaster he has brought on our heads. If we bring him with us then sooner or later we’ll end up dying here!”

Everyone quickly came to a unanimous opinion. Listening to these people, Monster Prince Duyu’s smile became increasingly wide. Now he finally had the opportunity he wanted to place Lin Ming in a death trap!

In Monster Prince Duyu’s eyes, there were dangers everywhere within the inner ridge. Without a guide to lead the way, this was an absolute world of death. Although it was true that Lin Ming was strong, this was a place where even World Kings could perish.

He had long harbored hatred for Lin Ming and now he finally had a chance to retaliate against him; this made him feel far too good in his heart. And for this chance to take revenge, he was even happy that Lin Ming’s enemy had hunted them all the way here, even if it meant they had been dragged into the mess.

“Brother Lin, you have quite the character…” Dragon Cloud looked towards Lin Ming, “You could clearly hide this matter, so why are you speaking out about it?”

Lin Ming looked at Dragon Cloud and faintly said, “Why would I want to hide it?”

Dragon Cloud was stunned, not knowing what to say.

“Heh! This brat doesn’t know of death or danger. He’s harmed us this much and yet he still has the airs to be righteous!”

Someone unhappily said. Lin Ming coldly sneered. In the Asura Road, strength was the law, strength was everything. If one was weak and pulled into a disaster where they died, they had no choice but to accept their fate!

The strong survived and the weak perished. This was the most basic law of the jungle. If the one being chased was an ordinary martial artist, then even if everyone here seized that person and stripped them of all their possessions, that person could only fall on their knees and beg for mercy.

But now that the person being chased was their teammate Lin Ming, they could only shout curses at him.

“This is… I, I hope you see what I must do. I can only say that I am sorry.” Fatty Zhou helplessly spread his arms wide as he spoke to Lin Ming, the implication clear in his words. He would comply with the view of the majority of the people here. Moreover, bringing Lin Ming with them was indeed far too troublesome. They would continue to be hunted down the entire time. Fatty Zhou didn’t believe that he had any chance of living if he were chased down by the combined forces of the Spider Brothers and a World King powerhouse.

“Sorry.” Dragon Cloud also helplessly said. Dragon Moon seemed as if she couldn’t help saying something, but she finally kept silent. To her, abandoning a companion to escape was not a glorious or heroic approach to doing this.

But at this moment, Xiao Moxian stepped forwards until she stood next to Lin Ming. She patted him on the shoulder, nodding as she indifferently said, “Haha, I think your social skills are far too lacking. It doesn’t seem that anyone here is willing to help you. How about this little miss here be merciful and take you in?”

As Xiao Moxian spoke these words, everyone was shocked that she would have such deep loyalty. As for Monster Prince Duyu, he suddenly jumped up. “Junior-apprentice Sister, what nonsense are you babbling on about!? You want to go with him? He is a dead man walking! If you go with him you will be killed!”

Monster Prince Duyu impatiently said. He wanted to grab Xiao Moxian’s hand but was actually dodged by her. “I say, why must you always be such a long-winded nagger. You go and do what you want and stop trying to manage me!”

“Junior-apprentice Sister, has he taken control of your mind? Are you still clear-minded right now? If you go with him you will die!” Monster Prince Duyu was about to go insane. He had finally thrown off Lin Ming with such great difficulty, and now that he was about to see his enemy die he was drowning in happiness. He fantasized about how, as long as he could leave safely, he could continue to journey through the Asura Road with Xiao Moxian and endure hardships with her, growing their feelings together all the while until she finally grew to love him. But now, Xiao Moxian actually wanted to join Lin Ming and die together with him!

Lin Ming was also startled. He looked towards Xiao Moxian, “Why do you want to go with me?”

Xiao Moxian wouldn’t know that he had an emperor jade that was carved with the lines of the God Burying Ridge’s dao field. According to any normal person’s reasoning, if she were to separate herself from the main group then although that wasn’t complete suicide, it was still nine chances of death and only once chance of survival.

Xiao Moxian clucked her tongue and laughed. “Me, I’m not someone that likes to abandon their companions. Moreover, I also owe you a life.”

When Lin Ming first entered the Great Desolate he had rescued Xiao Moxian. With this graciousness there was no way that Xiao Moxian would abandon him here alone. That was truly being ungrateful and forgoing all virtues.

“If you come with me, aren’t you afraid of dying?” Lin Ming looked at Xiao Moxian, the corners of his lips curving up in a happy expression.

He had to admit that for someone to disregard their own life or death and follow him at this moment was a touching decision.

“Haha, do you think this miss will die? Stop joking around with me! I am someone who will become a True Divinity in the future! Why would I perish in a tiny place like this?”

Xiao Moxian carelessly tossed out these words. Lin Ming wasn’t affected, but the others, including Fatty Zhou and the dragon siblings, nearly choked on themselves.

Become a True Divinity?

Many people already thought it was exaggerated to hear others say that they had set their goal to becoming an Empyrean. But to become a True Divinity, that was unimaginable!

This little girl was crazy…

This was the first thought that appeared in everyone’s minds. But as they recalled the ghostly movements that Xiao Moxian used to pass through the entrance to the inner ridge, they were actually rendered speechless. If every other aspect of hers was as outstanding as her movement techniques, then she really did have a chance of becoming a True Divinity!

This was simply an incomprehensible unrivalled genius!

“Junior-apprentice Sister!”

Monster Prince Duyu was extremely depressed. He knew that once Xiao Moxian made a decision there was no way anyone could change her mind; even Empyrean Demondawn himself was no exception. As for him, he was a mere acquaintance with no weight in her heart. Wanting to change her mind was simply a dream.

“It’s useless speaking to me. I guess you don’t plan on coming with me anymore, so bye-bye. I hope that we will see you alive once we leave this place.” Xiao Moxian giggled, seeming as if she wasn’t heading deeper into the perilous God Burying Ridge but rather having a nice outdoor stroll in the autumn.

Monster Prince Duyu clenched his fists so tightly that he drew blood. It was indeed impossible for him to continue following Xiao Moxian. Although he desired and fervently wished to obtain her, he wouldn’t continue onwards if he knew it led to certain death. To Monster Prince Duyu, his own life was the most precious treasure of all, surpassing everything else!

The groups had been determined. Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian would go together in one group and everyone else would be in another group.

But at this time, a deep fragrance suddenly stirred up in the grasslands. Beautiful flower petals danced in the breeze, fluttering along with the winds. This warm and delightful spring scene should normally have caused one to sigh in joy, but upon feeling this spring breeze, Fatty Zhou’s complexion suddenly changed.

“Bad… this is bad!”

Chapter 1478 - 10,000 Corpse Flowers

“What’s wrong Sage Zhou!?”

Everyone here in God Burying Ridge could be described as frightened birds. Now that they heard Fatty Zhou say such words, all of them raised their guard.

“Don’t breathe in that fragrance, it is the fragrance of 10,000 corpse flowers!”

Fatty Zhou shouted out. However, as he did so a martial artist was covered by this fragrance. In that moment, the martial artist seemed to lose consciousness as his eyes became lost. Flower petals began to fall down from the air like butterflies, landing on this person’s skin. Then, these flower petals melted, turning into a bright blood red liquid than sank into his body.

The martial artist’s body shook. In the next moment, a macabre and gruesome scene occurred. More and more flower petals fell onto this martial artist and more and more red liquid seeped into his body, spreading all over. Finally, even the martial artist himself began to melt apart into red liquid. Then, those bright blood red flowers began to germinate within him, sprouting out enchanting buds.

The roots of these flowers greedily absorbed the liquefied body of the martial artist; they were actually using the martial artist as nourishment!

This caused a tingling chill to crawl up the scalps of these people.

“Don’t let those flower petals touch you. This is how the 10,000 corpse flowers reproduce. A single flower petal can grow into a 10,000 corpse flower!”

Fatty Zhou rapidly said with a sound transmission. 10,000 corpse flowers were the most common type of creature in this Paradise Reborn land that used powerhouses as nourishment. They were extremely valuable for medicinal purposes. However, if someone wished to pluck these flowers, the price might be their life.

At this time the entire sky was filled with drifting flower petals. The bursts of flower fragrance met the senses and this flower fragrance actually had the effect of attacking one’s divine sense. By smelling this fragrance one’s thoughts would slow down, making it much harder to avoid the flower petals!

“Damnit!”

“Stand back to back! We’ll win if we can withstand this for a short time!”

Fatty Zhou rapidly cried out. At the same time he drew a thick cleaver and slashed out without holding anything back. Torrents of cleaver light fell downwards, each ray cutting through four or five flower petals, causing those flower petals to dissolve into red liquid that sprinkled onto the ground.

However, after every flower petal was cut apart the cleaver light would greatly weaken. After breaking through a fifth flower petal, the cleaver light would break apart. There were simply far too many flower petals dancing in the air!

“Everyone attack together!”

Dragon Cloud and Dragon Moon attacked with their spears. Their strength was not weak at all. Facing one side, they were able to destroy all of the incoming flower petals with their spear light.

Several other martial artists stood back to back, relying on each other to resist the attacks of these flower petals. If any one of them were to fall, all of them would die!

And at this time, Lin Ming and Xian Moxian were by themselves, soon covered in this rain of red flower petals.

“Junior-apprentice Sister!” Monster Prince Duyu shouted.

“Leave them be, we can’t even take care of ourselves!” A martial artist rapidly said. The martial artists that entered God Burying Ridge had extremely fragile relations to begin with, so who could care about others when disaster befell them?

Woosh! Woosh! Woosh!

Bright red flower petals were like flying knives that spun towards Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian. This beautiful, fairy tale-like scene was actually filled with a thick killing intent. The two of them were instantly blocked in by over a hundred flower petals.

The results of this scenario could be imagined. Once these flower petals touched the body, the consequences would be horrifying.

After falling into such a dangerous situation, Lin Ming wasn’t hurried at all. He poured his strength into his inner world, causing a boundless aura to surge out from within himself!

“Grandmist space!”

Hu - !

Star-heavy grandmist energy recklessly swept outwards, causing the space around Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian to immediately become as hard as a wall. The terrifying pressure pushed upon the flower petals, making them as slow as if they had fallen into a lake of molasses.

“What strange flower petals.” Through his formidable divine sense, Lin Ming discovered that every flower petal contained a resentful spirit! Moreover, these flowers were filled with blood vessels. Rather than flowers, they were more like condensed flesh and blood essence.

The 10,000 corpse flower was a flower of flesh and blood!

“Three Essences As One, Heretical God Force!”

Lin Ming revolved his strength to the limit. With a loud series of explosive sounds, a massive number of flower petals imploded upon themselves underneath the pressure of the grandmist space!

Simultaneously, Xiao Moxian formed a series of seals with her hands. Black flames blew outwards, setting the remaining flower petals on fire. As the flesh and blood was scorched away, the resentful spirits also disintegrated. In just several breaths of time, Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian’s combined attack completely eliminated the hundred plus flower petals!

“This is…”

Even Fatty Zhou and the others who were still surrounded by flower petals were shocked speechless. They knew that Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian were strong, but it was bizarre to be strong to such a degree. It seemed that the two of them alone were stronger than the rest of them combined.

In truth, the fact that Lin Ming could easily obtain victory was because his grandmist space was best suited to such a combat environment. As for Xiao Moxian’s flames, they inherently restrained all ghosts and spirits.

“30 feet to the front left, behind that gray rock, attack together!”

Lin Ming rapidly said to Xiao Moxian with a true essence sound transmission. As the many flower petals burst apart, he spread his formidable sense and quickly found the hiding spot of the 10,000 corpse flower’s main body.

The main body of the 10,000 corpse flower was extremely skilled at hiding. Even an experienced God Burying Ridge guide would find it difficult to locate it.

The reason that Lin Ming could accomplish this was because of the Divine Dream Law and his powerful divine sense. Moreover, it was also because when those many flower petals exploded, the main body of the 10,000 corpse flower received a backlash of energy, causing the energy fluctuations around it to wildly pulse about.

Hearing Lin Ming’s words, Xiao Moxian didn’t hesitate in the least. She slashed out with her whip, stirring up a terrifying wave of phoenix true fire!

At the same time, Lin Ming also followed up with his spear!

At that moment, from behind Lin Ming, the phantom of the Heretical God Tree appeared. The power of thunder and fire heavenly tribulation came tyrannically crashing down.

Bang!

A terrifying noise sounded out as a large chunk of this beautiful paradise was ripped apart. Then, a giant scarlet root that looked like a ginseng was raised out of the ground by this explosion. For a time, it was unknown how many root hairs were torn up.

Squee - !

The bright red root began to emit mouse-like screams in the air. It seemed to have a spiritual intelligence of its own and was struggling around in the force field in an attempt to escape.

“The 10,000 corpse flower was found by that youth?”

Fatty Zhou was completely shocked. Not only had Lin Ming broken through the besiegement of the 10,000 corpse flower but he had also dug out its main body.

The main body of the 10,000 corpse flower was not powerful at all; it only excelled in hiding. Once its hiding spot was found out, even a half-step Holy Lord powerhouse would be able to kill it.

Squeek! Squeek!

Beneath the horrifying pressure of the grandmist force field, the 10,000 corpse flower emitted waves of miserable screams. Its root body looked like an overfilled water bag, about to explode at any moment!

“Brother Lin, don’t destroy it! That is a precious type of raw medicinal material!”

Fatty Zhou quickly reminded Lin Ming as he saw the 10,000 corpse flower about to explode beneath the force field.

Lin Ming’s mind stirred. Without removing the grandmist force field he formed hundreds of seals with his hand that flew into the 10,000 corpse flower root.

“Divine Seal Art – God Forbidding Seal!”

Puff! Puff! Puff!

The aura of a black hole came shrouding over the 10,000 corpse flower, locking down the flow of energy within it! The 10,000 corpse flower wildly cried out as it was being imprisoned by the God Forbidding Seals, but soon after that there was no more sound as it was completely sealed away.

As the 10,000 corpse flower died, the remaining flower petals withered and fell. They slowly decayed, turning into red liquid that soaked into the ground.

The remaining survivors eyed Lin Ming and also the blood red 10,000 corpse flower in his hands.

This human youth was too terrifying! Such a dreadful disaster was easily solved by him!

Fatty Zhou knew that the reason Lin Ming was able to accomplish this was because he could be called perfect in all aspects. He had used that strange force field to break through the attack of the 10,000 corpse flower’s flower petals, and then he had used his far superior sense to immediately lock onto the position of the 10,000 corpse flower’s main body.

There was no weakness in the methods that Lin Ming had used. And thinking about his other aspects, he also surpassed everyone by far, far enough that they couldn’t look up to him. This was a true extreme genius!

“Little Sister… it seems we were mistaken about something… he does have the blood of an Azure Dragon within his body, but his achievements are not because of this blood. Rather, this bloodline is simply something that improves upon his perfection.” Dragon Cloud looked at Lin Ming, a strange feeling in his heart. As someone who was proud of his dragon clan bloodline, he was thoroughly overwhelmed by Lin Ming.

Chapter 1481 – Meeting Tian Mingzi

“Mm?” Xiao Moxian paused. Just now, she had also felt a powerful sense cover him. From this sense alone, she could tell that this other party was far stronger than an ordinary World King.

“Although you have a great destiny, who would have thought that I would have such bad luck following you. To think that in this damned place we’ve been caught by a World King powerhouse…”

Xiao Moxian took out a long whip from her spatial ring. Fleeing no longer had any meaning. Now that they had been locked onto by a World King powerhouse’s divine sense, with the difference in their speed it was only a matter of time before they were overtaken.

“Who is chasing you?” Xiao Moxian asked.

Lin Ming frowned. “I thought it would be the saint race’s Imperial Prince Naqi, but… it seems someone else has come this time.”

As the enemy approached closer and closer, Lin Ming could faintly feel that this person’s aura was becoming increasingly strong.

This was…

As Lin Ming thought of this person’s possible status, his pupils shrank. And in the next moment, his speculations were proven correct!

With a flash of black light, a tall and young-looking man appeared in front of Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian as if he had teleported there. He wore a long robe and held a black sword in his hand.

His body burned with faint black flames. His complexion was deep and gloomy and his dual pupils were blood red.

This person was Tian Mingzi!

At this time, Tian Mingzi’s entire body was gushing forth with a dense aura. His long hair flew in the wind, making him look like a demon god at night. It was a tremendous pressure to face this type of person.

“Lin Ming… it’s been a long time since we’ve seen each other…”

The man’s smooth and melodious voice contained an icy killing intent, as if it wafted up from the nine nether abyss.

“It really is you.”

Lin Ming grasped his Phoenix Blood Spear, his complexion dignified. This situation was far worse than he had anticipated! He had thought that only a World King had come, but now it was a Great World King powerhouse.

“10 years. I’ve been waiting for this day for 10 years.” Tian Mingzi slowly floated down to the ground, landing in front of Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian. He glanced over Lin Ming’s appearance and fiendishly grinned. “Your appearance changing technique is wonderful; to think that it can even change your aura. Unfortunately, that no longer matters.”

Lin Ming’s vision sharpened. His face began to gradually distort and transform. His skin became fairer and smoother, his looks became much more handsome and delicate, and he even grew, causing him to look stronger and more robust.

He had restored his original appearance, and beside him, Xiao Moxian had also lifted her concealment, returning to her originally beautiful appearance, that of an enchantress who could bring the downfall of nations.

“Young lady, you really are Ji Xian’er!”

Tian Ming looked at Xiao Moxian, causing her eyelids to jump. She certainly recognized Tian Mingzi. This was because Tian Mingzi had come from the Demondawn Great World and had also entered Demondawn Heavenly Palace in the past to study their inheritances.

However, she couldn’t rely on any graciousness that Tian Mingzi owed Empyrean Demondawn in the past. Tian Mingzi was already a traitor to his universe and now he no longer had any scruples. It was likely that he wouldn’t mind killing both of them here.

Xiao Moxian had the Dark Phoenix bloodline within her body and was considered a top quality alchemy material. The efficacy was the same as eating a living God Beast!

“So it’s you. Why are you hunting us?” Xiao Moxian coldly asked.

“That matter is far too complex to say. All sorts of grudges gathered together have doomed me to kill Lin Ming. I must say that I have waited for this day far too long! Thus, there is nothing you can do or say that will stop me today. Miss Ji, you don’t plan on staying with Lin Ming, right?”

Xiao Moxian continued silently holding her whip.

“Then that is too unfortunate…” Tian Mingzi began to stroke the front of his blade, killing intent overflowing from his body without end. “You should know that going against me now is the same as dying! Your grandfather showed graciousness to me, so I could have originally left you alive, however… ten years ago I lost a hand and I suffered tremendous damage to my blood vitality, even causing the spirit body I trained for so long to have a flaw. Now, it is not possible for me to step into the Empyrean realm. What I need are top grade blood elixirs to restore my lost blood vitality…”

As Tian Mingzi spoke he revealed the extent of his killing intent. At this time, he was like a human-eating beast.

Although Xiao Moxian was brave to the heavens, even she felt a cold chill crawl up her back. It was hard for anyone to directly face Tian Mingzi’s gaze.

He actually used such a casual tone to state that he wanted to eat her.

In all her years, Xiao Moxian had encountered many people with perverse ambitions who wanted to befriend her in order to gain benefits from her body. But, most of these people’s thoughts were to obtain her primordial yin and dual cultivate with her. Very few people were as crazy as Tian Mingzi!

Tian Mingzi lifted his sword high, his aura suddenly erupting. A fearful force field came falling down to lock in Lin Ming, preventing any chance that he could escape.

“Lin Ming, you don’t think that you still have any chance of escaping alive right now, do you? I will put everything I have into killing you and will not leave you any chance to escape. After you die, I will inherit your everything and I will even help you accomplish your unfinished dream of reaching that illusive peak of martial arts. As for you, you can become a stone that paves my road to the top!”

As Tian Mingzi spoke he hurtled forwards. The long sword in his hand came slashing out to behead Lin Ming!

As Tian Mingzi had said before, he didn’t hold back anything in his strike. A black sword light emitted a keening whistle as it tore through the surrounding space like paper. Beneath the imprisonment of the aura around him, Lin Ming couldn’t dodge at all. Even if he fled to the ends of heaven and the edges of the sea, this sword would still home in on him, following him forever!

This was the all-out strike of a Great World King, it absolutely wasn’t something Lin Ming could hope to contend with.

In this critical moment, Lin Ming poured all of his true essence into his inner world.

Origin energy violently surged. The moment Tian Mingzi’s sword pierced forwards, a palace of black stone left Lin Ming’s inner world, rapidly spinning, rapidly growing!

“Mm! This is!?”

Tian Mingzi was shocked. From this black stone palace he could feel an ancient and boundless aura; it was clearly some extraordinary thing.

Of course, even if this were some extraordinary treasure, Tian Mingzi didn’t think that it had any chance of harming him when used by a mere Divine Transformation realm martial artist. However, to be careful, Tian Mingzi avoided this black stone palace, his sword light circling around it and continuing to thrust towards Lin Ming!

As the sword light was about to cut off Lin Ming’s head, in that instant, a dark divine light shot out from the black stone palace, covering both Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian.

“Don’t resist!”

Lin Ming quickly said to Xiao Moxian with a true essence sound transmission. In truth, even without his sound transmission, Xiao Moxian was well aware of what was happening. She relaxed her guard, allowing that black light to sweep her up into the black stone palace.

In the next moment there was a terrifying explosive sound as Tian Mingzi’s sword crashed into empty space. The earth trembled as thousands of jins of sand was recklessly lifted up by energy, shooting into the world like a massive tsunami!

Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian were dizzy for a short moment but they were protected from the energy impact by the black light. Then, they landed within the black stone palace!

Peng!

With a muffled sound the two people hit a wall and bounced onto the ground. Lin Ming felt all the blood within his body tumble around and he stretched out a hand to brace himself. He felt something soft beneath his hand, and as he looked down he could see that Xiao Moxian was being pushed down by him.

“Sorry.”

Lin Ming awkwardly apologized.

“I’m sorry that you didn’t hurry up with that. Aiya, that really hurt!” Xiao Moxian rubbed her head. Just a moment ago her head bumped into the wall. Luckily she had her God Beast bloodline otherwise she would have been seriously bruised and beaten.

“What is this place?” Xiao Moxian asked.

“This is Primordius Heavenly Palace.” Lin Ming briefly stated. In the Eternal Demon Abyss, Lin Min had inherited the legacy of Empyrean Primordius. If he didn’t consider the Primordius martial intent then the Primordius Heavenly Palace was absolutely the most precious treasure that Empyrean Primordius had left behind! As long as he entered Primordius Heavenly Palace then any martial artist with a cultivation below the Empyrean realm would be unable to break through. Of course, the premise of all this was that Primordius Heavenly Palace had enough energy.

“Primordius Heavenly Palace?”

Xiao Moxian was startled. Before she could respond, the black stone palace violently shook. Xiao Moxian tumbled about, unable to hold back a shout as she was tossed into the air.

“Tian Mingzi is attacking us.”

Lin Ming’s thoughts stirred and images of what was occurring outside Primordius Heavenly Palace appeared above him.

Outside of the Heavenly Palace, Tian Mingzi was holding his sword with both hands and wildly hacking at the Heavenly Palace. However, his barrage of all-out attacks was only able to cause the Heavenly Palace to tremble. To break through its outer walls was actually impossible!

“Just what is this palace!?”

Tian Mingzi grimly said. He had thought he was going to kill Lin Ming, but now everything had suddenly changed at the last moment. This was a piece of meat near his mouth that had escaped at the last moment!

“This palace is protected by array formations, I can’t break through…” Tian Mingzi frowned. This palace was definitely something refined by an Empyrean, moreover it was definitely an extreme Empyrean powerhouse, otherwise there was no way just an array formation would be so firm!

“it really is Empyrean Primordius!” As Tian Mingzi looked at the black stone palace he could feel the aura of the primal grandmist universe. Before this he had already looked at as many ancient texts as he could find. With the information he gleaned he suspected that the supreme elder who died on the Sky Spill Planet was Empyrean Primordius, and now this confirmed his suspicions.

“The rumors said that Empyrean Primordius controlled some shocking secret in the past, something that alarmed even the saint race. Now, this secret is likely to have fallen into Lin Ming’s hands. If I can obtain it then I will ascend to the heavens with a single leap!”

As Tian Mingzi thought of this he grew increasingly excited.

Although Lin Ming was hiding within Primordius Heavenly Palace, Tian Mingzi wasn’t worried at all. Primordius Heavenly Palace relied on its array formations to protect itself, but these array formations needed an astronomical supply of energy. As long he continued to attack and exhausted the energy or Primordius Heavenly Palace, then catching Lin Ming was simply a matter of time.

Thinking this, Tian Mingzi summoned all the true essence within his body and readied himself to attack once more. But at this time, Primordius Heavenly Palace wildly shook. In the next moment it turned into a beam of light, shooting into the horizon like a meteor with unbelievable speed.

“What!?”

Tian Mingzi nearly bit his tongue. This palace could actually fly, and fly so quickly!

“Damn! If it continues flying deep into God Burying Ridge then I will have to face considerable risks to keep up with it, and wanting to capture it will be even harder!”

Chapter 1488 – Perfect Harmony

Bang!

With a terrifying explosion, a dreadful column of black energy erupted from deep within the God Beast Tomb, impacting into the skies!

The demonic tide had begun!

Lin Ming grabbed onto Xiao Moxian’s hand with even more strength. He didn’t expect Empyrean Divine Mist to lend him a helping hand. Empyrean Divine Mist was weakened to an extreme degree and the fires of his soul were greatly diminished. Although he could still use sound transmissions, he likely lacked the ability to help them resist the demonic tide. Moreover, he didn’t have any obligation to help them.

Rumble rumble rumble!

Like an angry roaring sea, the entire God Beast Tomb began trembling. A terrifying flow of energy began gushing out from deep within the tomb, washing towards the cliff with endless momentum!

Facing this dreadful storm of energy, Lin Ming didn’t immediately escape. Instead, his concentration was completely focused on that tumbling sea of black energy, as if he were thinking of something!

Lin Ming was indeed pondering something. On one hand, he had to observe the flow of demonic energy to see whether it conformed to the rules within the emperor jade’s dao field. On the other hand, he needed to see just what variations would occur when the demonic tide spewed forth from the God Beast Tomb.

“Lin Ming!”

In this critical moment, Xiao Moxian’s complexion completely changed. Her hand was pulled tightly by Lin Ming but he didn’t seem as if he was planning to run away at all. Instead, he stood there as if he were in a daze. If they continued to stay here then both of them would die miserable deaths!

“Go!”

Grasping Xiao Moxian’s hand, Lin Ming turned and fled!

Lin Ming flew in front and Xiao Moxian behind him. She followed his exact footsteps, her body fluttering forwards like a piece of cotton as she was pulled forwards by Lin Ming as if she didn’t weigh anything at all!

Just as they took several steps away, a brilliant black beam of energy shot up 30 feet in front of them, piercing through space like a sharp sword. To even pierce through the void, the degree of sharpness that this energy beam had was unimaginable!

Seeing this beam of energy in front of her, Xiao Moxian paled. It seemed that the eruption of demonic energy would come not just from deep within the God Beast Tomb, but also from underground!

If they had walked just a few dozen feet further forwards then they would have been struck by this demonic energy and their fates could be imagined!

Lin Ming held onto Xiao Moxian’s hand as before, seeming as if he didn’t even see this column of energy. He continued wildly dashing forwards; this was a race with his life on the line!

“He can actually remain so calm! His disposition and foundation are impeccable. If such a good seedling could have been my disciple then my life’s work wouldn’t perish with my death… but what a pity… the demonic tide is heartless. No matter how calm a martial artist is, that alone cannot save them. He and I… will both die, and it is only a matter of time.”

A bitter and bereft voice echoed through the God Beast Tomb. If it were a World King with a deep foundation, they could rely on their protective true essence to resist the demonic tide. But, a Divine Transformation realm martial artist simply didn’t possess this ability…

Bang!

Another beam of black divine light broke through the ground in front of Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian, piercing through the void. This black divine light was more than fierce enough to take both their lives! To flee in such an environment, this could barely be described as frantically dancing upon a knife’s edge!

Xiao Moxian didn’t even doubt that they would both die in the next moment! Each time they seemed to encounter a stroke of good luck and avoid being struck by these energy beams, but they would be struck sooner or later!

She following Lin Ming without knowing what direction she was going. In this apocalyptic scene, Xiao Moxian felt the world fall far away from her, with only this hand grabbing her own seeming to exist. This powerful hand was true to the touch, even causing a bit of pain with how tightly it held onto her…

Lin Ming’s strong feet pumped across the mottled rocks. Energy surged within him and his divine sense radiated outwards, rapidly sensing all of his surroundings! However, wanting to use his sense to discover where the next explosions of energy would occur was useless, even for someone like Lin Ming who cultivated the Divine Dream Law. It was impossible for his sense to penetrate the ground of God Burying Ridge that was covered by a massive dao field.

Bang!

Another beam of divine light shot upwards. This time, it came from right beneath Xiao Moxian’s feet!

In that moment, Xiao Moxian felt herself lighten as if she would turn into ashes at any moment. She couldn’t help but cry out in alarm!

The feeling of being on the verge of death was like an electric current that shot through her body!

At this moment, time seemed to come to a standstill. But then, Xiao Moxian felt a great strength cover her body, wrapping her up and forcefully ripping her away from her position.

The black divine light rubbed against Xiao Moxian’s right half, disintegrating her clothes.

“Lin Ming!?”

Xiao Moxian could barely collect her scattered wits. The one who pulled her away just now was Lin Ming. He had already switched direction ahead of time, thus he didn’t step onto that beam of energy and was able to pull her away in time!

As if he knew where that energy was going to erupt from to begin with.

“He avoided it? Was that a coincidence?”

It wasn’t just Xiao Moxian, but even Empyrean Divine Mist was startled; he also thought of this idea. Even that eruption of energy had been avoided by Lin Ming. Could this still be described as a coincidence?

Empyrean Divine Mist couldn’t believe that. The ground rock of Tragic Death Valley was extremely bizarre, and no sense was able to pierce through it. Even a Great World King wouldn’t be able to determine where the next eruption of energy would appear, so how could a human youth accomplish that?

Empyrean Divine Mist didn’t have any time to think about this; Lin Ming had pulled Xiao Moxian upwards and flew towards the precipice of Tragic Death Valley!

Beneath the distortion of the Space Laws, Lin Ming easily climbed up the several dozen mile cliff. He was able to borrow leverage from the cliff, jumping hundreds of feet each time.

Woosh! Woosh!

Crazy flows of energy shot out from the cliff face without end, but Lin Ming seemed to have some incredible ability to predict where they would emerge and managed to avoid them the moment they shot out. This was true whether the energy flows were in his immediate vicinity or not!

Underneath this horrifying tide of energy, the ground and mountains were torn asunder. The earth cracked apart and black serpents of fire continued to jet outwards. The demonic tide became increasingly fierce, increasingly violent. Xiao Moxian felt that what she was breathing was no longer air, but the chaotic flow of energy!

Peng!

Another energy flux shot out. Lin Ming rolled over on the cliff, perfectly avoiding this beam that seemed as if it would absolutely hit him!

And at this time, Xiao Moxian, who was being pulled forwards by Lin Ming, was left completely speechless. This clear pattern of evasion absolutely could not be explained by coincidence. It was clear that Lin Ming could foresee where the dangers would erupt!

How was he doing this?

Xiao Moxian couldn’t imagine how it was possible. In terms of sense and soul force, with the support of her own God Beast soul, she wasn’t necessarily any worse than Lin Ming, who studied the Divine Dream Law.

But, she was completely unable to feel where the energy tide would erupt from.

“This junior, just how is he doing this?” In the God Beast Tomb, Empyrean Divine Mist was surprised. All of this was completely unexpected and it surpassed his scope of understanding. It was obvious that Lin Ming possessed some ability that allowed him to accomplish this.

The eruption of energy continued. Compared to the black sea of energy that swelled up from the God Beast Tomb, the true dangers lay in the energy beams that shot out from the ground and walls. They were virtually unavoidable.

If one could avoid these then there was no need to fear the demonic tide!

And Lin Ming seemed to have the ability to foresee where the energy would erupt.

Lin Ming’s concentration was completely focused on dodging. He zigzagged around, holding onto Xiao Moxian’s hand the entire time.

With her hand held by Lin Ming, Xiao Moxian felt as if she were holding onto the entire world. Even when the world seemed to be ending, this hand was her safe haven, making her feel as if she could rely on it.

Dreadful black waves crashed against the rocks, splashing up tens of thousands of feet. These waves were also dodged by Lin Ming.

The rocks were torn apart by energy. The ground underneath Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian’s feet had nearly turned into a black sea.

Such a scene continued for a quarter hour of time. Then, the energy tide began to weaken and no more chaotic energy erupted. Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian came to a stop atop a rock on the precipice of the cliff.

At this time, Lin Ming’s entire body was drenched with sweat. Because he had used up too much strength and because of how tense everything was just now, his forehead had blue veins sticking out and his fingers were softly trembling.

It’s over…

As the black waves fell away, Lin Ming let out a long sigh of relief. He felt weak with exhaustion.

Beside Lin Ming, Xiao Moxian hesitated for a moment and then stretched out a hand, wiping away Lin Ming’s sweat. Her other hand was still being held by Lin Ming. With their two hands grasped together, there was an inexplicable feeling of the two being in perfect harmony.

As they fled all the way here, Lin Ming’s mind was too tense and concentrated, so he never noticed how it felt to hold onto Xiao Moxian’s hand.

In fact, this was the first time Lin Ming had held Xiao Moxian’s hand. Although he had grabbed her arm before, he was separated by the cloth of her sleeves.

But now, he was truly holding her palm in his.

Xiao Moxian’s hand was soft to an unimaginable degree, and calling it warm and fragrant wasn’t enough to describe it. As he held onto her hand, he felt his entire body be refreshed, like a parched traveller taking a taste of clear spring water at an oasis, making his entire body feel comfortable. Lin Ming wasn’t a virgin who had never been intimate with a woman before, but this was the first time he felt something so marvelous when holding onto someone’s hand.

“How could this…”

Lin Ming was startled and yet he wasn’t willing to release Xiao Moxian’s hand for some time. Because of the special circumstances just then, he had no choice but to grab her hand and fly, but now that the danger had abated, with Lin Ming’s personality he wouldn’t continue taking advantage of her.

However, as he released her hand, he felt an unexpected feeling of dismay. This wasn’t because of the emotions between men and women, but because his bloodline and soul blended together well with hers.

Lin Ming had absorbed a 1000 foot Azure Dragon bone and he had the Azure Dragon bloodline within him. As for Xiao Moxian, she was the descendant of a phoenix, a true blood child of a phoenix.

Dragon and phoenix, rejoicing together!

It wasn’t just Lin Ming who was feeling this, but Xiao Moxian was the same. She had a strange lingering sadness at releasing Lin Ming’s hand. Although Lin Ming’s Azure Dragon bloodline could hardly be considered rich when compared to her own, his foundation was solid and his body was tempered to an amazing degree, even touching upon the boundary of the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace.

In terms of bodily toughness, Lin Ming didn’t lose out to Xiao Moxian!

From Lin Ming’s body, his blazing astral essence and yang-attribute Azure Dragon blood subtly vitalized her bloodline, making her feel satisfied.

Chapter 1494 – Asura Sutra General Outline

…

…

…

When the demonic power was suppressed by the Asura Sutra, Empyrean Divine Mist’s sound transmission echoed out near Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian’s ears. “So that’s how it is. You both obtained the Asura Sutra general outline left behind by the Asura Road Master. It seems that you two have perfectly left behind your names atop the Emperor Stone…”

The moment Xiao Moxian and Lin Ming entered the God Beast Tomb, Empyrean Divine Mist’s sense had locked onto their bodies, not leaving them just yet.

Thus, he naturally witnessed the scene where Lin Ming helped Xiao Moxian use the Asura Sutra to overcome the summoning attraction of the demonic power.

“Does Senior also know the Asura Sutra general outline?” Lin Ming thought out loud.

“Yes. The Asura Sutra general outline is rare, but in these countless years there have also been people who were able to perfectly leave behind their name on the Emperor Stone, thus it has spread out from them. I once tried myself to perceive something from it, but my natural talent was lacking and in the end I couldn’t perceive anything at all. I never imagined that the Asura Sutra general outline could have such fantastic effects in the God Beast Tomb. Just meditating on it allows you to resist the attack of that demonic power.”

When Empyrean Divine Mist referred to his own talent as lacking, he was being modest about it. With his extreme Empyrean cultivation, he had made very little harvests upon meditating on the Asura Sutra general outline. This was because the Asura Sutra general outline was a mere several hundred words and didn’t contain any specific cultivation method; it was only an outline of the Heavenly Dao. Although it contained profound and mysterious principles, it wasn’t possible for him to perceive anything through it.

“You have perceived the Asura Sutra general outline?” Empyrean Divine Mist asked Lin Ming.

“Yes, this junior obtained the Asura Sutra general outline from the Emperor Stone seven years ago and I have been enlightening myself upon it this entire time.”

“Seven years… of meditating upon the Asura Sutra, and you have also researched the God Beast Tomb… did you recognize that the Asura Sutra general outline is the key to opening the God Beast Tomb?” Empyrean Divine Mist guessed that this was the reason Lin Ming dared to venture deeper into the God Beast Tomb. Lin Ming was smart and had recognized that the Asura Sutra was related to the God Beast Tomb’s array formation.

However, Empyrean Divine Mist had also meditated on these two things before and was well aware of just how horrifyingly profound and mystical the principles contained within them were. The God Beast Tomb was an array formation spread over several thousand miles and was complex to the extreme! As for the Asura Sutra general outline, it was only a mere several hundred words, inversely simple to the extreme!

Whether it was complex to the extreme or simple to the extreme, wanting to perceive something from either one was as hard as ascending to the heavens. As for connecting the two together, wasn’t that easier said than done?

“Seven years and only several hundred words, how much could you have perceived from the Asura Sutra general outline?” Empyrean Divine Mist faintly said.

“Junior’s comprehension is poor and I also lack the main text of the Asura Sutra, thus… my understanding is actually very shallow.”

“Alright.” Empyrean Divine Mist heaved a deep sigh. He knew that urging was useless because Lin Ming wouldn’t listen to him. “My divine sense can continue for 600-700 miles, but after that I can go no further. You must take care of yourself!”

After Empyrean Divine Mist said these words he fell silent.

Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian continued going deeper into the God Beast Tomb, and the summoning of the demonic power grew increasingly strong. From the start, Xiao Moxian was able to meditate upon the Asura Sutra general outline to easily withstand this strange call, but after they were almost a hundred miles in, that terrifying demonic power had nearly turned into essence.

Chi chi chi!

A ghostly fire began to burn in front of Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian. In just several breaths of time, this ghostly fire transformed into a fierce demon. It had gruesome features with fangs and claws. Two wings stretched out from its back and it held a trident in its hand, looking like the Asura King from nighttime stories.

The demon roared and hurtled towards Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian!

Xiao Moxian paled as she saw this demon. Just this casual demon that appeared had an aura comparable to a half-step World King!

This was still the outer edge of the God Beast Tomb. If they continued deeper in, who knew what they would encounter! No wonder it was said that even an Empyrean would perish here!

“Chant the Asura Sutra together!”

Lin Ming hurriedly shouted out as this demon rushed towards them. Xiao Moxian’s pupils shrank. At this time she didn’t need Lin Ming reminding her to know that her only method was to use the Asura Sutra to battle this enemy. A half-step World King demon was not an existence she could contend with on her own!

Xiao Moxian’s cherry red lips opened and moved, the words of the Asura Sutra enunciated clearly. The words condensed into glowing runes in the air, flying towards the Asura demon like a flock of birds and locking it in place!

“How fierce…”

After locking down that Asura demon, Xiao Moxian grimaced in surprise. She had poured her complete strength into her words and yet only managed to barely lock down this Asura demon; she hadn’t been able to destroy it at all.

And at this time, Xiao Moxian heard a series of explosive sounds around her. Not too far away, several black demonic flames burst into existence, condensing into new Asura King phantoms. These Asura Kings were formed from the overwhelmingly rich demonic power here, every Asura phantom stronger than the first!

Xiao Moxian was dumbstruck. This was too terrifying! They were two Divine Transformation realm martial artists, but here they had to face several half-step World Kings!

How could they begin to fight them?

She couldn’t help but look towards Lin Ming. From the moment they entered the Great Desolate, without noticing it, she had slowly started to depend on Lin Ming. Although he wasn’t too much stronger than she was, whenever there was some danger that occurred he would be able to easily resolve it.

At this time, Lin Ming focused his energy into his inner world. The Heretical God Force and Eight Inner Hidden Gates opened together. Because he seemed to breathe in too much, his entire body seemed to inflate, and a strong aura of the power of thunder and fire filled his mouth and nose!

In that moment, Lin Ming squatted down a little and opened his mouth to shout out loud and release massive tongues of thunder and flame!

The power of thunder and fire was fused into Lin Ming’s breath. He began to speak, and as his words echoed out, each syllable was fierce and thrilling, shocking the mind, seeming to crash down like heavenly tribulation, containing a holy and destructive power beyond description. The power of thunder and flame howled out, rolling through the air like thunderclaps, igniting the world with 10,000 flames!

What Lin Ming was loudly proclaiming was the Asura Sutra general outline. Compared to Xiao Moxian’s version, it was dozens of times more massive!

In that instant, an Azure Dragon phantom appeared behind Lin Ming! It was like a Divine Dragon was awakening in Lin Ming’s body, sending out an earthshaking roar!

With Lin Ming’s body as the center, visible sonic waves wantonly spread out, surging from him like a storm.

“33 Heavens! The boundless Great Dao!”

A horrifying sound echoed within the world. With a loud crash of thunder, the demonic power all around them was destroyed and those Asura phantoms were torn asunder by these dreadful sounds.

Golden runes formed the general outline of the Asura Sutra. Underneath the suppression of these glowing runes, all of the Asura phantoms began to continuously explode!

Peng! Peng! Peng!

Like this, over ten half-step World King Asura demons were ripped into fragments by Lin Ming!

The few remaining Asura demons were greatly weakened, their condition extremely poor. They wanted to escape, but Lin Ming clasped his hands together and the golden runes crashed down upon them with a dreadful pressure.

With a cracking sound, these final demons were all completely killed off.

All the Asura demons turned into demonic power that fluttered all about them.

Off to the side, Xiao Moxian was shocked as she saw this.

Although they had both chanted the Asura Sutra general outline, how come there was such a great difference between the two of them?

“Lin Ming… what cultivation method did you use just now?”

Xiao Moxian thought that Lin Ming should have used some sonic wave type cultivation method, but before Lin Ming could respond, Empyrean Divine Mist’s shocked sound transmission echoed out to her.

“Lin Ming… when you meditated upon the Asura Sutra general outline, did you become aware of the Asura Road Master’s ‘Dao’?”

The reason the Asura Sutra that Lin Ming had shouted out just now was able to have such an effect was not because he had used any secret technique on his voice, but because he had an astoundingly deep comprehension of the Asura Sutra!

The Asura Sutra general outline was a mere several hundred words long and each word stood by itself. There was no concrete cultivation method nor was there any description about moves or techniques. From this, it was simply impossible to utilize it in battle. Yet, under Lin Ming’s comprehension, the Asura Sutra general outline had become a deadly life culling weapon! That mantra of several hundred words was able to eliminate his enemies!

Empyrean Divine Mist had never thought this possible.

Although he himself had meditated on the Asura Sutra in the past, in the end he didn’t obtain any harvests.

“Senior is far too exaggerated. This junior has merely obtained some superficial insights, and I am still far, far away from becoming aware of the Asura Road Master’s ‘Dao’. From this Asura Sutra general outline, what I can understand is only one 10,000th of the truth within it. I can only waste its potential and shout it out loud to destroy my enemies here. But, the true function of the Asura Sutra general outline is to help guide a martial artist towards the peak of martial arts and help them find where the direction of the Great Dao lays. This is the summary of the Asura Road Master’s 33 lives, and the direction it points to might be to a realm even above that of a True Divinity. This junior simply cannot see it clearly.”

As Lin Ming assiduously meditated for seven years, he could increasingly feel just how mighty the Asura Road Master truly was.

“To transform the words of the Asura Sutra into a strength that could be used to kill others is already fantastic.” Empyrean Divine Mist sighed with emotion. “The Heavenly Dao is vast and endless. In its endless cycles, who can see its direction? For you to arrive at this step is already astonishing. Perhaps you are right. If one morning I could gain knowledge of the correct path then I could die at sunset without regrets. I will no longer try to change your mind. Go forth and break through this God Beast Tomb’s great array formation, whether you succeed or fail.”

“Thank you Senior for your understanding. I will not disappoint Senior’s expectations.

Lin Ming respectfully cupped his hands together. As he turned back around, the demonic power had already vanished. All that appeared in front of him was a massive city wall created by the bones of a God Beast!

The pale white walls were formed from bones, shocking and alarming!

“What is this?” Xiao Moxian said, bewildered. This city wall seemed to emerge from thin air. Before this moment, she had never noticed it at all.

“33 Heavens Asura Bone City. Within these city walls lies the main center of the God Beast Tomb’s great array formation…”

Chapter 1495 – 33 Dao Diagrams

“33 Heavens Asura Bone City?” Xiao Moxian was startled. She never thought that deep within the God Beast Tomb would be a city wall built from God Beast bones.

“Let’s enter.”

Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian flew towards this massive city wall. 10,000 feet in the air, they were able to see the world behind that wall of white bones.

Then, Xiao Moxian saw something she would never forget in her life.

After that wall of bones was not endless barren and desolate earth, nor was it some wilderness. Rather, it was more accurate to say that this didn’t seem like they were in some valley at all, but the endless starry skies!

The infinite starry skies were broad without end. And floating in these starry skies were massive dao diagrams.

Because the distance was too great and these starry skies were too vast, Xiao Moxian found it hard to determine how large these dao diagrams were. As she probed with her sense, she finally sucked in a deep breath of astonishment.

These dao diagrams were thousands of miles large; they were comparable to a small planet!

All of these dao diagrams floated still in the skies. At the center of each array diagram was the complete skeleton of a God Beast.

These God Beast skeletons were clearly different from the God Beast remains near the outer edges of the God Beast Tomb.

The bones at the edges of the tomb had weathered the passage of billions or even tens of billions of years. Their blood had long since dried up and there was no value to them besides the bones themselves.

But, the bones in these array diagrams were shining crystalline like jade. These bones were exuding a rich blood vitality, seeming as if they were alive!

These beast bones even emitted the aura of a God Beast, forming a God Beast phantom above them. There were phoenixes soaring into the highest heavens, dragons leaping through the misty sea – it was like these God Beast bones would revive at any moment.

“This place is…” Xiao Moxian looked at this vast array formation, shocked. These complete God Beast skeletons were several hundred miles high and thousands of miles long. As they floated in the vast infinite space, their size was bewildering to the senses!

As for Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian, in this space they were nothing but tiny particles of dust, completely not worthy of mentioning.

“This is the true God Beast array formation. Without a doubt, the passage to leaving Tragic Death Valley should be here!”

Lin Ming closed his eyes and allowed his sense to recklessly spread outwards as he verified what he knew with this array diagram.

“There are 36 dao diagrams here and 33 God Beast skeletons. The central three dao diagrams are empty.”

Lin Ming murmured to himself. He had already expected this scene after perceiving it from the emperor jade.

“I never imagined that… this would be the scene of the array formation within the God Beast Tomb. I attached my divine sense to your body and it seems you’ve broadened my horizons.

Empyrean Divine Mist softly said. If it weren’t for Lin Ming then his sense wouldn’t have been able to break through the chains of the demonic power and he wouldn’t have been able to see the true array formation.

“36 dao diagrams. Each dao diagram has its own guardian God Beast sealed within it. The inherent killing intent is endless and peerless. Such a terrifying aura already completely surpasses any Empyrean, to a point where it is hard to look up to. If an Empyrean were to step into such a dao diagram they would immediately perish!”

Empyrean Divine Mist didn’t doubt how terrifyingly deadly these 36 dao diagrams were. Just the aura alone was fearful enough.

“How do we pass this?”

Xiao Moxian asked. She had never seen such a scene before. In particular, after listening to Empyrean Divine Mist’s analysis, she deeply understood just how terrifying this array diagram was.

If she had to enter this array diagram then her pathetic cultivation level could basically be ignored. Just any speck of light could turn her to ash without the smallest chance of escaping.

“Let’s go over!” Lin Ming succinctly said.

These three simple words caused Xiao Moxian’s heart to skip a beat. Even Empyrean Divine Mist hesitated, but if Lin Ming was so confident in himself then he should have researched this 33 array diagram beforehand.

For seven years, Lin Ming had been sitting quietly in meditation above the cliff. How had he managed to perceive the Asura Road Master’s God Beast Tomb array formation?

Empyrean Divine Mist sucked in a light breath. He could feel that there were far too many secrets on Lin Ming’s body. With Lin Ming’s Divine Transformation realm cultivation, he wanted to contend with the array formation left behind by the Asura Road Master. This sort of decision was far too shocking!

“Can he really succeed?” Empyrean Divine Mist couldn’t help but produce such an idea. He didn’t think that Lin Ming would die now, because Lin Ming arriving at this point was already a miracle, even if this miracle was because of the Asura Sutra general outline.

Empyrean Divine Mist was well aware that if Lin Ming truly managed to break through the God Beast great array formation, there was a high chance he would find the method to leave Tragic Death Valley. And ever since the Asura Road was formed, there had never been a person who had left Tragic Death Valley!

“Come with me!” Lin Ming took hold of Xiao Moxian’s hand and together they flew towards one of the 36 dao diagrams.

The dao diagram that Lin Ming chose shined with a brilliant spectrum of rainbow light. At the center of the dao diagram was a flame-colored skeleton, shining like heated rubies, brilliantly burning. This was a phoenix!

“Phoenix…”

As Xiao Moxian saw this crystalline phoenix skeleton, her body shook. Her bloodline roiled within her, faintly resonating with the phoenix skeleton.

“This is a royal amongst all phoenixes, and a peak royal at that!”

Xiao Moxian whispered to herself. The God Beast skeletons within the 33 dao diagrams were not from common God Beasts, but the most peak existences amongst all God Beasts!

If one could absorb the phoenix marrow within this phoenix skeleton, then whether it was Xiao Moxian or Lin Ming, either of them would experience unimaginable benefits.

Of course, this was only wishful thought. This phoenix skeleton was locked onto the array formation and impossible to obtain.

When Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian stepped onto the dao diagram, the dao diagram erupted with seven brilliant fountains of light. These seven fountains of energy were the colors of a rainbow, thrusting into the sky like seven divine swords.

All around these erupting fountains were beams of divine light formed from energy. These divine lights were as sharp as sword lights, recklessly shooting about.

Looking at these distant erupting fountains, Xiao Moxian could clearly feel the terrifying strength contained within them. Although they appeared beautiful and enchanting, the truth was that these fountains of energy could easily shatter apart stars! If one’s mortal body was sucked into those fountains, then one would absolutely die; not even an Empyrean could escape!

Facing this titanic power that could eliminate the heavens and earth, Xiao Moxian felt that her own strength was far too little.

Even those divine lights that flowed out from around them were extremely terrifying. Xiao Moxian hesitated for a moment and then took out a high-grade spirit artifact, carefully tossing it into the cutting path of the divine lights.

The moment that the spirit artifact touched those divine lights, there was a slight cracking sound as the high-grade spirit artifact was easily cut in half by the divine light. The halves of the spirit artifact were sucked into the light, and in the next moment that high-grade spirit artifact had been reduced to nothing but dust!

Although she had already expected this result, Xiao Moxian still sucked in a cold breath upon seeing for herself how sharp this divine light was. Destroying a spirit artifact was bad enough, but disintegrating a spirit artifact into dust was even more terrifying!

And, what was even more dreadful was that these divine lights were only tiny beams that leaked out from the main seven rainbow fountains; they weren’t even comparable.

Then, just how terrifying should the main body of that divine light be?

Xiao Moxian was clear that this dao diagram was not something that a person could contend with. Even if there were 1000 copies of her, all of them would die inside.

After throwing away that destroyed spirit artifact, Xiao Moxian looked towards Lin Ming.

All she could rely on now was Lin Ming. And facing those terrifying fountains of energy, even Xiao Moxian wasn’t too confident in his chances right now.

At this time, Lin Ming was floating motionlessly. His eyes were like two stars that shined with a dazzling light, his sense capturing the entire dao diagram.

This was one of the 33 dao diagrams; Essence Gathering – Five Elements!

The 33 dao diagrams represented 33 different ways to cultivate the Great Dao. There were 11 body transformation kinds, 11 essence gathering kinds, and 11 soul forging kinds. This dao diagram in front of them was one of the essence gathering paths to cultivating the Great Dao!

Lin Ming chose this dao diagram because this essence gathering dao diagram closely resembled humanity’s cultivation system. Lin Ming possessed high attainments in this domain, and the Thunder and Fire Laws he practiced also belonged to the power of the five elements.

Lin Ming took a step forwards, revolving all the true essence within his body to the limit. Behind him, the phantom of the Heretical God Tree began to slowly appear.

The Heretical God Force Lin Ming used was extremely overbearing. Within his level, there was no martial artist that could compare with him. If he revolved the Heretical God Force to the absolute limit and combined it with Three Essences As One, then in terms of true essence intensity alone, even Xiao Moxian’s Counterforce Heaven Absorbing Demon Art would have a hard time comparing to it.

But now, in front of these terrifying fountains of energy that erupted into the skies, Lin Ming’s Heretical God Force was nothing but a little trickling stream flowing next to the raging seas; there was no comparison between them at all. Lin Ming’s strength was only that of a person, but that erupting energy fountain seemed to contain the strength of the universe.

Just what was Lin Ming planning to do?

Xiao Moxian’s eyes widened. She found it hard to imagine what would happen. Lin Ming had summoned the Heretical God Tree, but relying on this weak strength, what could he do to this massive dao diagram?

Lin Ming’s mind focused into his inner world. In his inner world, the azure emperor jade began to shine with a dim brilliance.

Lin Ming’s true essence poured into the emperor jade without end, slowly spinning around the lines within it.

This process continued for several breaths of time.

The energy that was poured into the emperor jade came gushing out. Then, the energy condensed into Great Dao runes, each one containing the charm of the emperor jade!

Several hundred Great Dao runes spun around, forming a complete dao diagram.

This dao diagram spun out from Lin Ming’s inner world, slowly coming to a rest above his head where it slowly revolved.

Then, after a brief period of time, a second dao diagram shot out from Lin Ming’s inner world.

Then a third, a fourth…

After a quarter hour passed, 33 dao diagrams spun around Lin Ming’s body, wrapping him within.

“Come in.” Lin Ming said to Xiao Moxian.

Xiao Moxian immediately walked into the barrier of dao diagrams.

The space within these 33 dao diagrams was extremely narrow. Xiao Moxian was nearly stuck skin to skin with Lin Ming, and they could even feel each other breathing.

Being so close to Xiao Moxian, Lin Ming’s nose was filled with her fragrance. He could even feel her soft body beneath her clothes.

Although this sort of feeling was infinitely enchanting, at this time, all of Lin Ming’s concentration was focused on the task at hand without diverting even the least bit to anything else. This was a moment that concerned his life or death!

“Follow me. You must absolutely not walk beyond the range of the dao diagrams.” As Lin Ming spoke he began to walk towards those seven erupting fountains of rainbow energy.

After understanding what Lin Ming wanted to do, Xiao Moxian was shocked. Her eyes went wide and her face was filled with disbelief. Lin Ming actually planned to enter those erupting fountains of energy like this?

Chapter 1501 – Opening the Coffin

“Lin Ming, you think that the Essence Spirit Embryo Stone is sealed within the coffin?” Xiao Moxian immediately knew what Lin Ming was thinking from the light in his eyes.

“It really might be so.”

Lin Ming walked near to the ancient bronze coffin. This coffin had lain here for countless years and the surface of it was covered with carved images. These images included fierce Asura demons, ancient vicious beasts, and even martial artists of other races.

Thick chains wrapped around this coffin, and every chain buckle was covered with runes. Because too much time had passed, the divine iron that formed the ancient coffin and chains was stained with rust, filled with an atmosphere that seemed to come from the deepest depths of time.

Through the crevices in these iron chains, Lin Ming could see the scenes on the ancient coffin. There were Asura demons eating humans and even humans burning demons as a sacrifice to Asuras.

There were also ancient vicious beasts ripping apart people to shreds as well as people striking vicious beasts and drinking their blood.

In short, all of these scenes were filled with a tyrannical, brutal, and cruel feeling. Looking at them caused killing intent to surge in the heart, as if it would erupt at any moment.

Lin Ming squatted down near the ancient bronze coffin. The coffin was as wide and tall as the book, appearing extremely heavy. The coffin lid and coffin body seemed cast together, without the slightest gap separating them.

“This ancient bronze coffin also exudes demonic power…” Lin Ming’s eyes sharpened. The demonic tide that occasionally erupted in Tragic Death Valley was related to the first volume of the Asura Sutra, but a part of it also came from this ancient bronze coffin!

“If we open it will something ominous happen?” Xiao Moxian weakly said as she saw all the violent carvings atop the coffin. Tragic Death Valley had existed for billions of years, and with the time enchantment here, dozens of billions of years had passed. For such a long time, this ancient bronze coffin had existed within the center of the God Beast Tomb array formation. It was hard to imagine just how much essence energy was absorbed here and what it could have been breeding.

It had to be known that the things in Tragic Death Valley could easily kill a World King. If this Essence Spirit Embryo Stone had already taken form then the terrifying strength it possessed was something neither she nor Lin Ming could deal with.

“Lin Ming, do you think that these chains are locking in the embryo stone to prevent it from breaking out of the coffin?” Xiao Moxian suddenly asked. Lin Ming was silent for a moment. There was indeed a great risk if they opened up the ancient coffin, especially when he still knew so little about the Asura Sutra’s first volume.

“Maybe. But no matter what happens if I open the ancient coffin, I will still open it. Still, I must fully perceive the Asura Sutra first.”

Lin Ming would certainly open the ancient coffin. In order to arrive here he had to take numerous risks and complete something that countless ancient heroes had never done before. Now, he would soon obtain the Asura Road Master’s inheritance. If anyone were to tell him to give up here then that would simply be a joke.

All Lin Ming could do now was to thoroughly perceive the Asura Sutra to reduce the risk to the smallest level possible.

Like this, Lin Ming sat in meditation in front of the Asura Sutra and assiduously enlightened himself upon it.

As for Xiao Moxian, she also accompanied Lin Ming in meditating on the Asura Sutra together. Of course, in terms of comprehending the Asura Sutra, Lin Ming was naturally faster than she was.

Thus, if Xiao Moxian were to run into any questions of spots she found difficult to understand, she was able to consult Lin Ming.

Slowly, Xiao Moxian also gained a deep understanding of the Asura Sutra. Her perception was extraordinary to begin with, and in addition to Lin Ming’s guidance, her rate of growth slowly rose. This caused Lin Ming to praise her without end. In terms of perception alone, she indeed surpassed him.

Training passed without sense of time. Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian sat in meditation within this hall every day. Like this, a full year passed them by.

Whether it was Lin Ming or Xiao Moxian, the foundation of their mortal bodies was outstanding. And, the Asura Sutra First Volume revolved around cultivating the mortal body. The Asura Sutra cultivated essence, energy, and divine. The main difference from other cultivation methods was that when the Asura Sutra was cultivated to the extreme, a martial artist could gather essence, energy, and divine unto themselves and then reach an inconceivable boundary.

However, every positive had a negative. Although the Asura Sutra was a cultivation method that pointed towards the peak of all martial arts, the route it took to get there was extremely time intensive. It required a massive accumulation of time, on the magnitude of millions of years, in order to show its true strength.

The days of seclusion were boring and dry. As Lin Ming meditated, he often exchanged information and insights. At the start, it was him helping Xiao Moxian. But afterwards, Xiao Moxian provided him with many unique thoughts and inspirations.

Due to the limit of their cultivation it was impossible for them to cultivate the Asura Sutra First Volume to the limit. Even so, the two of them fully carved the Asura Sutra First Volume deep into their hearts. Now, even if they lost the ancient bronze book they could still recall the Asura Sutra in full detail, including the various Concepts and textures and feelings of the runes.

Another half year passed. Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian combined everything they understood into one. At this point, they had already spent a total of nine years in Tragic Death Valley.

In these nine years, Lin Ming’s cultivation had made considerable progress, in particular, the last half year in which he was perceiving the Asura Sutra First Volume. He was only half a step from reaching the Divine Lord realm.

“I see. So this is the original appearance of the God Burying Ridge’s dao field…”

After perceiving the Asura Sutra First Volume, Lin Ming recalled the traces of the dao field that were carved within the emperor jade. Many things he couldn’t understand before had suddenly become clear to him.

Now, if Lin Ming were to leave Tragic Death Valley and explore God Burying Ridge, he could rely on his understanding of the Asura Sutra to wander about with absolute freedom and safety, even with his eyes closed.

“God Burying Ridge is divided into death roads and life roads. When life roads reach the extreme, mortals can safely enter and exit. When death roads reach the extreme, even World Kings will perish. And of God Burying Ridge’s extreme death roads, there are a total of seven spots.”

Lin Ming murmured to himself. The so-called guides of God Burying Ridge were the product of the countless experiences and knowledge accumulated by their seniors. These people had tested the many death roads until they had found the one life road into God Burying Ridge. They simply didn’t understand the true principles that lay behind the God Burying Ridge’s dao field, and had simply relied on their own empirical methods of testing to find a way to avoid danger. This was why being a God Burying Ridge guide was such a dangerous occupation, one that always teetered on a knife’s edge.

Then, Lin Ming’s eyes flashed open from his meditation. He stood up and walked towards the ancient bronze coffin.

Xiao Moxian’s thoughts stirred. “Lin Ming, are you planning to open the coffin now?”

During these past days, she and Lin Ming had reached a bottleneck in their understanding of the Asura Sutra. This was the limit placed upon them by their cultivation level and broadness of their horizons. Until they became stronger, it would be hard to experience another breakthrough.

When a martial artist cultivated the martial path, it was impossible for them to go into seclusion and directly leap up several large boundaries. They had to constantly adventure and gain more experiences, and then realize new things from these experiences. They had to constantly fight in order to temper themselves. If they were to go into seclusion for all their life, not only would that weaken a martial artist’s true combat strength, but it would cause their comprehension of Laws and cultivation methods to stagnate.

“Now is as good a time as any.” Lin Ming nodded his head. “We’ve been in Tragic Death Valley for nine years now. We’ve done everything that we can and have reached the limit of what we can accomplish here. It’s about time that we think of leaving this valley, but before we go I must open this coffin.”

Lin Ming took out the emperor jade from his inner world. Then, he held the emperor jade in his hand as he prepared himself to open the ancient bronze coffin. The risks were unknown and it was impossible to know just what would come out from the ancient coffin. It might be an unrivalled treasure but it also might be a life-reaping killing intent!

With the emperor jade in hand, Lin Ming felt things would be much safer. Thinking about it, the Asura Road Master shouldn’t have deliberately left a killing trap here for his future inheritors to open. That would simply be too great of a joke.

Because too much time had passed, the chains on the ancient coffin had melded together with it. Lin Ming took a deep breath, linking his hands together and forming hundreds of seals, each seal resonating with the runes on the chains.

In that instant, the runes on the chains began to shimmer one at a time. The entire hall was illuminated with a dazzling light. With a light popping sound, all of the chains fell apart.

Lin Ming pressed his hands on the coffin and glanced at Xiao Moxian. “Do you plan on staying here?”

Lin Ming cautioned her. He was afraid that if some evil being really did emerge, then Xiao Moxian would suffer a gruesome fate like he would. But if she left earlier then she would be able to survive.

Xiao Moxian chuckled, indifferently saying, “At this time do you really think I would change my mind? Hey, if I’m here maybe I’ll be the one saving your life.”

Xiao Moxian wasn’t bragging. In terms of overall strength, although she was inferior to Lin Ming, she wasn’t too far off. If Lin Ming encountered some danger then with Xiao Moxian here he would have a much higher chance of surviving.

Lin Ming faintly smiled. He didn’t bother speaking any more. His fingers suddenly grasped down and gripped two corners of the ancient coffin.

With a loud shout, crackling sounds emitted from all over his body. The Heretical God Force erupted, the Eight Inner Hidden Gates opened, and from behind Lin Ming the phantom of a True Dragon appeared!

At this time, he bent down, focusing his strength into his waist. His spine curved like a taut bow as all his strength passed into his arms. A power equal to nearly a billion jins of strength suddenly broke out!

Rumble rumble rumble!

The ancient bronze coffin that had lain here for 100 billion years was shoved open by Lin Ming!

In that moment, it seemed as if what Lin Ming pushed open was not the lid of a coffin but a door leading to another world!

Ka ka ka ka!

The entire bronze temple shook. The ground trembled. With loud rustling sound, a beam of light descended from high above, shining atop the Asura Sutra. Countless runes of the Great Dao swirled about, gathering together in a purple kaleidoscope to form a door of light!

“This is… a portal!?”

Xiao Moxian held her breath. For a door of light to suddenly appear, seeming as if another world was behind it, this should be a portal!

Did this portal lead to the outside?

Xiao Moxian couldn’t help but think this, a sense of excitement rising in her mind.

She had already stayed in the absolute darkness of Tragic Death Valley for several years. Moreover, before she entered the God Beast Tomb with Lin Ming, a wisp of despair had begun growing in her heart. Now that she realized she could soon leave Tragic Death Valley, how could she not be excited?

However, being pleasantly surprised was only one matter. At this time, Xiao Moxian’s concentration was completely focused on what was happening around her. Her right hand touched her spatial ring, ready to deal with any dangers that arose.

What was in the ancient coffin?

If it were a treasure, then they could naturally take it and everyone would have a happy ending. But if it were an evil being, then both she and Lin Ming would face a life or death crisis.

Chapter 1505 – Becoming A Divine Lord

Bang!

Lin Ming’s body shook. In that moment, a terrifying power rushed into his body. This was the power condensed by the God Beast array formation, and now it was pouring into his body, breaking into his inner world!

Lin Ming had already foreseen this change when he unraveled the seal, but he didn’t expect the impact to be so wild and intense. His inner world seemed as if it couldn’t withstand this strength and wanted to crack apart!

If his inner world cracked open then his fate could be imagined. In this life or death moment, Lin Ming had an obvious choice; he could open his inner world and let this tyrannical strength gallop outwards. In doing so, although it would make things safe for him, it would actually waste away a large amount of essence energy that the God Beast array formation had accumulated.

A sharp light blew up in Lin Ming’s eyes. He didn’t open his inner world. Instead, he relied on this ferocious strength to begin rapidly increasing the boundaries of his inner world! He wanted to take advantage of this opportunity and break into the Divine Lord realm!

This was a crazy decision. Underneath the torrents of so much wild energy, if he couldn’t withstand the pressure of this energy then his inner world would develop cracks all over it and it would be nearly impossible to recover from. The reason Lin Ming dared to do this was because he had absolute confidence in his own foundation as well as the intensity of his body!

As energy filled him, Lin Ming’s body emitted explosive crackling sounds. The blood vessels under his skin ballooned upwards, making it seem as if they would all collapse at any moment.

In the Nine Divine Shifts, the Divine Lord realm was the last boundary. Divine Lord, Divine Lord, the meaning of that was to truly become divine! Of course, this ‘divine’ was relative to common mortals. A Divine Lord martial artist could hold a world within their body and enjoy the worship of mortals. To mortals, they would be a god. As for the True Divinity boundary in the road of martial arts, this was a divine god of martial artists. A True Divinity powerhouse could control an entire universe. To them, the title of True Divinity was well deserved!

An ordinary Divine Lord powerhouse could already create their own clan or establish their own eighth-grade sect. They could create an inheritance that lasted for hundreds of thousands of years, become an ancient ancestor, and enjoy the devotion of countless disciples and followers.

In the Divine Realm, a Divine Transformation martial artist could already wander the world. A Divine Lord realm martial artist was a true character.

As for Lin Ming, once he became a Divine Lord he could instantly kill a Holy Lord. To a certain degree, he could even contend with a World King!

In the entire Divine Realm, besides in Empyrean Heavenly Palaces, World Kings were extremely rare even in a great world. They were figures that countless martial artists respected and revered. There were many peak Holy Lands that had inheritances of millions of years and yet they couldn’t produce even a single World King!

Thus, to Lin Ming, the Divine Lord threshold was extremely significant!

However, for Lin Ming to break through the Divine Lord realm in this situation, the pain he had to withstand could be imagined.

Underneath the tremendous pressure, Lin Ming’s blood vessels ballooned up from beneath his skin, even breaking apart. Blood seeped out from all of his pores! This blood mixed with his sweat, making Lin Ming look as if he were being bathed in blood.

And within Lin Ming’s inner world, the crazy energy impacted towards him, strong enough to cause mountains and rivers to shake. His inner world was originally filled with spiritual energy, but now it was filled with a terrifying energy storm. Those spiritual plants within his inner world were smashed apart in this storm, turned into innumerable fragments!

In his inner world, rivers changed course, lakes evaporated, and mountains collapsed!

In his inner world, it seemed as if the end of times had arrived.

“Heretical God Tree!”

Lin Ming roared out. Within his inner world, the towering Heretical God Tree stretched out its lush branches and vibrant leaves, stabilizing it.

The massive root system held the earth of Lin Ming’s inner world firmly in place. With this divine tree stabilizing Lin Ming’s inner world, everything became much more stable. However, a powerful pressure caused Lin Ming’s body to balloon; the blood vitality within him seemed as if it would burst out in the next moment.

Lin Ming grit his teeth and opened the Eight Inner Hidden Gates to the limit. With the dual support of his formidable mortal body and the Heretical God Tree, he forcefully withstood the impact of energy. Then, with a ‘ka ka ka’ sound, the boundaries of Lin Ming’s inner world began to break open!

As the boundaries of Lin Ming’s inner world opened, the void outside of the world was constantly fused with pure energy. Lin Ming’s inner world was growing, evolving!

Once his inner world opened up there would be an avenue for the energy to drain out of. The pressure on Lin Ming began to rapidly reduce.

Slowly, the bulging blood vessels beneath Lin Ming’s skin began to shrink back down. Blood also stopped leaking from his pores. Like this, Lin Ming had crossed the most difficult stage. Following this, breaking through the Divine Lord realm was only a matter of time.

However, because Lin Ming had withstood the terrifying pressure, nearly all of his blood vessels had burst open and even his inner world had been wrecked in the baptism of that ruinous energy storm. In addition to him having branched out a proportion of his divine soul into his essence energy avatar, he would be greatly weakened for a long period of time.

“Lin Ming, you’re really too reckless, you always do things to the extreme. Anyone that follows you will have a permanent heart attack.” Xiao Moxian had been watching Lin Ming’s entire breakthrough process from the side. She was left somewhat speechless by everything.

From entering God Burying Ridge then falling into Tragic Death Valley, the two of them had survived demonic tides together and had even rushed into the God Beast Tomb array formation. After that, Lin Ming had risked his soul to refine the essence energy avatar. He was always making her heart race without end.

Lin Ming’s lips twitched and he laughed. “I still haven’t yet reached 60 years of age. From the time I was 15 years old, I've spent the following 40 years of my life struggling like this. I cannot compare to someone like you who comes from an Empyrean background. From birth you possessed an unachievable talent that mortals could only dream of as well as the support of endless precious resources. I am simply a martial artist that came from the lower realms, moreover I am even a martial artist that originates from the most common stock of mortals. Although I encountered my own lucky chance in the lower realms that changed my fate, relying on that alone would not have been able to make up the difference between us. I had to risk everything I had. I had to risk my life on lucky chances and even risk my life to step further on the road of martial arts, otherwise it would have been impossible for you to see me standing here.”

Because of his exhaustion, Lin Ming’s words seemed a bit faint, as if they were lacking energy. But as these words fell onto Xiao Moxian’s ears, they caused her heart to shake.

In truth, she had already heard that Lin Ming came from a common mortal birth. He wasn’t someone who was taken in by an Empyrean level character as a disciple, but he still managed to attain his current incredible achievements.

This sounded like a fantastical bedtime story, and even Xiao Moxian had been skeptical of it, half-doubting it the entire time. Now, she had confirmed this from Lin Ming himself. Not only was he a common person, but he was even a common person of the lower realms. Within the entire Divine Realm as well as the billion plus worlds of the lower realms, there were countless common mortals, but their lives only lasted for a mere several dozen years. They were truly like ants, continuing generation after generation. For a common mortal of the lower realms to arrive at Lin Ming’s current level and have his achievements, this was simply unbelievable!

In comparison, Xiao Moxian herself came from Demondawn Heavenly Palace and was the most beloved daughter of the monster race and demon race. Disregarding her resources and inheritances, she possessed a rare half-phoenix body, something that might not even occur in a billion years. Yet, for all that she had, her present achievements were no better than Lin Ming’s.

This caused Xiao Moxian to feel a bit ashamed of herself. How could anyone live in the presence of such a freakish genius?

Chapter 1513 - More and More Murder

“A World King powerhouse died by my hands!”

At this time, Lin Ming’s blood was still tumbling within his body. He had yet to fully recover from that violent collision just now.

This was the first World King that Lin Ming had killed, but it wouldn’t be the last. This was because before long, he would have to face the next World King!

That would be a truly savage battle. Either they would die, or he would perish!

“Old… Old Zhou…”

Not too far away from where Mister Zhou had miserably died, the half-step World King that was barely managing to live watched helplessly as everything occurring around him. His two eyes were already dull and glazed over.

When he saw Lin Ming block Mister Zhou’s all-out strike he felt as if he were living in some sort of dream. In that maniacal clash of energy, Lin Ming and Mister Zhou had both been sent flying backwards. However, Lin Ming had avoided the murderous black divine light, and as for Mister Zhou, he had died a horrible death!

“This Lin Ming is simply a demon…”

This was the half-step World King’s last thought. Within a breath of time of Mister Zhou’s death, the 108 iron-armored spectral soldiers rushed over to the altar and hacked him to meat sauce!

Like this, the squad that Mister Zhou led here had been completely annihilated!

However, Lin Ming didn’t relax at all. He looked over to those 108 iron-armored spectral soldiers that were approaching.

Chik chik chik!

After the iron-armored spectral soldiers killed the last saint race martial artist, they turned in unison to Lin Ming and pointed their weapons at him.

Lin Ming’s heart tightened. He slowly retreated, but the 108 iron-armored spectral soldiers continued to press down on him!

He had expected this situation from the very start. Every time he took a step he was able to step on a life zone of the black stone altar’s dao patterns in order to avoid that terrifying black light. But, these iron-armored spectral soldiers were different. Once they were activated, it was hard to say whether or not they would attack him!

In order to minimize the danger, from the start Lin Ming had never disturbed the grave of Blue Throne Bai Qi. Instead, he used words to provoke Mister Zhou into action.

Otherwise, if he only wanted to activate the great array formation here, Lin Ming wouldn’t even have tried to goad his enemies but would have directly attacked them.

The iron-armored spectral soldiers approached closer, step by step. Lin Ming held his breath, his palms wet with sweat.

“Asura Heavenly Dao, Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel!”

Lin Ming lifted his hands. Behind him, a brilliantly red wheel appeared. This wheel was engraved with innumerable demons and Asura phantoms. Runes covered its surface, just like the runes that covered the surface of the ancient bronze coffin in the God Beast Tomb array formation. This wheel was thick with the smell of blood and slaughter!

The so-called Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel was the 10,000 life and death samsaras experienced by 10,000 demons. The pain that these demons suffered in their 10,000 samsaras, their sins, the heavenly tribulations they faced, all of their karma was carved into a wheel and condensed into infinite demonic power. This was an offensive and defensive technique!

However, the reason Lin Ming used the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel was not to attack or defend. He was well aware that with his limited strength it was simply impossible for him to oppose these 108 iron-armored spectral soldiers. Even if he were to hide within Primordius Heavenly Palace, he would have to face the barrage of attacks from the great array formation. Sooner or later, Primordius Heavenly Palace would run out of energy and he would be in the same dead end as before.

The only way out of this predicament for Lin Ming was to use the power of the Asura Heavenly Dao and obtain the approval of Blue Throne Bai Qi’s array formation.

The Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel slowly spun. In the moment that a tide of great demonic power surged out, the 108 iron-armored spectral soldiers froze. The weapons in their hands also slowed down. Their blazing red eyes all focused on the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel above Lin Ming. Those 108 iron-armored spectral soldiers had been demons before their death, and they had a natural sense of awe and subservience upon seeing this Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel.

Lin Ming held his breath, keeping completely still. This sort of feeling was just like a common mortal facing 108 vicious tigers. A single careless move would mean a fate where he didn’t even have bones remaining!

This stalemate lasted for a dozen some breaths of time. To Lin Ming, this time was as long as hours. Then, from the black stone altar, beams of black light shot out. Black lights each struck an iron-armored spectral soldier, and these iron-armored spectral soldiers that were struck immediately returned to being black stone sculptures.

In a short period of time, the 108 iron-armored spectral soldiers completely transformed into black sculptures and gathered again around the black stone altar. The sealed off space crack also re-opened.

One difference was that these 108 iron-armored spectral soldiers were in different positions from before. And, the blazing red light in their eyes hadn’t yet gone out. This proved that the array formation was still in an active state.

“I’m safe… for now!”

Lin Ming let out a long sigh of relief, his body dripping with sweat. To face such a close encounter with death, the pressure on him had been great.

Stepping on the life zone dao patterns, Lin Ming stepped off the black stone altar. He used black flames to eliminate the pieces of meat and blood on the ground. After that, he removed all traces of combat and also received Mister Zhou’s spatial ring and treasures that he dropped. Then, like a ghost, he flitted back to the shadow of the great array formation, waiting in ambush yet again.

He was like a wolf hiding in the dark, waiting for his prey.

He also summoned Primordius Heavenly Palace. This Heavenly Palace contained the Laws of Space and Time and was able to shrink and grow as he pleased. Currently, Primordius Heavenly Palace was only the size of a table. Lin Ming placed it atop a life zone of the black stone altar’s dao patterns, and then with a flash, Lin Ming’s figure submerged into it.

As soon as Lin Ming entered Primordius Heavenly Palace he relaxed his body. He immediately began to swallow down pills, sitting down in meditation to control his breathing. He was fully aware that the battle he experienced just now was only the appetizer. Soon, he would have to face more battles, in addition to the extremely deep Tian Mingzi. Lin Ming felt a sense of dread when he thought of Tian Mingzi; he had to adjust himself to his peak condition to face him.

After an incense stick of time, Lin Ming opened his eyes from meditation. He saw Xiao Moxian sitting not too far away from him. When Xiao Moxian had entered Lin Ming’s inner world, she also entered Primordius Heavenly Palace within him.

At this time, Xiao Moxian was leaning back in a chair, her long legs propped up on a stone bench. Her snow white thighs were vivacious, filled with the vitality of youth.

“I didn’t imagine you would also have this kind of move.” Xiao Moxian chuckled. For a time, it was like spring had arrived.

She was referring to when Lin Ming had stood atop the black stone altar and had mercilessly taunted and enraged the saint race martial artists. This sort of Lin Ming was simply far too different from how he was normally.

“The situation required it.” Lin Ming wryly smiled.

“Well, nice acting!” Xiao Moxian leapt down from her chair. “What are we going to do next?”

“Wait.”

Lin Ming didn’t have any better methods. Bai Qi’s tomb was an extremely dire and ominous place, but not every spot in this hall was dangerous.

The black stone altar was likely to be where Bai Qi was buried. If Bai Qi’s corpse was really interred there, then that black stone altar was undoubtedly the most important place in the entire tomb as well as the most dangerous place. To wait there was the wisest and safest choice.

“The absolute killing array here can identify my Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel. Moreover, those 108 iron-armored spectral soldiers are not a force that Tian Mingzi can deal with. If we’re here, we can control the battlefield. However, there’s just something I’m worried about…”

Lin Ming faintly frowned as he spoke.

“What are you worried about?”

“I’m worried that Tian Mingzi might have some hidden card in hand or perhaps he might be plotting something else. When we left Tragic Death Valley, we stepped into the tracking array formation that he laid down and we have his tracking mark within us! The area outside of Bai Qi’s grave isn’t too dangerous. By all rights, with Tian Mingzi’s strength, he should have caught up to us by now. If so, then the first ones to come here shouldn’t have been that one called Mister Zhou, but Tian Mingzi!

“Besides Tian Mingzi there is also Imperial Prince Naqi. Imperial Prince Naqi wasn’t with that Mister Zhou fellow, so there can only be two possibilities. Perhaps he never came to God Burying Ridge, or perhaps there is someone even stronger protecting him. That person might be Tian Mingzi or it might be someone else!”

In Lin Ming’s opinion, Imperial Prince Naqi had an extremely important role in the saint race. Generally speaking, Imperial Prince Naqi should also be the most closely guarded.

Tian Mingzi was a Great World King. In terms of strength, he was much better than Mister Zhou. However, he wasn’t a saint after all and anyone would find it hard to trust in others that weren’t of their race. With the saint race’s naturally arrogant and suspicious minds, Imperial Prince Naqi most likely wouldn’t seek out protection beneath the wing of Tian Mingzi, but with Mister Zhou. However, he didn’t do this. This caused Lin Ming to suspect that during his time in Tragic Death Valley, Imperial Prince Naqi had found an even stronger helper.

As Lin Ming was thinking this, the warning array he left outside of the black stone altar was touched. At this time, the warning array was directly shattered. Lin Ming’s thoughts turned cold. Someone had come, and they were apparently much stronger than Mister Zhou!

Chapter 1516 – The Furious Ash Murder

Seeing Imperial Prince Naqi grievously injured by his spear strike, how could Lin Ming give him a chance to recover? Taking advantage of his weakened state, Lin Ming stepped forwards, slashing out the Phoenix Blood Spear to take Naqi’s head!

To finish off his opponents without any reservation, this was how Lin Ming fought!

“Your Highness!”

Beside Naqi, Manyu cried out in panic. If the Imperial Prince died then it would be because of his protection being flawed. Once he returned to the saint race he would suffer extreme penalties.

“You dare to injure the Imperial Prince of my people? I’ll take your life!” Manyu grabbed a saber and cut out at Lin Ming’s waist, wanting to use this attack to force him back.

Lin Ming shouted out loud and a broad and ancient stone gate appeared beside him. This stone gate was as stable and still as a mountain, completely blocking Manyu’s saber strike!

Kacha!

The saber slashed down on the stone gate. The stone gate only trembled a little but not a single mark was left behind.

“Out of my way!”

Lin Ming struck his palm out on the stone gate. The stone gate howled out, suppressing Manyu!

“This brat!” Manyu was shocked. Lin Ming’s strength had far exceeded his imagination! By himself, he actually faced all of them together and had taken the upper hand! Although it could be said that Lin Ming took advantage to sneak attack them the moment they were all focused on dealing with the 108 iron-armored spectral soldiers, for him to accomplish this was nearly unbelievable. After all, he only had an early Divine Lord cultivation.

Manyu didn’t have time to think about how Lin Ming broke into the Divine Lord realm in just a few years; he had to face off against this incomparably heavy Primordius Gate. This area was an absolute killing zone. Although Lin Ming was able to recklessly dash about, Manyu definitely didn’t have the courage to do so.

He slashed out several hundred saber lights, all of the saber lights crashing onto the Primordius Gate and releasing a dazzling explosion. At the same time he roared out loud and used his fists to punch against the Primordius Gate. He wanted to use his powerful saint race body to forcefully resist the Primordius Gate.

His entire body swelled with blood vitality, some of it even leaking out the corners of his mouth. He turned around and what he saw left his body icy cold. Lin Ming had already arrived in front of Naqi. Naqi’s face was pale. Right now, his life hung on the thinnest thread!

Lin Ming’s attack was merciless. With a sharp thrust of his hand, the Phoenix Blood Spear whistled forth, howling towards Naqi like a raging red dragon!

As long as this spear struck, Naqi would die without a burial ground!

But as soon as the Phoenix Blood Spear was about to strike Naqi, a gray rope whipped outwards and wrapped around Naqi, immediately carrying him away!

Bang!

The Phoenix Blood Spear heavily smashed into a space barrier. The space barrier trembled and divine light shot out, but the space barrier didn’t even have the tiniest crack. This was the space barrier that held Bai Qi’s grave; not even a Great World King was able to break through it.

“Just a little bit more!”

Lin Ming darkly sighed in regret. Just a little more and he would have killed Naqi!

As he turned around, he saw Naqi wrapped in the gray rope and shooting towards a gray-robed man. Naqi entered his inner world, vanishing from sight.

This gray-robed man was that mysterious Mister Ash Murder.

“So you are Lin Ming! To think that you would ambush us here. You little beast, I will take your life!”

Ash Murder was so angry that his insides were gurgling within him, seething with rage! Lin Ming had chosen the time when his concentration was completely focused on other matters to sneak attack him. Before this, he didn’t even know that Lin Ming had been hiding here. Lin Ming’s sudden appearance had left Ash Murder startled.

The battle array that Imperial Prince Naqi and the others formed had been shattered by Lin Ming, and the two puppets were also crushed apart by him. Not just that, but Lin Ming had made him lose his concentration in order to save Naqi. This caused the pressure of those 108 puppets to be even greater on him!

“This brat was already long waiting in ambush here. He was waiting for us to break out of the array formation before he sneak attacked us!”

Ash Murder wasn’t an idiot; he was able to immediately understand what was happening. A junior that was only several dozen years old was able to freely move within a danger zone of God Burying Ridge, a place where even World Kings could perish. Not just that, but he was able to keep guard in this ancient array formation and ambush a half-step Empyrean!

This boldness and these methods caused even Ash Murder to feel a cold chill run down his spine.

Lin Ming glanced at Ash Murder and simply didn’t bother him with. He turned around and immediately attacked Manyu!

Although Ash Murder had invested all of his strength into sealing away the 108 iron-armored spectral soldiers and was unable to divert his attention, he still possessed a half-step Empyrean cultivation and likely had many terrifying abilities. Lin Ming found it hard to contend with an ordinary World King right now. If he approached Ash Murder, a simple strike would severely wound him or even kill him.

The most intelligent plan would be to wait until Ash Murder was completely exhausted by the iron-armored spectral soldiers, and then Lin Ming could wait for a chance to deal with him.

“Brat, you really do not know the meaning of death or danger!” Manyu was already enraged by Lin Ming. He had been caught off guard by Lin Ming’s sneak attack and now that he saw Lin Ming continue to attack him, he roared out loud, grasped his saber and slashed out at Lin Ming!

All of his strength was poured into this saber strike without any held back! He had already seen Lin Ming’s strength with his own eyes, but he didn’t believe that Lin Ming had the strength to kill a half-step World King in frontal combat.

A saber cut out, the saber light piercing through the dark like a bolt of lightning. At this time, the Phoenix Blood Spear was still covered with the interwoven power of thunder and fire, but it was different from the previous red and purple spear light. This time, Lin Ming’s spear also contained a gray light, one that seemed to swallow all of existence!

This gray light was concealed in the spear light, seeming common and humble, something that no one would notice. After all, it wasn’t strange for a martial artist’s attack to cause an eruption of multi-colored lights. These lights were the colors of the various Laws.

Kacha!

An explosive whistling burst out and Lin Ming’s figure suddenly came to a stop. His spear crashed into the saber and the power of thunder and fire erupted, surging outwards!

A terrifying impact spread through Lin Ming’s body, causing him to fly away. He didn’t lose his balance because of Manyu’s attack, but had used the attack to swiftly bounce away like a bird. As for Manyu, his body shook for a moment before he stabilized himself.

“Manyu, join forces with my contract beast and delay Lin Ming! I just need you to buy me some more time!”

Ash Murder shouted as blue veins stuck out all over his face. In that collision just now, Lin Ming had been forced back and Manyu had only shaken a bit. This allowed Ash Murder to let out a breath of relief. As long as Manyu could suppress Lin Ming, then all he had to do was seal away these iron-armored spectral soldiers. Once he did so, killing Lin Ming was only a matter of time.

“Awoo!”

With Ash Murder’s order, the silver blue wolf contract beast let loose a howl as it hurtled itself towards Lin Ming!

In that explosion just now, the silver blue wolf had also been injured. But, the life force of an ancient vicious beast was extremely tough. Even if it were severely wounded it could still stubbornly continue fighting!

The silver blue wolf flanked Lin Ming and leapt at him. At Ash Murder’s order, Manyu should have joined in to attack from Lin Ming’s right. However, as the blue wolf rushed forwards, Manyu remained motionless as before.

During his collision with Lin Ming just now, when Manyu broke through the thunder and fire heavenly tribulation, an all-swallowing black light had shot into his spiritual sea!

This black light was a soul attack that came from the inheritance of Empyrean Divine Mist – this was Empyrean Divine Mist’s transcendent divine might!

Empyrean Divine Mist’s soul attacks were completely different from all other soul attacks that Lin Ming knew of. Most soul attacks used one’s own soul as the weapon, and if the attack failed, one would receive a backlash to the soul. But, Empyrean Divine Mist’s soul attacks could actually use energy to directly strike an opponent’s soul, without any need for using one’s own soul as the attack medium.

As long as one fused this energy into their attack, then this attack would have both a material attack as well as a soul attack; this was a nearly unstoppable strike!

“What is happening?”

Seeing Manyu remain motionless, Ash Murder was confused. Manyu hadn’t died but his mind had entered a state of utter chaos, one that he was unable to rid himself of.

And at this time, Lin Ming welcomed the silver blue wolf. With a loud shout, he opened the Eight Inner Hidden Gates to their limits. The phantom of a True Dragon reappeared behind him. “Celestial Tyrant Manual – Hundred Layered Waves!”

In an instant, 100 spears thrust out and fused as one. Lin Ming’s bodily strength suddenly increased by several times, reaching several billion jins of strength!

After losing Manyu’s pincer attack, the silver blue wolf had to face Lin Ming alone!

Bang!

Lin Ming’s spear crashed into the silver blue wolf’s skull!

An impact force of several billion jins erupted. With a loud cracking sound, the silver blue wolf’s skull caved in and its two eyeballs were popped out by the pressure.

“Awoo!”

The silver blue wolf emitted a sorrowful howl. Its magnificent body was directly pounded into the ground by Lin Ming’s brutal and absolute strength. Fresh blood and pieces of meat were sent flying out!

Lin Ming’s attack was ruthless, giving no chance of reprieve. He stepped forwards, thrusting his spear out at the silver blue wolf’s throat!

The Phoenix Blood Spear pierced through, and with a twist, the silver blue wolf’s throat and neck were torn apart as the spine was completely severed. Like this, the silver blue wolf died a miserable death!

“Silverback!”

Seeing Lin Ming kill his own contract beast, Ash Murder’s eyes turned red with rage! His blue wolf wasn’t strong. Although the blue wolf was an ancient vicious beast, ancient vicious beasts normally grew at a slower pace than the mortal races. He had tamed the blue wolf far too early and although Ash Murder was at the half-step Empyrean realm, the blue wolf was only equal to a mid to late Saint Transformation realm martial artist. At this point, the blue wolf was no longer able to provide much help to Ash Murder, but Ash Murder had always felt an extremely deep sentimentality towards this contract beast that he had raised for hundreds of thousands of years. Now, this contract beast of his had been killed by Lin Ming’s spear strike. How he could not hate!?

“Brat, I will pull out your soul and tear you to pieces!”

Ash Murder angrily roared. He felt like a lion that had been wrapped in chains and was now being played around with by a mouse!

As for Lin Ming, he simply didn’t care about Ash Murder’s threat. He turned around and rushed towards Manyu, who was still frozen by his soul attack!

At the same time, Ash Murder’s body burnt all over with gray flames. His face turned as red as fresh blood!

Then, he suddenly bit down on the tip of his tongue and spat out blood essence. This blood essence began to brilliantly burn!

Ash Murder had been pushed to the brink by Lin Ming. Without any hesitation, he burnt his blood essence to use an arcane skill. He vowed to kill Lin Ming here and now!

Chapter 1517 – Angering One To Death

Piki paka!

Ash Murder’s entire body erupted with astral essence. His upper robes tore apart, revealing a vibrant and thickly muscled body as strong as diamonds. These muscles were completely covered with blue veins that stuck out like worms, continuing to inflate!

As his muscles inflated, Ash Murder also increased in size. His skin split apart and massive bone spikes stretched out from his body, shining with a cold light.

Many saint race martial artists were capable of body metamorphosis and Ash Murder was no exception to this. With an enraged half-step Empyrean burning his blood essence and then metamorphosing his body, it could be imagined just how dangerous he was!

Chi-la!

All of Ash Murder’s clothes split apart. Behind him, a pair of dripping wings stretched out, similar to a bat. Ash Murder’s arms also grew to seven or eight feet long, as long as an adult was high. His arms were covered with blue veins and had claws that were sharp and fierce!

After transforming his body, Ash Murder resembled a savage demon!

As Ash Murder transformed his body, the gray ropes he formed with his sealing technique also burst apart!

With Naqi’s combat array broken, it was no longer realistic for Ash Murder to think of sealing away these 108 iron-armored spectral soldiers, especially in the face of Lin Ming’s assault.

With this being the case, he no longer bothered with sealing away the spectral soldiers. Instead, he chose to fight. He wanted to tear apart Lin Ming and then break through this array formation of iron-armored spectral soldiers!

Although these spectral soldiers were strong, once he ripped apart a corner it would be possible to escape!

“You little beast, give me your life!”

After burning his blood essence, Ash Murder’s face was blood red. He completely ignored the iron-armored spectral soldiers and crazily threw himself towards Lin Ming, wanting to kill this human brat who he hated to the extreme.

Seeing Ash Murder hurtle towards him, Lin Ming remained calm. For Lin Ming to face Ash Murder in this condition would be a hopeless battle.

Then, a table-sized gray palace shot out from Lin Ming’s inner world, rapidly spinning about. Lin Ming sank into this palace, vanishing from sight.

This was Primordius Heavenly Palace, an escape route that Lin Ming had kept in place all this time.

Seeing this, Ash Murder sneered. “You want to hide away in your abode but you will die all the same! I will crush your turtle shell!”

Kacha!

With a terrifying sonic boom, Ash Murder’s claws struck Primordius Heavenly Palace. The grand array formation within the Heavenly Palace violently trembled. However, although the array formation shook, there wasn’t the slightest crack in its defenses. Primordius Heavenly Palace had solidly withstood Ash Murder’s attack!

According to Empyrean Primordius, as long as Primordius Heavenly Palace was given enough energy, no force below that of an Empyrean would be able to break through it. Although Ash Murder had transformed his body and burnt his blood essence, he was still a half-step Empyrean. Moreover, he couldn’t be considered an outstanding existence amongst half-step Empyreans. Between him and a true Empyrean, the difference was immeasurably vast. It was absolutely impossible for him to break through the defenses of Primordius Heavenly Palace!

“What!?”

That strike just now had caused Ash Murder’s arms to go numb. He didn’t think that his all-out strike would actually be blocked by such a common-looking palace.

With his strength, he could crush thousands of miles of mountains and rivers, and yet he couldn’t even break apart this table-sized palace.

“Is this an Empyrean spirit treasure?”

Ash Murder immediately thought. An Empyrean spirit treasure wasn’t too rare; even he possessed them. But, most Empyrean spirit treasures were weapons and armor. In their life, an Empyrean ordinarily refined two or three Empyrean spirit treasures, and with the countless Empyreans that had appeared in the 33 Heavens through the billions of years of history, there were many weapons and armors left behind by them.

As for other categories of Empyrean spirit treasures such as accessories, flexible armors, pill furnaces, or other such treasures, they were mostly ignored. These types of objects had extremely harsh requirements in terms of materials and array formations needed. An Empyrean wouldn’t normally refine such items, thus not many of these types of Empyrean spirit treasures existed.

And, if there was a category of Empyrean spirit treasure that was rarer than those, that would be an immortal abode spirit ship!

A weapon could be refined from a piece of divine iron, but a dwelling was different. It required far too many complex structures and array formations, making it so that it would inevitably be shaky and weak. But now, Lin Ming’s Empyrean spirit treasure was such a rare immortal abode spirit ship.

And, if it could block his attack so easily, then it likely wasn’t just an Empyrean spirit treasure, but the highest peak of Empyrean spirit treasures.

All of these thoughts passed through Ash Murder’s mind like a bolt of lightning. But at this time, his complexion immediately changed. He could feel a massive killing intent lock onto him; he had stepped onto a death zone dao pattern!

“Damn!”

Ash Murder cursed in his heart. This wasn’t a coincidence at all, but a plan Lin Ming had thought of from the start!

Lin Ming had deliberately stood behind this death zone dao pattern. When Ash Murder attacked Lin Ming, he had stepped into this trap!

Woosh! Woosh! Woosh!

Hundreds of black divine lights shot out from all directions, blocking all directions for Ash Murder to dodge in!

In that moment, Ash Murder was so enraged that his hair almost flew straight up and his eyes nearly popped out of his head. His intestines hurt from anger so much that they twisted in his body!

In this encounter with Lin Ming, he had been suppressed and controlled at every turn, suffering loss after loss. How could he not be infuriated.

“You little bastard, you remember me!”

Underneath the net of black lights, dodging was no longer possible. Ash Murder roared out loud and closed his two wings around himself. He stimulated his astral essence to the limit, forcefully resisting this strike!

This was an absolute killing zone that Lin Ming had carefully chosen; it was at least a hundred times more dangerous than normal danger zones. Since Lin Ming wanted to kill Ash Murder he naturally had to choose the riskiest place!

Peng!

Thick beams of black light crashed into Ash Murder’s protective astral essence. They pierced through his wings and smashed into his body.

Ash Murder’s muscles tore and his blood vessels burst apart. However, Ash Murder was indeed worthy of being called a half-step Empyrean powerhouse. In addition to the powerful mortal body of a saint, he had abruptly withstood this barrage of black lights!

Of course, this was also because Bai Qi’s tomb had existed for far too long. Too much of the array formation’s energy had faded away, making it much weaker than it was at the start. Otherwise, if it were at full power, then even a true Empyrean might have perished if they entered here!

After being tricked by Lin Ming, Ash Murder’s entire body was wet with blood. His wings had nearly been torn in half and he looked wretched.

As for Lin Ming, he was calmly hiding in Primordius Heavenly Palace, watching all of this occur.

“Haha, Old Man Ash Murder, your defensive capabilities are quite good. You lived through such an attack but your wings are torn and you seem a bit pathetic. You continue fighting out there. I’m going to take some pills and restore my condition. After I’m better, I’ll come back out to play with you.”

Lin Ming’s words could be called angering someone to death. He purposefully said this to provoke Ash Murder and disrupt his rhythm!

He could see that this Ash Murder was extremely strong and also had a certain understanding of array formations. As for the great array formation of Bai Qi’s tomb, it had undergone far too long a time. In the case that it wasn’t able to kill Ash Murder, the consequences would be disastrous.

However, breaking through these dao patterns required a calm mindset. If Ash Murder wildly stumbled around and stepped onto several more killing zone dao patterns, the results could be imagined.

Disturbing Ash Murder’s mindset was the exact effect that Lin Ming wanted.

Hearing Lin Ming’s words, Ash Murder felt his eye sockets nearly split open. He took a deep breath, glaring at Primordius Heavenly Palace with utter hate. His burning gaze seemed as if it could pierce through the Heavenly Palace and kill Lin Ming. He was well aware that Lin Ming was deliberately angering him, but even though he knew this, it was hard for him to calm down his heart. After all, once he transformed his body, his personality became even more crazy, savage, and hard to control.

Ash Murder knew that the dwelling Lin Ming was hiding in was an Empyrean spirit treasure. As long as he continued to attack, he would slowly exhaust the energy of the palace. Then, he could seize Lin Ming and do whatever he wished with him.

However, he didn’t have this chance because at this time, those 108 iron-armored spectral soldiers had already rushed forwards. The moment that he attacked Lin Ming, the remaining other two people, Manyu and his own follower, had already been hacked to pieces by the spectral soldiers’ weapons!

Thus, except for Naqi who had been received into Ash Murder’s inner world, everyone else had died!

The iron-armored spectral soldiers roared out loud and hurled themselves towards Ash Murder. Ash Murder broke into the midst of the spectral soldiers, slamming his claws atop one of their heads!

Kacha!

That iron-armored spectral soldier was smashed away by Ash Murder’s claws like a flimsy chicken! It crashed into the space barrier, causing cracks to tear through its body.

Ash Murder’s strike had cracked the spectral soldier’s body. This was simply because far too much time had passed and its body had eroded over the years.

If Ash Murder only faced a single iron-armored spectral soldier then he could easily win. But unfortunately, he had to face 108 of them.

Pitch black ghostly sabers chopped down on Ash Murder’s body. All of these iron-armored spectral soldiers were covered in a thick aura of death, as if they were evil ghosts that rushed out from the depths of hell!

“Old Idiot Ash Murder, you’re quite fierce! But, I don’t think you’ll be able to last much longer. This place is quite peaceful; it would be perfect for your tomb. What do you think? Hahahaha!”

Lin Ming began making a ruckus from within Primordius Heavenly Palace once more.

Ash Murder’s eyes blazed red. He forcefully held back the cruel and savage personality he gained after transforming his body. If he could just grab ahold of Lin Ming right now, he would tear him to strips!

Whoosh!

A burning arrow shot towards Ash Murder. Ash Murder punched out, blowing up the arrow. Then, with a wave of his hand, seven or eight nearby spectral soldiers were sent flying back by him.

“Amazing!” Lin Ming clapped. “Splendid, you are truly splendid. This is extremely entertaining! How come it feels like I’m watching a monkey dance around?”

Lin Ming tried to anger Ash Murder some more. In front of Lin Ming, Xiao Moxian traced her chin as she sized up Lin Ming. “You’re too naughty Lin Ming. I think that old man Ash Murder, even if he isn’t killed by the army of those iron-armored spectral soldiers, would still be angered to death by you.”

Lin Ming shook his head, saying, “It would be great if I could anger him to death. This person is extremely fierce. Normally, it is very difficult to control your personality after undergoing body metamorphosis, but even after being mocked by me he is still managing to suppress the negative thoughts in his heart so that he doesn’t step into some danger zone.”

As Lin Ming spoke, he was continuously keeping track of Ash Murder’s steps. The dao patterns in Bai Qi’s tomb were in all directions and at all heights. Whether it was flying in the air or walking on the ground, one could touch them. As for Ash Murder, it was impossible for him to remain still while fighting these iron-armored spectral soldiers.

And if he were to be forced all over then he would inevitably fall into a danger zone. After all, he wasn’t like Lin Ming who had a true understanding of the Asura Heavenly Dao. Ash Murder only relied on his intuition and the experience he gained through numerous life or death dangers to feel his way between the life zones and death zones.

“These iron-armored spectral soldiers are being destroyed by him, but once he steps into another death zone, I want to see just how he’ll hide!”

As Lin Ming looked at Ash Murder, his eyes blazed with a brilliant light.

Chapter 1519 – Unimaginable

Kacha!

With a resounding crack, Lin Ming’s protective true essence exploded as Ash Murder’s fist smashed into him. In that moment, his ribs collapsed and he spat out a mouthful of blood as he was sent flying backwards!

However, Ash Murder was the one who was surprised by his fist’s damaging effects. He thought that his fist strike would tear Lin Ming apart, and yet it only caused him to vomit blood?

When his fist struck Lin Ming’s body, Ash Murder felt like he had struck an ancient bronze bell that had been refined for an extremely long period of time, making his fist shake to the point of pain!

Even he didn’t possess such a bodily intensity; this was simply incredible!

He was a half-step Empyrean who also specialized in body transformation and Lin Ming was only an early Divine Lord powerhouse who took the body transformation as his subclass of martial arts. When comparing the both of them, how could there be any comparison at all?

“What a durable mortal body, this boy must have had some strange fortuitous encounter!”

Ash Murder was inexplicably shocked as Lin Ming crashed into the black stone altar. Although Lin Ming was coughing up blood his life force remained as vibrant and blazing as before, without seeming as if it would die down the least bit. It could even be said that his wounds weren’t heavy at all.

“This is impossible!”

Ash Murder was completely dumbfounded. This fist strike had come after he burnt his blood essence and yet he hadn’t been able to kill Lin Ming with it. In fact, he hadn’t even been able to severely wound him!

Moreover, what shocked Ash Murder the most was that when Lin Ming was sent flying backwards, he didn’t touch any death zones at all. Instead, he safely landed on the black stone altar, without triggering any traps. Besides the shaking wounds he had received he was relatively fine.

How could this be such a coincidence!?

Just as Ash Murder thought of this ‘coincidence’, he felt his entire body go cold as if he were dropped into an icy lake.

Something was wrong!

This wasn’t a coincidence at all, but a path that Lin Ming had already calculated when he was sent flying backwards!

The speed Lin Ming rushed forwards with as well as the angle of collision was already calculated well in advance. Thus why he didn’t touch any death zone runes.

This also meant that Lin Ming had intentionally been struck by him. From the start, he had never imagined that his attack would work out, but was planning on being struck instead. Just why would he do such a thing!?

An intense feeling of unrest surged in Ash Murder’s heart. He turned around to look at his own Sacred Soul Primal Spirit!

But the moment Ash Murder turned around, seven or eight iron-armored spectral soldiers already rushed towards him from behind. They grasped their ghostly sabers and dark spears, striking at him!

However, from between the gaps of these iron-armored spectral soldiers, Ash Murder was clearly able to see another ‘Lin Ming’ flying towards his Sacred Soul Primal Spirit!

This Lin Ming was wrapped in thunder and flames, a deep red long spear in his hands. A terrifying vortex of energy swirled around the spear point, drawing in all the origin energy within Bai Qi’s tomb. This was the black hole seed!

At this moment, Lin Ming had used his strongest strike, gathering the power of essence, energy, and divine into one. He used the Gate of Life to burn his blood essence and fused the power of thunder and fire heavenly tribulation into a soul attack. The Eight Inner Hidden Gates and Heretical God Force were released to the limit. Underneath his strongest state, he struck out with the Divine Seal Art’s Eternal Darkness!

“No!”

As Ash Murder saw this happen, his eyes widened so much that blood flowed out!

However, with the iron-armored spectral soldiers blocking him, there was no way for Ash Murder to stop Lin Ming. He could only watch helplessly on as all of this occurred!

“How is this possible!?”

Ash Murder roared out in unwillingness. At this time, seven or eight spectral weapons slashed out towards him, not giving him any time to attend to other matters!

Time seemed to come to a standstill.

Whether it was the ghostly weapons that were swinging at him or Lin Ming who was attacking with his strongest strike, everything became extremely slow…

Ash Murder felt as if all the strength in his body was being sucked out. He grit his teeth and raised his claws that were dripping with blood, and then fired into the group of iron-armored spectral soldiers.

“Get out of my way!”

Two iron-armored spectral soldiers bore the brunt of Ash Murder’s attack and were swept away, their necks broken. But at this time, a ghostly spear and saber stabbed into his body.

Beneath the impact of this tremendous strength, Ash Murder’s organs were twisted to pieces. The pitch black ghostly spear forcefully punctured through Ash Murder’s body and came through the other side, carrying with it a rain of blood!

At the same time, the black hole seed atop Lin Ming’s spear point burst out with a black brilliance. In that moment, it was like a black sun had risen within this sealed off hall!

The Sacred Soul Primal Spirit wasn’t without intelligence. Even though it was severely wounded, it still counterattacked Lin Ming. Its human-faced beast body spread its tattered wings and plunged towards Lin Ming.

However, Lin Ming’s attack was too sudden and his methods too ruthless. At his first strike, he released the limit of his strength and had even burnt his blood essence. As he collided with the Sacred Soul Primal Spirit, a dreadful detonation erupted.

Energy brutally surged outwards. Shockwaves of energy spread out like countless sabers. The Sacred Soul Primal Spirit that was already completely spent of energy was instantly shattered by Lin Ming’s strike!

However, Lin Ming was caught up in this wild explosion. He was sent flying away like a ragdoll!

As Lin Ming flew backwards, he revolved the Space Laws to avoid the killing zone dao patterns.

“Ji Xian’er!”

Lin Ming shouted out. Xiao Moxian had already been waiting in advance. She revolved Primordius Heavenly Palace’s grand array formation according to Lin Ming’s direction, commanding it to receive him within it.

Bang!

Just as Lin Ming was about to crash into Primordius Heavenly Palace, a gray light shout out and wrapped around him. In the next moment, Lin Ming felt himself tumbling into a soft form as an enchanting scent filled his senses.

In the final moment, Xiao Moxian had caught Lin Ming. After being struck by those energy shockwaves and now being caught in the embrace of a beautiful young woman, Lin Ming felt much better than before and his nerves even relaxed a bit.

He had succeeded!

Underneath the gaze of a half-step Empyrean powerhouse, had had sneak attacked the Sacred Soul Primal Spirit and had succeeded in doing so!

This had been an extremely risky plan. Lin Ming was far from being Ash Murder’s match. If Ash Murder grabbed onto him, he would have suffered the fate of instant and immediate death.

Bang!

Ash Murder’s bloodied body fell onto the ground. Two cruel weapons were thrust into his chest and stomach. Not too far away, the Sacred Soul Primal Spirit had already been exploded into pieces by Lin Ming!

In such a condition, the Sacred Soul Primal Spirit had fallen into an everlasting sleep. Without a transcendent divine miracle pill it would be impossible to awaken it. And at this time, Ash Murder himself was a lamp without oil; his hopes of leaving this hellish place had now become extremely slim!

Without the Sacred Soul Primal Spirit it was impossible for him to have any free time to attack the space barrier. Moreover, Ash Murder was no longer able to resist the attacks of the remaining spectral soldiers.

He looked towards the direction of Primordius Heavenly Palace, his eyes blazing with hatred and despair.

In this battle, every choice Lin Ming made had been upon the precipice of life or death! In this battle, he had faced an enemy over ten times stronger than he was but had used the array formation here as well as all sorts of guerilla tactics to instead kill those who had come here to kill him!

Especially in this final strike, he had calculated his escape route ahead of time, had lured the tiger out of the cave, and had then used diversionary tactics to strike down Ash Murder’s last hope!

To lose to such an opponent, to lose to a mere junior that was only several dozen years old with a Divine Lord cultivation, Ash Murder felt frustration and depression fill his heart.

At the start he had indeed underestimated his enemy, but later, he had lost even after he dropped any contempt he had.

Ash Murder looked towards the black stone altar. The ‘Lin Ming’ that was struck by him had already shakily stood up. This Lin Ming looked at him, a hint of pity in his eyes. Then, this Lin Ming flew towards Primordius Heavenly Palace.

At this time, Ash Murder was no longer capable of stopping him.

Up until now he still couldn’t understand why there were two Lin Mings. Based upon the manners and movements of these two Lin Mings, it was impossible for one to be a puppet. If so, it could only be an avatar!

How could Lin Ming have such a powerful avatar?

“Hah - !”

The array formation of Primordius Heavenly Palace revolved once more. Then, another Lin Ming rushed in!

This Lin Ming was not the Lin Ming that was being held by Xiao Moxian. But, there wasn’t any difference in their auras. It was only that this new Lin Ming was holding not the Phoenix Blood Spear, but a red spirit artifact that appeared similar.

Just then, this Lin Ming had been the one to withstand the frontal attack of Ash Murder’s fist. This Lin Ming’s chest had been pounded in by Ash Murder’s strike, and he had even spat out blood and had his organs break apart.

Even so, his life force remained as vibrant as before despite his combat strength having dropped by a great deal.

As Xiao Moxian saw this new Lin Ming appear, she shouted out in praise. “Fierce! Too fierce! A mortal body equal to the Saint Lord realm was able to receive the frontal strike of a half-step Empyrean and only be severely wounded! Moreover, this wound is…”

Xiao Moxian looked towards the chest of the new Lin Ming. The muscles of his chest were slowly creeping together, visibly regenerating!

Such a terrifying defensive ability and such a terrifying resiliency, this was something that not even Xiao Moxian with her half God Beast body could hold a candle to!

“This is indeed worthy of being the Essence Spirit Embryo Stone. I must say Lin Ming, your true self is too pitiful, you’re so much worse than your avatar!”

Lin Ming ruefully smiled, “How can I possibly compare with him? The life that is bred from an Essence Spirit Embryo Stone is no worse than a God Beast’s body to begin with. And not just that, but even if you ignore perception, his mortal body was similar to yours from the start, and in addition, he has been nourished by the Asura Road Master’s God Beast Tomb array formation for billions of years! In terms of the intensity of his mortal body, he is far superior to you and me!”

In the bronze temple, after Lin Ming had divided a portion of his soul to occupy the Essence Spirit Embryo Stone, this Essence Spirit Embryo Stone had become eternally marked by Lin Ming’s soul. Like this, his facial appearance, his limbs, his hair, his bloodline, everything was completely similar to Lin Ming.

His energy was inherited from Lin Ming and his cultivation realm was also similar to Lin Ming’s. It could only be said that this Essence Spirit Embryo Stone was a perfect clone of Lin Ming.

The only difference was that this Essence Spirit Embryo Stone was focused in mortal body intensity and the body transformation system; it had no combat strength in the essence gathering system.

With this sort of essence spirit avatar, Lin Ming’s combat capabilities had more than doubled. It was only because of this avatar’s formidable defensive abilities that Lin Ming dared distract Ash Murder to launch a sneak attack.

“Awesome! Doesn’t this avatar have two more seals that aren’t undone yet? If you undo those seals, just how strong will it become? It’s truly worthy of being called the Asura Road Master’s masterpiece. How could any inheritance that he left behind be bad? Otherwise, he’d probably be too ashamed to put it out.”

Xiao Moxian patted the strong mortal body of Lin Ming’s avatar, grinning as she spoke.

Lin Ming’s avatar had an intelligence of his own. But, because the avatar’s soul was a part of Lin Ming’s soul, this avatar’s intelligence was the same as Lin Ming’s. With Lin Ming in front of his avatar, he naturally didn’t control it.

Chapter 1521 – Crisis

“Lin Ming, let’s die together!”

Naqi crazily shouted. He was also a ruthless and decisive individual. He clearly knew he wasn’t Lin Ming’s match and chose a suicidal attack. In that moment, all of the energy within his body erupted as he rushed towards Lin Ming; he wanted to blow up all of his astral essence!

Naqi was also well aware that even if he exploded his body, it still wouldn’t be possible to kill Lin Ming. But, as long as he caused severe wounds to Lin Ming that was more than enough, because in this absolute killing zone, there was a chance Lin Ming could die if he was injured so deeply!

To cause heavy wounds to Lin Ming with his own death, this was 10,000 times better than having his soul sealed in the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel.

Lin Ming wasn’t surprised to see this at all. He sneered, withdrawing at the same time. His fingers flashed as he formed tens of thousands of gray seals.

As these seals appeared, the surrounding space and time began to distort. Even light was swallowed into these seals. Each of these seals that Lin Ming formed was a miniature black hole.

“Divine Seal Art – God Forbidding Seal!”

The Divine Seal Art was said to possess the ability to seal away all of existence; naturally, sealing away astral essence was nothing at all. In the Divine Realm First Martial Meeting, the Divine Sea realm Lin Ming had been able to break through Frost Dream’s Dreamsoul Immortal Melody by using the God Forbidding Seals.

Woosh! Woosh! Woosh!

These seals flew towards the wounded Naqi like a hail of arrows, sinking into his body. At that moment, Naqi felt as if demonic leeches crawled within his body. These leeches sucked his blood, absorbing his astral essence and flesh and blood essence.

“Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel!”

Lin Ming thrust his right palm forwards and the gray demon wheel was pushed forwards by him. It covered Naqi like a cruel and hungry maw.

“No!”

Naqi miserably cried out, struggling with all his strength. However, with his entire body sealed by the God Forbidding Seals, no matter what he tried, he still couldn’t revolve his astral essence or bodily strength.

Suicide was not possible and neither was escape. At this time, Naqi finally deeply understood what it meant to feel fear and powerlessness.

At this time, Naqi felt a terrifying demonic power cover his body, wanting to forcefully pull out his soul.

The agonizing pain of having his body and soul split apart struck him like a tide. This horrifying feeling was like being slowly skinned alive! The pain was indescribable!

Naqi cried out, his screams so loud they split his throat and lungs. With a light cracking sound, his soul was torn away from his body, turning into a wisp of gray light that submerged into the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel. Thus, the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel gained its first demon soul.

Lin Ming waved his hand and took away the God Forbidding Seals from Naqi’s body. Then, all of Naqi’s origin energy and blood energy was sucked out by the Essence Spirit Embryo Stone.

In just a moment, Naqi’s originally perfectly tempered body lost all of its blood vitality, nearly turning into a mortal body.

Like this, an Imperial Prince, a proud genius of his generation, had died a tragic death in God Burying Ridge. He had been struck down by Lin Ming and even his soul had devolved into a ghost slave!

After the Essence Spirit Embryo Stone sucked Naqi’s bodily strength, its blood energy became increasingly vibrant. The collapsed chest of that avatar began to wriggle around, clearly regenerating at an increased speed.

Lin Ming looked at the wounds of the Essence Spirit Embryo Stone and estimated that it would fully recover in an incense stick of time. This sort of regenerative ability was really far too abnormal.

Unfortunately, the Essence Spirit Embryo Stone wasn’t able to grow quickly. Even though it had swallowed the massive amount of blood energy within Naqi, the energy it contained still didn’t grow by much.

After swallowing up Naqi’s origin energy, Lin Ming repeated this process and had the Essence Spirit Embryo Stone swallow Ash Murder’s origin energy.

Ash Murder’s essence energy was dozens of times more formidable than Naqi’s. After the Essence Spirit Embryo Stone swallowed up this essence energy, the wounds on his body continued to squirm around before fully recovering in several breaths of time.

“It’s over!”

Lin Ming let out a long sigh of relief. Just as he was about to return to Primordius Heavenly Palace, a strange premonition emerged in his heart. This dangerous premonition came from the Essence Spirit Embryo Stone!

“What!?”

Lin Ming’s entire body went cold. At this time, where could this danger have come from?

Lin Ming didn’t know what this danger was. Without thinking further, he flew straight towards Primordius Heavenly Palace at max speed. As long as he entered Primordius Heavenly Palace then he would be temporarily safe. This was the best strategy to deal with the current situation.

But at this moment, a corpse that was lying on the ground suddenly leapt upwards!

This corpse had been that of Ash Murder’s follower!

There had been a total of four people in Ash Murder’s group. They were Ash Murder, Naqi, Manyu, as well as some common-seeming follower who only had a mere Saint Lord realm cultivation. When Lin Ming first ambushed them, this follower had been sucked into the storm and died afterwards. Not even Lin Ming had kept track of him afterwards!

Even the two puppets that Ash Murder put forth as well as his silver blue wolf contract beast seemed far more important than this follower!

But now, this follower leapt up, plunging towards Lin Ming like a demonic fiend!

“How is this possible!?”

Lin Ming was bewildered. This torn corpse, could Ash Murder have seized its body?

This was Lin Ming’s first thought, however, he had no time to continue thinking of what was happening. He had to immediately respond!

This corpse that rushed towards him seemed as if it only had a Saint Lord realm cultivation, but Lin Ming absolutely would not believe this. If this corpse had been able to hide from his sense and hide from the killing array in Bai Qi’s tomb, then it was absolutely a terrifying character!

Without thinking, the Essence Spirit Embryo Stone rushed towards this corpse like a cheetah. At the same time, Lin Ming himself hurtled towards Primordius Heavenly Palace!

Primordius Heavenly Palace was only 100 feet away. With Lin Ming’s speed, this was less than the blink of an eye!

However, at this time, a voice echoed in his mind.

“It’s too late! Today is the day you die!”

This voice was somewhat familiar. Lin Ming’s hands and feet immediately turned cold, his entire body drenched in sweat.

Tian Mingzi!?

Bang!

With a loud explosion, Lin Ming solidly crashed into an enchantment, feeling as if his skeleton would come apart. In that brief moment just now, Tian Mingzi had laid down an enchantment, isolating Lin Ming from Primordius Heavenly Palace!

Tian Mingzi knew how to hit Lin Ming where it hurt. He had already calculated Lin Ming’s weakness. As long as Lin Ming couldn’t return to Primordius Heavenly Palace then he could pinch him however he wished!

Peng!

With a loud ring, Tian Mingzi punched out, solidly striking the Essence Spirit Embryo Stone!

Lin Ming’s avatar spat out a mouthful of blood and was sent flying backwards! Even though the Essence Spirit Embryo Stone was powerful, it still couldn’t withstand a frontal collision with Tian Mingzi!

This was the strength of a Great World King!

In a sense, the extreme talent Tian Mingzi was not necessarily any weaker than the half-step Empyrean Ash Murder!

Lin Ming felt a cold chill creep into his chest. He was completely dumbfounded by Tian Mingzi’s sudden appearance!

“This person… has been waiting here for a long time already, waiting for his opportunity. This is really what they mean by the praying mantis stalking the cicada, while ignoring the sparrow from behind!”

Lin Ming immediately understood what was happening. Tian Mingzi used some skillful arcane technique to change his appearance into that of the follower to mix in with Imperial Prince Naqi’s group. This was something that neither Naqi nor Ash Murder was aware of. It was likely that the true follower had long since been killed off by him!

“The one who can change their appearance isn’t just you!” Tian Mingzi coldly sneered.

When Lin Ming was at the Divine Transformation realm, he had used the Bodily Rebirth Technique to change his appearance and was even able to conceal his identity from the World King realm Mister Zhou. Then, it wasn’t strange for Tian Mingzi with his Great World King strength to conceal the truth from the half-step Empyrean Ash Murder.

Tian Mingzi had used this appearance changing technique to wait for a chance to launch a sneak attack. When Lin Ming and Ash Murder critically wounded each other, he would launch his fatal life reaping strike!

He chose to do this because he really feared Lin Ming’s methods too much. And in fact, what happened had proved that his choice had been correct. Otherwise, the first to die would have been Tian Mingzi and not Ash Murder.

“Your avatar is quite good; did you obtain it in Tragic Death Valley? Moreover, there is that dwelling you hide in, that is also a top grade Empyrean spirit treasure. What a pity, what a pity. You have nowhere else to go now. Without your dwelling you are like a mouse without a hiding place. I can mess with you as I please!”

Tian Mingzi moved towards Lin Ming, one step at a time. After he removed his camouflage, he didn’t launch an attack first. Rather, he set up an enchantment to separate Lin Ming from Primordius Heavenly Palace. As long as Lin Ming wasn’t able to return to Primordius Heavenly Palace then Lin Ming would lose any shelter he had and have no strength to resist him!

“Your methods… are praiseworthy!”

Lin Ming’s breath slowed down and his complexion turned dark and grim. He already knew that Tian Mingzi was a sinister and cunning individual. With his mortal commoner background, he began as an outer court disciple of the Verdant Feather Holy Lands, and slowly crawled his way upwards to become an inner court disciple, core disciple, and finally became the one who overthrew the Verdant Feather Holy Lands, even killing the Verdant Feather Holy Lands’ old Great World King. For him to arrive at this step by himself, besides having his own destiny and lucky chances, he also had to have spectacular methods of his own!

Today, Lin Ming had finally experienced them.

Lin Ming had thought it was strange from the start. Out of all the people who had hunted him down to this place, only Tian Mingzi had placed a tracking mark on him. Yet, he was also the only one who hadn’t arrived. For Tian Mingzi, this didn’t seem to make sense at all.

So, it seemed as if he had already arrived but he had simply been waiting for his chance all along! Lin Ming thought that he was the winner, but he was made into a fool by Tian Mingzi!

Chapter 1522 – To Seek Survival In The Face Of Death

Tian Mingzi slowly extracted a long sword from his spatial ring. This sword was black with a narrow blade. It was eight feet long and engraved with images of cruel and savage demons.

This was not the first time that Lin Ming had seen this sword. Tian Mingzi’s weapon was a strange sword variation, not much shorter than his Phoenix Blood Spear.

With Tian Mingzi’s strength in combination with this strange sword, the strength he could display in battle was hard to imagine.

“Although your strength is nothing compared to mine, I will do everything in my power to kill you and not give you the tiniest chance to resist!” Tian Mingzi said, his killing intent completely locked onto Lin Ming. He slowly advanced; each step he took was on a life zone dao pattern.

While pretending to be dead in Bai Qi’s tomb, Tian Mingzi carefully memorized where Lin Ming stepped. He knew where safety was and where danger was.

As long as he didn’t step on a death zone dao pattern then the grand array formation in Bai Qi’s tomb would not activate.

Seeing Tian Mingzi perfectly avoid the death zone dao patterns, Lin Ming’s complexion was solemn. His complete divine sense radiated outward as numerous possibilities were calculated in his mind.

Today, he would face a second life or death crisis!

Growing to this point, Lin Ming had faced countless life or death crises! Forgetting the past, just after entering God Burying Ridge, Lin Ming had faced numerous dangers on the edge of death. Just a single step and he would have tumbled down beyond redemption!

After experiencing all these dangers, this caused Lin Ming to be even calmer the more dangerously critical a situation was!

Facing Tian Mingzi head on, Lin Ming could come up with no strategy that allowed him to live. This was an enemy that was two and a half large boundaries higher than him. At most, Lin Ming could jump two large boundaries to barely contend with someone.

The further a martial artist went in their cultivation, the greater the disparity was. This was why early on Lin Ming was able to jump two and a half large boundaries to fight, but now, even after experiencing innumerable lucky chances and repeated fortuitous encounters, he could only jump two boundaries to fight.

“Tell me your secrets. I know that you have some heaven-shaking secret on your body. If you tell me then I will let you die in peace. If you don’t tell me, then I will break your hands and feet, waste away your meridians, suck out your blood energy, crack open your bones, and turn you into a pile of rotten meat. I will make it so that you won’t even have the strength to resist mortals. Then, I will tear out your soul and obtain your secrets all the same, the only difference being that it is a little bit more troublesome for me. But for you, the pain you will experience will be indescribable.”

As Tian Mingzi spoke, his aura reached the limit!

As for Lin Ming, at this time he was still calculating the only possibility to escape from this disaster!

Tian Mingzi frowned. “You really are courting death. Although there is no hope for you to escape, I won’t give you any time to think about it!”

As Tian Mingzi spoke, he rushed forwards like an ancient vicious beast, directly impacting towards Lin Ming!

In these years, Tian Mingzi and Lin Ming hadn’t fought many times. But each time Tian Mingzi thought Lin Ming had no path to escape, Lin Ming was always able to flee to the heavens. This was the case at the Sky Spill Continent and also the case at Tragic Death Valley.

Now, in Bai Qi’s tomb, no matter how much Tian Mingzi was assured in his plan, he wouldn’t give Lin Ming any chance to think about escaping!

As Tian Mingzi attacked, Lin Ming also moved. Lin Ming revolved his true essence, pouring all of it into the Phoenix Blood Spear. Then, Lin Ming reversed his body, releasing the Eight Inner Hidden Gates to the extreme. A billion jins of strength erupted and Lin Ming threw the Phoenix Blood Spear straight out!

Woosh!

The Phoenix Blood Spear shot forwards like a meteor as it tore through the void. However, the direction of the attack was not towards Tian Mingzi, but towards an absolute death zone rune atop Bai Qi’s grave!

At this moment, Lin Ming used the Phoenix Blood Spear as the weapon to attack an absolute death zone rune.

Once this absolute death zone rune was activated, terrifying black light would rain down from the heavens, directly attacking the person who touched it. Even if Lin Ming had thrown the Phoenix Blood Spear and hadn’t even touched this death zone rune, he still wouldn’t be an exception!

Woosh! Woosh! Woosh!

At that moment, several hundred beams of black divine light shot towards Lin Ming like hundreds of divine swords!

And at this time, Tian Mingzi had arrived just in front of Lin Ming; he too had to face the attack of the black divine lights!

For a time, Tian Mingzi’s complexion changed. He never imagined that Lin Ming would be so ruthless. The moment that Tian Mingzi attacked, Lin Ming had also moved against the death zone runes, making it so that both of them fell into danger! However, if Lin Ming wanted to use this method to kill Tian Mingzi then he was far too naïve. Lin Ming was the focus of this attack and Tian Mingzi was only collateral damage.

This attack of divine light was far too fierce and brutal without any angle to dodge. Even for Mister Zhou and Ash Murder, when they touched these absolute killing zone runes, they still couldn’t dodge and had to face these black lights head on!

“This brat, is he thinking of committing suicide!”

Tian Mingzi’s pupils shrank. In that instant he could only forcefully withdraw his attack and retreat, stimulating all the true essence within his body to resist that black divine light!

With Tian Mingzi’s strength, it was impossible for this black divine light that had been weakened over billions of years to easily kill him. Even so, he had to resist this black divine light with all his strength. If he tried to exterminate Lin Ming underneath the deluge of this black divine light then he too would die without a grave here.

Tian Mingzi could resist the attack of divine light several times, but Lin Ming was in a far worse position. Once he was struck by this black divine light, then whether it was his protective true essence or his mortal body defensive capabilities that far surpassed other martial artists of the same step, they would all be torn apart like the thinnest pieces of paper!

In that moment, Lin Ming’s complexion was as calm and cold as a glacier. Seeing these hundreds of black divine lights shoot at him, their trajectories all reflected within his eyes.

“Asura Heavenly Dao!”

Lin Ming cried out, his body erupting with energy once more. In front of him, the phantom of the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel appeared again. He wasn’t thinking to use this to block the black divine light, but the black divine light still came from the same origin: the Asura Heavenly Dao. Because of this, the black light was also similarly restrained by the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws. This was a point that Lin Ming clearly understood after training in the first volume of the Asura Sutra.

In this hopeless situation, Lin Ming had to bet his life on a single move. With the Asura Heavenly Dao, he had to restrain the black divine light, forcefully opening up a slim chance of survival in the barrage of light that had no dead angles.

Even though Lin Ming had had already cultivated the Asura Sutra to the degree that it would give him this chance, he still didn’t fully grasp whether or not he could truly accomplish this.

“Open!”

Lin Ming roared. The Heretical God Force erupted to its limits, and the Gate of Life burned with blood essence. The Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel was shot forth with all his strength!

In that moment, the attack trajectory of the black divine lights slightly shifted. Although this shift didn’t seem worthy of mention at all, it was the difference between life and death for Lin Ming!

Lin Ming’s pupils contracted. His body twisted at an unbelievable angle. At this moment he was like a slippery fish, shuttling back and forth through the beams of black divine light!

“What!?”

Not too far away, Tian Mingzi felt his mind shake as he saw all of this happen. This was because as the one who had stirred up the absolute death zone dao pattern, Lin Ming had to withstand an onslaught of black divine light that was ten times worse than what he had experienced. Moreover, these black lights left no paths open for dodging. If Tian Mingzi were the one placed in this hopeless situation, even he wouldn’t be able to avoid the black divine lights. He would have to forcefully withstand three or four black divine lights, and although he wouldn’t die, he would still be injured.

Tian Mingzi originally thought that Lin Ming would undoubtedly die in this situation. However, he never imagined that Lin Ming would be able to dodge these black divine lights!

How was this possible!?

“Break again!”

Just as Lin Ming was about to run through the net of black divine lights, he punched out his fists, sending a current of true essence smashing into a second death zone rune. This action caused Tian Mingzi to be thoroughly shocked.

Lin Ming hadn’t even yet fully dodged the divine lights from the first absolute death zone rune, but he had now attacked a second one! He was insane!

Two nets of divine light gathered together. This terrifying attack was life-threatening even to someone like Tian Mingzi. Even so, Lin Ming placed himself in the midst of this danger!

From the inconceivable way Lin Ming had dodged just now, Tian Mingzi could confirm that Lin Ming struck the death zone dao patterns not to kill himself but to seek a road to survival in the face of death!

But, Tian Mingzi didn’t have time to think just what road to survival Lin Ming had found. With the net of black divine lights gathered around Lin Ming, Tian Mingzi couldn’t approach him right now. But, as soon as those black divine lights ended, Lin Ming would die.

Hu - ! Hu - ! Hu - !

The hundreds of black divine lights from the second absolute death zone rune fell down on Lin Ming in a horrifying deluge.

These black divine lights superimposed on those from the first wave, becoming even more dense and dangerous!

At this time, Lin Ming’s heart was calm and still to the extreme. The paths of the divine lights were all reflected in his eyes as he revolved his divine sense to its utter limit. He flushed right and left, finally closing in on Tian Mingzi’s enchantment.

As Tian Mingzi saw this, his entire body shook. He finally understood just what Lin Ming was planning. Lin Ming was planning to use himself as the lure to guide those black divine lights into attacking his enchantment. As long as the enchantment was broken, Lin Ming would be able to return to Primordius Heavenly Palace!

And now, Tian Mingzi had to face the absolute killing array in Bai Qi’s tomb that had been activated by Lin Ming!

Even so, a good half of this array formation had been broken by Ash Murder. Of the original 108 iron-armored spectral soldiers, around half of them had been destroyed and the remaining half wasn’t too great a threat to Tian Mingzi. But, Tian Mingzi wasn’t willing to let Lin Ming’s plan succeed because he had a premonition that once Lin Ming returned to Primordius Heavenly Palace and was given a chance to catch his breath, he would inevitably produce some unbelievable method again and again to deal with him. In the end, Tian Mingzi might even be the one played to death!

“Lin Ming, I won’t let you!”

Finally, Tian Mingzi moved. Disregarding the threat of the black divine lights, he fired right into Lin Ming!

The enchantment that Tian Mingzi laid down blocked Lin Ming from returning to Primordius Heavenly Palace. With Lin Ming’s strength, it was impossible for him to break past this barrier and Tian Mingzi wouldn’t give him the chance to do so.

But now, Lin Ming was guiding these terrifying black divine lights, a force that could even kill World Kings. With a barrage of hundreds of black divine lights striking Tian Mingzi’s enchantment, it would be pierced through like paper!

“Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel!”

Lin Ming shouted out as he used the Asura Heavenly Dao a second time!

The first barrage of divine lights had yet to pass, and now with a second wave added on, Lin Ming had to use the Asura Heavenly Dao yet again. This placed a tremendous burden on his body!

“Open again!”

Lin Ming roared. All the blood vessels under his skin bulged out. With the Gate of Life, he burnt 10% of his blood essence!

Chapter 1523 – Lin Ming’s Counterattack

Black light shot out and energy wildly raged about in the air. Beneath the cover of countless killing intents, Lin Ming tightened his protective true essence to the limit, rushing left and right without any defensive protections.

This was because Lin Ming was well aware that even if he stimulated his protective true essence to the limit, against this black light, any defense he summoned was no different from paper! If this was the case, then he might as well focus all of his concentration and true essence on the Asura Heavenly Dao!

Three beams of divine light that couldn’t be avoided had their trajectory forcefully changed by Lin Ming. In that instant, Lin Ming became flexible as if he had no joints at all and passed through a narrow slit between those black lights at an inconceivable degree. But at this time, the fourth unavoidable beam of black light came shooting at him. Because Lin Ming had consumed too much strength too quickly, he simply wasn’t able to deal with it. There was no way for him to avoid this!

Lin Ming’s pupils shrank. He chose not to use his true essence to protect himself when withstanding this divine light because he knew that doing so was useless.

He twisted his body once more, allowing this black beam of light to pierce through his lower left abdomen.

This part of his body didn’t have any vital zones. If his body had to be pierced somewhere, then having it pierced here was much better than his chest or head.

Puff!

In that moment, the black light easily punctured through Lin Ming’s body. Lin Ming spat out a mouthful of blood, biting down on the tip of his tongue as he stimulated the Divine Mist Heart Mantra. With this, his consciousness didn’t flicker in the slightest, even with the severe pain that wracked his body.

Rumble rumble rumble!

The black divine lights that Lin Ming avoided fell down on Tian Mingzi’s enchantment in waves. With the sound of a rolling thunderstorm, this barrier exploded like glass!

In that moment, Lin Ming didn’t reveal any happiness at all. With his emotionless face, he calmly continued hurtling towards Primordius Heavenly Palace!

“Dream on!”

A voice struck Lin Ming’s ear like a peal of thunder. Tian Mingzi had finally attacked!

Tian Mingzi shot into a place where the divine light was the sparsest. By revolving all the strength in his body, he forcefully withstood a beam of black light. Although this black divine light wasn’t able to pierce his body, it still ravaged his back muscles, tearing them apart.

Tian Mingzi simply wasn’t able to care about the wounds on his back. His sword cut forth and a black vortex appeared from thin air, “Heaven Absorbing Demon Art!”

In that moment, a dreadful suction force erupted like a tide, directly locking onto Lin Ming!

Because it was weakened by the black divine light and also because of the haste in which it was used, this Heaven Absorbing Demon Art wasn’t even a tenth of Tian Mingzi’s usual strength. However, when it locked onto the severely wounded Lin Ming, he still slowed down. Lin Ming was like a fly that fell into a giant spider web, his speed sharply plummeting!

The dragging force of the Heaven Absorbing Demon Art was simply far too strong. Lin Ming was unable to continue forwards.

“I’ll drain your blood dry!”

Tian Mingzi made a claw with his right hand and pulled it backwards. The terrifying suction force of the Heaven Absorbing Demon instantly shifted to Lin Ming’s lower abdomen where he had been pierced through. Tian Mingzi actually wanted to use his Heaven Absorbing Demon Art to suck out all of Lin Ming’s blood from his wound. From this move, one could see just how cruel and insidious Tian Mingzi’s methods were!

In that moment, Lin Ming’s body shook. He felt all of his blood vitality being gathered into his lower abdomen by that suction force, wanting to gush outwards. He grit his teeth, locking in his blood vitality with true essence.

Tian Mingzi’s eyes flashed with a grim light. His right hand tightened, as if he wanted to crumble something in his grasp.

Puff!

With a loud cracking sound, Lin Ming’s true essence lock was shattered by Tian Mingzi’s strength. A pillar of brilliant blood erupted from Lin Ming’s abdomen like a fountain!

Lin Ming’s lips trembled and his face began to whiten.

“Hahaha! Today is the day you die!” Tian Mingzi wildly laughed. He waved his hand and his black sword appeared in his grip. With the sound of howling wind, he hurtled towards Lin Ming!

With the strength of a Great World King and his true essence fused into his sword, this sword strike could even pierce through a celestial body. It was impossible for the wounded Lin Ming to resist it!

Moreover, Lin Ming’s movements were bound by the Heaven Absorbing Demon Art; it was impossible for him to defend!

The black sword came shooting towards Lin Ming’s heart. If it struck its target, Lin Ming would die here and now!

“You’re finished!”

Tian Mingzi maniacally grinned. It was like he could see the future where Lin Ming was slowly dismembered by his sword.

He had hunted Lin Ming down for a full ten years. This Lin Ming with his countless secrets had cost him a hand and also the foundation that he spent 50,000 years building. Now, Lin Ming would finally die at his hands today!

The keen sword whistled forwards. The distance of only several hundred feet passed by in a flash. Then, just as that sword was about to pierce through Lin Ming’s body, a shadow shot forwards like lightning, blocking Lin Ming from that black sword!

“Mm!?”

Tia Mingzi was startled, but his black sword had already struck that shadow!

With a loud ringing sound the black sword was deflected backwards. As for that shadow, it simply shook a little but didn’t receive any damage at all.

Tian Mingzi’s eyes focused. This shadow was only the size of a table; it was Lin Ming’s Primordius Heavenly Palace!

After the enchantment was shattered by the black divine lights, Lin Ming could fly to Primordius Heavenly Palace, and naturally, Primordius Heavenly Palace was able to fly towards him. But, the one temporarily controlling Primordius Heavenly Palace was not Lin Ming, but Xiao Moxian!

Xiao Moxian had already controlled Primordius Heavenly Palace once before, and now this was the second time. In a critical moment, she had used Primordius Heavenly Palace to block this fatal strike against Lin Ming!

“Damn it!”

Tian Mingzi wanted to attack once more, but at this moment, a brilliant rainbow-hued beam shot out from Primordius Heavenly Palace, wrapping around and dragging in the severely wounded Lin Ming.

Hoh - !

Xiao Moxian flew up to grab Lin Ming. As she grabbed him, her hands were shaking slightly.

“Lin Ming, are you okay?”

Xiao Moxian’s breath caught in her throat, her voice trembling. When Lin Ming had been pierced through the abdomen by the black divine light and then had a fountain of his blood come gushing out when Tian Mingzi used the Heaven Absorbing Demon Art, she had felt her heart shrink.

“I’m… fine…”

Lin Ming’s complexion was pale and his lips were dry. Just now, almost 80% of his blood had been sucked out! He had also lost a great deal of his blood vitality.

“The blood you drew out of me, I will make you pay back this debt.”

Lin Ming grit his teeth, a thick killing intent shining in his eyes.

……

“Just a little more, just a little more and I would have killed him, damn it all!”

Tian Mingzi was breathless with anger. He reached out his hand, wanting to call back his black sword. But at this time, he heard a rumbling behind him.

Tian Mingzi turned to see Lin Ming’s Essence Spirit Embryo Stone grab onto the Phoenix Blood Spear and come hurtling at him.

With the strength that Lin Ming’s avatar had, Tian Mingzi wasn’t scared of it at all. But, the crux was that behind Lin Ming’s avatar, there were hundreds of black divine lights chasing him.

That explosive rumble just now was the Essence Spirit Embryo Stone actively attacking the death zone rune. It was deliberately drawing in black divine lights to attack Tian Mingzi!

That death zone rune was far too close to Lin Ming. Moreover, with the angle that Lin Ming had chosen, it was impossible for Tian Mingzi to avoid it!

Lin Ming’s true self had already been severely wounded be Tian Mingzi and the black divine light. When his body was pierced through and a massive amount of his blood vitality was drawn out by the Heaven Absorbing Demon Art, Lin Ming’s fighting will hadn’t diminished in the least. Even though his true self had lost his combat strength, he still controlled his avatar to activate the black divine lights and calculate the best angle to attack Tian Mingzi.

His avatar would have to withstand the black divine light with Tian Mingzi. No one was going to emerge from this unscathed!

“What!?”

Tian Mingzi’s complexion changed. He never imagined Lin Ming would be so ruthless. When he was on the verge of death, he had actually used just several breaths of time to come up with this plan and turn the tide of battle!

The black lights were imminent and threatening; there was no way for Tian Mingzi to evade!

Tian Mingzi clenched his jaw. “Lin Ming, only one of us can live beneath the heavens!”

He roared out, erupting his true essence to the limit. Demonic energy surged around him, forming a black protective shield.

He was well aware that he had to resist this strike by paying the lowest price possible. If he suffered devastating wounds from these black lights then he would absolutely fall into tremendous danger!

Chapter 1524 – Tragic

“Counterforce – Heaven Absorbing Demon Art!”

Tian Mingzi recklessly released the energy absorbed by the Heaven Absorbing Demon Art to withstand this strike!

And at this time, Lin Ming’s avatar came shooting towards Tian Mingzi without fear. Without any consideration for the black lights all around it, it wanted to attack Tian Mingzi!

Tian Mingzi’s complexion instantly turned ugly. He had personally witnessed Lin Ming’s avatar being punched in an all-out strike by a half-step Empyrean powerhouse, and yet it had only received injuries.

The defensive capabilities of this avatar were simply like those of a farm animal!

Just from this alone, Tian Mingzi knew that in a competition of defense, he couldn’t compete with this vicious beast in human form. In a situation that he couldn’t defend, there was no way he could resist the all-out attack of a half-step Empyrean.

Those with bare feet did not fear shoes with holes. This was only Lin Ming’s avatar, but the one defending was Tian Mingzi’s true self. To go all-out with his true self against an avatar, only an idiot would do something so stupid!

“Who cares if you attack me, I will block all attacks together!” Tian Mingzi’s eyes flashed with a grim light. In this moment, he stimulated his strength to the extreme!

The main threat to him was from those black divine lights. As for the attack of Lin Ming’s avatar, he simply didn’t care about it.

Bang!

Lin Ming’s avatar smashed its spear into Tian Mingzi’s black barrier. The terrifying mortal bodily strength of that avatar erupted like a volcano!

Lin Ming’s avatar specialized in body transformation and its mortal body was far superior to that of Lin Ming’s true self. It was a God Beast Essence Spirit Embryo Stone. In the bronze temple, it had been refined over billions upon billions of years with the essence energy of 33 extreme God Beasts. In terms of how formidable its body was, this avatar far surpassed both Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian, and completely outclassed Imperial Prince Naqi. This was a grand masterpiece of the Asura Road Master; how could Naqi possibly compare with it?

Thus, this avatar’s physical strength was almost 10 times stronger than Lin Ming’s true self, reaching up to 10 billion jins!

Kacha!

The spear of Lin Ming’s avatar pierced into Tian Mingzi’s black barrier and actually caused a crack to appear in the surface!

Although only a tiny crack appeared, this meant that Tian Mingzi’s barrier had greatly weakened. If he were to meet another powerful attack then his barrier would completely collapse.

“What!?”

At this moment, Tian Mingzi was completely panic-stricken!

He knew that Lin Ming’s avatar was fierce, but he thought it was only its defensive capabilities. No matter what, he never imagined that its striking power would also be so terrifying. Disregarding the essence gathering system, disregarding the various Laws and martial skills, in terms of frontal impact ability alone, Lin Ming’s avatar far surpassed his true self! If Lin Ming’s true self was a mortal fighter then Lin Ming’s avatar was a wild tiger! When facing off head to head, how could a mortal fighter compare to a tiger?

Seeing the black divine lights come shooting down, Tian Mingzi’s eyes nearly popped out with rage. In that life or death moment he bit down on his tongue and burnt his blood essence!

For Tian Mingzi who dreamed of breaking into the Empyrean realm, there was no need to mention how precious his blood essence was. Ten years ago, he had lost a hand to Lin Ming and now he was forced by Lin Ming to burn his blood essence. This was decision he only made as a last resort!

However, even though he burned his blood essence, Tian Mingzi didn’t have enough time to use a defensive martial skill because the black divine lights had already arrived in front of him. Now, he could only use this black barrier that had a crack in it to withstand this attack!

Woosh!

Lin Ming’s avatar had ruined Tian Mingzi’s plans, forcing him to directly face the impact of these black divine lights.

Lin Ming definitely wouldn’t block these black divine lights for Tian Mingzi. If the avatar had to withstand the attack then both of them would do so together!

“Ahhhh!”

Tian Mingzi wildly roared out, the anger blazing in his heart hot beyond imagination. It was clear that he was far stronger than Lin Ming and he had done everything in his power to kill him. Whether it was disguising himself as Ash Murder’s follower, hiding away to sneak attack, isolating Lin Ming from Primordius Heavenly Palace with an enchantment, or drawing out Lin Ming’s blood through his wound with the Heaven Absorbing Demon Art, everything Tian Mingzi did could be called desperately trying to kill Lin Ming no matter the cost. All of this was so that Lin Ming wouldn’t have the tiniest sliver of hope to survive. But, the end result was that through all the twists and turns, he was forced once more by Lin Ming into a dangerous situation!

Bang!

Several hundred black lights solidly smashed into Tian Mingzi’s barrier. The barrier that had been struck once already suddenly produced a massive fissure that raced down it before it shattered into pieces. Tian Mingzi coughed, vomiting out a mouthful of blood as he was sent flying away!

Ca!

As he was sent flying backwards, a black light pierced through his right shoulder, mincing his shoulder blade to pieces!

Feeling this severe pain in his shoulder, Tian Mingzi’s complexion completely changed. To a Great World King, this sort of wound only needed a single day to regenerate. But in his current situation, this pierced shoulder would actually affect his combat strength, causing all sorts of serious consequences for him.

At this time, beside Tian Mingzi, Lin Ming’s avatar was also struck by the raging river of black divine lights. The avatar was flushed away, distressed and gushing blood all over.

However, this avatar was extremely formidable. Even with such heavy damage, although its bones and muscles had been torn apart and its organs had been scrambled up, its body hadn’t been pierced through. In terms of mortal bodily defense, Tian Mingzi was far from being able to compare with it.

Energy surged, wildly storming about. Tian Mingzi suppressed the harrowing pain in his shoulder to form a final shield of protective true essence to block the shockwaves of energy. Even so, a great deal of this energy broke into Tian Mingzi’s body where it wildly rushed through his meridians!

Pa pa pa!

Tian Mingzi’s blood vessels collapsed one after another, blood spraying from his body!

He crashed into the black stone altar. In the final moment, he barely managed to change his direction to avoid landing on another death zone dao pattern. Luckily, Tian Mingzi had remembered where the majority of the death zone dao patterns were, otherwise if he were to strike another one now then he might have simply died here.

Lin Ming’s avatar also crashed into the black stone altar, its entire body covered with blood.

Looking at the area where Tian Mingzi fell, Lin Ming’s avatar darkly sighed. According to the angle of the black divine lights, Tian Mingzi should have fallen into another death zone dao pattern. But, Lin Ming hadn’t placed much hope in this to begin with. He didn’t think that the prudent and cautious Tian Mingzi would make such a low-level mistake.

Gritting his teeth, Lin Ming’s avatar flashed away, flying straight towards Primordius Heavenly Palace!

Tian Mingzi saw Lin Ming’s avatar escape, but didn’t stop him at all.

His current condition was extremely bad so it would be hard to instantly create another enchantment, and even if he did, he might not be able to block Lin Ming’s avatar.

Moreover, even if he blocked Lin Ming’s avatar, it would be hard for Tian Mingzi to do anything in a short period of time. This avatar’s defensive capabilities were far too dreadful. If they fought then this avatar might disregard all consequences to strike another death zone dao pattern, wanting them both to perish together. If that were to occur, Tian Mingzi found it hard to imagine what the consequences would be.

The moment that Lin Ming’s avatar entered into Primordius Heavenly Palace, Tian Mingzi felt a thick killing intent surge up from behind him.

He turned around to see the remaining 50 some-iron armored spectral soldiers come to life once more. The stone chips on their bodies had already fallen and a red flame lit up their eyes. They grasped their deadly weapons and began moving towards him!

Although Lin Ming and Tian Mingzi’s battle seemed as if it occurred over a long period of time, the truth was that everything had happened far too quickly. The battle could only be described as ever-changing. From the time when Tian Mingzi rushed towards Lin Ming’s true self, to the time at which Lin Ming activated the death zone dao pattern to draw the black divine lights into helping him enter Primordius Heavenly Palace, and even to the time that Lin Ming’s avatar had triggered another death zone dao pattern, causing tremendous losses to Tian Mingzi, all of this had occurred in just several breaths of time!

And, several breaths of time were all that were required for those iron-armored spectral soldiers to reawaken. Now, they had finally entered their combat state.

For a time, Tian Mingzi’s complexion became even uglier. This iron-armored spectral soldier array formation had only half of its spectral soldiers remaining and was far weaker than it was before. Perhaps it was only at 20-25% of the original array’s strength. But now, Tian Mingzi’s condition was also extremely poor. His shoulder was ruined and he had lost the ability to move one of his arms. His blood was chaotically moving within his body and many of his blood vessels had exploded. He had even been forced to burn some of his blood essence.

To fight against 50 iron-armored spectral soldiers in this situation, the difficulty of this could be imagined!

In terms of strength, Tian Mingzi was a peak Great World King, not much worse than the half-step Empyrean Ash Murder. But in terms of endurance and defensive capabilities, Tian Mingzi was far inferior to Ash Murder, who was from the saint race. Ash Murder cultivated body transformation and even in a situation where he was extremely wounded he was still able to maintain a considerable amount of his combat strength. This was not something that Tian Mingzi could copy.

Facing these iron-armored spectral soldiers, Tian Mingzi had fallen into a life or death struggle!

“Well done, Lin Ming!” Tian Mingzi gazed towards Primordius Heavenly Palace with hatred shining in his eyes. He could already foresee that in order to defeat these remaining iron-armored spectral soldiers, he would need to pay a heavy price!

However, Lin Ming wasn’t much better off. He had lost almost 80% of his blood and his blood vitality had been deeply diminished.

As for his avatar, it would be unable to fight again. After being struck by so many divine lights, it wouldn’t have any combat strength for some time.

Now, what mattered the most was whether or not Tian Mingzi would have to pay some sky-high price to destroy all these iron-armored spectral soldiers.

If Tian Mingzi had even just 20% of his combat strength left afterwards, Lin Ming still wouldn’t dare to leave Primordius Heavenly Palace. At that time, if Tian Mingzi were to simply sit down, meditate, and restore himself to his peak state then Lin Ming would die without a doubt.

“Lin Ming, for you to achieve what you have, I truly do admire you. But, you will die, no matter how deep the price I must pay. I will kill you and take all the secrets from your body!”

Tian Mingzi said with a true essence sound transmission towards Primordius Heavenly Palace. The palace array formation didn’t stop sounds without striking power, thus Lin Ming was able to hear all of this.

“And there is you too, Xiao Moxian! You also must have left Tragic Death Valley and have been secretly assisting Lin Ming from the shadows to oppose me! When I break into your dwelling’s grand array formation, I will toss you alive into a pill furnace and use your half-phoenix body and primordial yin for my alchemy to make up for the blood energy I have lost! You are nothing more than a turtle in a jar, there is no way for you to survive!”

Tian Mingzi threatened Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian with words, wanting to shake their wills. Although this was a simple tactic, in this desperate situation it had a great effect. This was because everything that Tian Mingzi said had a chance of becoming reality!

After Xiao Moxian heard this, she paled.

Growing up until now, there were many people who had threatened her. Some people wanted to capture her to dual cultivate with her, and some people even wanted to rape her and take her primordial yin.

But, she had never encountered someone like Tian Mingzi who wanted to toss her into a pill furnace alive to refine her into a pill.

Thinking about how it would feel to be slowly refined alive into a pill, Xiao Moxian was terrified. Tian Mingzi was a brutal and ambitious person. He had no sympathy for beauty or lingering sentiments. For him, his only ambition was to conquer the world and become a god; he felt no emotions like lust or love.

Chapter 1528 – Dao Diagram of the Heavenly Dao

To refine a star to enter his body was easier said than done. Lin Ming constantly swallowed starlight, gathering his strength. His mortal body continued to grow stronger and stronger. Although he didn’t break through to the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, his mortal bodily strength rose up from a billion jins, rapidly approaching 2 billion jins!

“My strength is still far too lacking!”

Lin Ming’s eyes were like bolts of lightning in the darkness. He formed more seals with his hands, drawing out another ancient python of blood vitality from the Grandmist Spirit Bead and having it rush into his body.

This python was another 20% of the Grandmist Spirit Bead essence. Lin Ming had now swallowed a full 40% of the Grandmist Spirit Bead essence in this attempt. When this was added onto the powerful blood vitality within the Nine Star Heaven Pill, Lin Ming’s mortal body rapidly inflated as if he would explode at any moment.

His veins bulged out like worms. Sweat dripped down from all over him. His body had reached the limit of strength that it could absorb and wanted to explode!

Lin Ming looked up, his brilliant eyes locking onto one of the nine stars floating in space. Then, he leapt upwards!

Nine stars. Of them, seven were incomparably bright and two were dim. The seven bright stars corresponded to the seven Bright Palaces within the human body, and the two dark stars corresponded to the two Hidden Palaces within the human body.

Now, the star that Lin Ming rushed towards was the closest bright star! This star’s name was Army Breaker!

The Army Breaker Star. The meaning of this was that it could freely wander the world, breaking through the lines of any army, unstoppable and irresistible!

Lin Ming’s bodily strength erupted to the limit. The Eight Inner Hidden Gates opened to the limit. He wanted to forcefully pluck this star down!

When martial arts were practiced to the highest level, one could pick down stars and shoot down moons. These were not empty fairytales, because Lin Ming was trying to do this right now!

In terms of foundation, if Lin Ming were compared to the body transformation martial artists from 3.6 billion years ago, he would be ten times or even a hundred times better! In the past, if Lin Ming wanted to break through the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace with his strength, it would have been as easy as eating a meal. But now, he had to break past the Heavenly Dao rules!

The Heavenly Dao rules did not abide the existence of the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace; this caused Lin Ming’s cultivation to be blocked. But looking at this from another viewpoint, this meant that the foundation of Lin Ming’s body transformation had been suppressed even as it accumulated to an unbelievable degree. Once it erupted then it would truly be like dragons and phoenixes soaring to the highest heavens, showing naught but disdain for the world!

The moment that Lin Ming rushed towards the Army Breaker Star, the void trembled around him. It was like all of the surrounding space-time was collapsing. A terrifying strength gathered, dreadful to the extreme!

Lin Ming maintained his vigilance. This dreadful power was truly fear-inspiring. It seemed as if it could tear apart everything and it was clearly aimed at him!

Opening the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace was something not allowed by the Heavenly Dao rules. Even if Lin Ming’s mortal body foundation had accumulated to an incredible degree, the moment that he tried to impact the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, he would inevitably be hindered by the Heavenly Dao!

In the empty void, lines of the Great Dao slowly appeared, weaving together into a dao diagram that locked down the nine stars in the sky.

“Are these the Heavenly Dao Laws that lock down the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace?”

Lin Ming looked towards the dao diagram in the sky. This dao diagram contained an incomparably horrifying strength. He didn’t doubt that as long as he rushed forwards, he would be ruthlessly and mercilessly suppressed by this dao diagram!

To transgress the Heavenly Dao was to withstand heavenly tribulation. Once heavenly tribulation came falling down, even extreme geniuses could perish in ashes, without even their bones remaining!

Lin Ming took a deep breath and decisively shot into the dao diagram. He had to gamble everything he had because there was no alternative for him!

Weng –

The lines of the Great Dao came pressing down upon Lin Ming, carrying with them a great aura that could not be defied, one that stood at the pinnacle of all existence.

Lin Ming roared out. He gathered all his strength and punched!

In the dark void, all strength besides that of the body transformation system was forbidden. Lin Ming could only revolve the strength within his mortal body, releasing his Eight Inner Hidden Gates to their limit as he smashed into the dao diagram!

Kacha!

With a thunderous peal, Lin Ming’s arm shook, the bones nearly cracking as his fists stained themselves red with blood.

As for the Great Dao lines in front of him, they only slightly trembled, without any hint that they would shatter.

The dao diagram slowly rotated, pressing Lin Ming in the center of countless dao patterns. These dao patterns were like a terrifying grinding pan, grinding down on Lin Ming’s bones and muscles!

The void was crushed to pieces. Under this horrifying pressure, even Lin Ming’s powerful mortal body seemed as if it would crack open. His blood vessels exploded and blood gushed out from him.

This was the strength of the Heavenly Dao, completely different from the nine by nine heavenly tribulation of metal, wood, water, fire, earth, wind, thunder, yin, and yang, that Lin Ming had previously experienced. Those were tangible disasters, but this time it was entirely suppression of the Laws.

These invisible Laws could be as heavy as stars, able to grind down everything.

Lin Ming’s body emitted loud crackling sounds. No matter how durable his mortal body was, under the suppression of these Laws he still couldn’t withstand it.

Lin Ming clenched his jaws, his eyes turning red with effort. The moment that he had decided to break through the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, he had expected that this experience would be difficult. But, he didn’t think it would be difficult to such a ridiculous degree.

“Did I overestimate my 10% chance of success?”

Lin Ming was unwilling. In the past, Empyrean Primordius had undergone a similar tribulation, but back then, Empyrean Primordius also possessed the Grandmist Spirit Bead, a divine object of the highest level when it came to body transformation Laws. By relying on the Grandmist Spirit Bead to protect his body, only then did he overcome that tribulation.

As for Lin Ming, he had to resist the Heavenly Dao Law unarmed!

The difficulty of this could be imagined!

Bang!

Lin Ming punched out his fists once more. Countless blood vessels exploded, leaving his clothes dripping red. His body was nearly crushed to pieces. And on the outside of this empty nothingness, Lin Ming’s true self was also in an extremely poor situation.

At this time, Lin Ming’s true body was pale white and shivering. He was bleeding from his nose, eyes, and ears!

Above Lin Ming’s head, the phantoms of nine stars were clearly visible. As the vast and endless starlight came sprinkling down, even Primordius Heavenly Palace vanished. Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian arrived in an endless cosmos. What they sat on was no longer the chaos stone bed, but the infinite galaxy.

“Lin Ming…”

Xiao Moxian’s heart tightened as she saw Lin Ming’s pained expression. She already knew that breaking into the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace would be extremely risky. Even an extreme character like Empyrean Primordius had relied upon a divine object in order to break through. Moreover, when Empyrean Primordius had broken through to the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, he had already been cultivating for tens of thousands of years.

As for Lin Ming, all he had to rely on was his heated blood and ardent will. With his less than 60 years of cultivation, he was attempting to break through the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace. The risks he faced could be imagined.

Xiao Moxian also paled. At this time, she didn’t know how she could help Lin Ming. Although a massive amount of energy entered her inner world, she still wasn’t able to make her breakthrough. There was just some kind of final catalyst that was missing.

Weng – Weng – !

The Heavenly Dao Laws revolved. Lin Ming shivered as he overdrew his strength. Right now, his strength was still far from enough for breaking past the barrier of the Heavenly Dao!

Lin Ming took a deep breath, resolving to wrestle against the odds with his life. Using the Grandmist Heavenly Dao, he forced a third python from the Grandmist Spirit Bead essence to enter his body!

This was also another 20% of the essence. Combined with the previous two times, Lin Ming had absorbed a total of 60% of the Grandmist Spirit Bead essence!

In front of Lin Ming, Xiao Moxian was panic-stricken.

Lin Ming was insane! His mortal body was already ruined to such a degree and yet he wanted to absorb another 20% of the Grandmist Spirit Bead essence. Just how could he possibly refine it?

Chapter 1529 – Extreme Yin Blood Essence

The Grandmist Spirit Bead essence was originally an extremely violent and tyrannical blood essence energy. If one’s cultivation was insufficient, then directing the Grandmist Spirit Essence into the body would cause their body to perish through exploding. This was like a mortal swallowing down a bar of gold; their body wouldn’t be able to digest it and their stomach would swell until they died.

Lin Ming’s situation was already extremely poor. In this state, he forcefully swallowed another 20% of the essence energy. The burden this placed on his body could be imagined.

In the endless empty universe, Lin Ming roared out loud. With the support of this wild and brutal Grandmist Spirit Bead essence, he punched out at the nine star dao diagram! After directing the last 20% of the Grandmist Spirit Bead essence into his body, Lin Ming had already cut off all avenues of retreat. He could only bet everything on this last desperate attempt!

With Lin Ming’s current strength and his ruined body, it was impossible for him to fully absorb this 20% of the Grandmist Spirit Bead essence. If he couldn’t break through the nine star dao diagram then he could only wait for his body to explode!

Kacha!

Lin Ming attacked with everything he had, even splitting apart his fingers. The nine star dao diagram wildly shook, but, it still didn’t break.

“It’s still not enough!”

A deep sense of unwillingness surged in Lin Ming’s mind. Even though he had ignored the ramifications of swallowing this latest 20% of the Grandmist Spirit Bead essence, the strength he needed was ultimately far too distant from being able to break through the nine star dao diagram.

If this continued then it wouldn’t be long before Lin Ming’s body ruptured and his inner world exploded into pieces!

“Essence energy avatar, second seal, release!”

Lin Ming shouted out. The Essence Spirit Embryo Stone avatar that he inherited from within the bronze temple had a total of three seals. These three seals were left behind by the Asura Road Master and each successive seal was bound more tightly than the last.

The final seal was the most formidable. With Lin Ming’s current cultivation he was unable to release it, but he was able to unbind the first two.

In the bronze temple, Lin Ming had undone the first seal. Using the strength that was released, he expanded his inner world and broke into the Divine Lord realm!

With Lin Ming’s understanding of the Asura Heavenly Dao, he still wasn’t able to fuse his true self with his avatar. He could only use the method of undoing this seal and obtaining energy from his avatar.

Bang!

When Lin Ming released the second seal there was a loud explosion like 10,000 bolts of thunder crashing down together, like endless God Beasts roaring out!

An indescribably dreadful strength erupted like a volcano, surging out like a tsunami. This strength flooded out from the Essence Spirit Embryo Stone avatar and all of that extra strength impacted straight towards Lin Ming!

Lin Ming’s Essence Spirit Embryo stone avatar had already reached an inconceivable boundary in the intensity of its mortal body. As this wild and brutal power erupted from within it, it was still able to withstand it. However, Lin Ming’s true self was different. As this incomparably fierce strength flooded his body, in addition to everything before it, his body began to crack apart.

The reason Lin Ming crazily summoned all the strength he could was in order to shatter past the nine star dao diagram. As long as he could break through it then there would be a point where his strength could be released. He would be able to break into the next boundary and allow his strength to rapidly rise.

However, if the nine star dao diagram didn’t break then everything would reverse. Lin Ming would die beneath the suppression of the nine star dao diagram and the havoc that was being wreaked upon him by it.

“Celestial Tyrant Manual – Hundred Layered Waves!”

In this black void, Lin Ming could only use the strength of body transformation. With his strength that reached 2 billion jins, he struck out with the Celestial Tyrant Manual’s Hundred Layered Waves. In that moment, Lin Ming’s bodily strength increased by several times, breaking straight past the critical point of 5 billion jins!

This horrifying strength crashed into the nine star dao diagram, causing it to violently shake!

Energy wildly raged outwards, causing the surrounding void to tear apart like scrap paper. A crack finally appeared in the nine star dao diagram!

Seeing this crack in the dao patterns, Lin Ming’s eyes brightened. He was like a parched traveler in the desert who finally saw an oasis!

This crack was his final ray of hope. Otherwise, if this were to continue then his mortal body might not be able to last for another incense stick of time!

Bang!

Lin Ming’s fist smashed out again and all the muscles of his right arm split apart. Ignoring his collapsing body, he revolved the Celestial Tyrant Manual to the limit. The crack in the nine star dao diagram was expanded once more by Lin Ming’s strike!

At this time, Lin Ming had already reached his limits. He bit down on his tongue, burning his blood essence through the Gate of Life. Then, he struck out with a third punch!

Kacha!

His bones released a deafening explosive sound as they shattered. Lin Ming’s face twisted in pain. The bones in his right arm had completely shattered and his hand was hanging down at a strange angle; he was unable to make a fist!

“Damn it!”

For a time, Lin Ming’s pupils shrank. As he stared at his ruined right arm his entire body shivered.

Without a continuous barrage, the crack in the nine star dao diagram began to slowly regenerate!

Even if one used absolute strength to tear down a dao diagram of the Heavenly Dao, it would still slowly recover.

Just a little bit more!

Lin Ming bit down with his teeth, a furious rage blazing within him. He still had his left arm but this left arm would at most be able to punch three more times. With these three punches it was impossible for him to break through the nine star dao diagram.

“Will the heavens kill me?”

Lin Ming was unwilling! He was less than 60 years old and had walked down the road of martial arts for just over 40 years. He had passed through many great storms, suffered many tribulations, defeated countless extraordinary individuals, and had passed through innumerable life or death dangers to arrive at this step. Through all that, he finally stood at the peak of all young human geniuses!

How could he be willing to perish like this?

Although he had weakened, at the same time a terrifying energy wildly raged through his body, attacking his meridians!

There was the Grandmist Spirit Bead essence as well as the unsealed strength from the Essence Spirit Embryo Stone. These two strengths were both at the extreme yang. As they collided within Lin Ming’s body, they were like two volcanoes erupting together!

These two extreme yang strengths weren’t willing to submit to anyone, and with Lin Ming’s ruined body it was impossible for him to subdue them. They continued to ravage through Lin Ming’s body, using his body as a battlefield. If he wasn’t able to suppress them then he could only wait for his body to explode into pieces!

“The Heavenly Dao does not abide me. In the end, am I unable to overcome the Heavenly Dao?”

Within Lin Ming’s body, the two yang energies became increasingly wild, smashing into each other more and more, completely unable to be subdued. Lin Ming grit his teeth, his fingernails digging deep into his palm. With his current state, wanting to evenly stabilize these two yang energies was completely impossible.

The condition of his body became increasingly worse. His eye sockets began to crack apart and his eyes bled.

In that moment, he could feel death floating close by. In his life, he had only encountered this feeling once, when he had broken into the ninth stage of Life Destruction and experienced a nine by nine heavenly tribulation.

As Lin Ming was about to collapse and have the two energies blow up his body, he felt a soft, feminine yin energy enter his body. This strength was like a stream of clear spring water, revitalizing his ruined body.

“This is…”

Lin Ming was startled. He could faintly feel this soft feminine strength slip in between the two fierce yang energies, causing those two violently clashing energies to calm down.

Although this strength was far from being as formidable as the two yang energies, it was pure to the extreme. The soft and soothing attributes of this energy was able to smoothly stabilize the two other energies, achieving a state of yin and yang balance.

“This is Xiao Moxian…”

Lin Ming immediately realized. At this time, the only one who could release such a pure and soft blood vitality was Xiao Moxian.

From this soft feminine strength, Lin Ming could sense the rich energies of phoenix blood. As it was light and clear as water, it also carried with it a faint aura of flames.

But what surprised Lin Ming was that this strength was completely different from the time when he and Xiao Moxian held hands. Not only was Xiao Moxian sending out her True Phoenix blood energy, but it carried the aura of life force, as if this energy came from her source of life.

“Phoenix blood essence!?”

Lin Ming’s mind shook. His consciousness forcefully withdrew from the black void where he was attempting to break through to the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace and his eyes shot open to see Xiao Moxian.

At this time, Primordius Heavenly Palace was completely wrapped up in the divine light of the nine stars. Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian were placed within this endless world of starlight. She held onto his hand, her bright red lips open as a stream of rich blood energy fluttered out from between then and towards Lin Ming.

This power of blood vitality transformed into the appearance of phoenixes in midair. They were beautiful and enchanting, releasing clear and pleasant cries.

This was Xiao Moxian’s source blood energy and also her True Phoenix blood essence!

In the past, one could see how precious phoenix blood essence was from how much the Ancient Phoenix Clan treasured just a single drop. And, the Ancient Phoenix Clan’s phoenix blood essence came from the dead body of a phoenix, drawn out using a secret technique. That blood essence had been preserved for countless years and was far inferior to Xiao Moxian’s phoenix blood essence in terms of purity; her phoenix blood essence was brimming with life!

Moreover, the Ancient Phoenix Clan’s phoenix blood essence had come from the corpse of a phoenix that was thousands of miles long. That phoenix corpse had a tremendous amount of blood essence within it, so how could a single drop of that compare to the pure and highly condensed phoenix blood essence within Xiao Moxian?

A phoenix that underwent nine stages of nirvana could burn their blood essence infinitely without damaging their life source at all. But, this was restricted to burning their blood essence. If they were to give their blood essence to others, that would be a permanent loss, one that was extremely difficult to recover from!

This could be said to be Xiao Moxian’s most precious thing. It was what the countless individuals who tried to obtain her body considered to be the most valuable treasure!

But now, Xiao Moxian was directly giving this phoenix blood essence to Lin Ming to stabilize the two violent yang energies within him.

“Ji Xian’er!”

Lin Ming anxiously shouted out. If Xiao Moxian gave him her blood essence then not only would this affect her current cultivation but also her future lifespan and achievements!

Hearing Lin Ming’s shouting, Xiao Moxian opened her eyes. Her pupils were dark like the bottom of a lake, as cold as an iceberg.

“Why are you doing this? This kindness is too heavy.” Lin Ming was unable to shoulder this burden. “If you give me your life’s most precious blood essence, then even if I break through to the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace it will still injure your life source and cause permanent damage to your cultivation. How will I have the face to stand tall in this world?”

The blood essence in Xiao Moxian’s body was no trifling matter.

A martial artist with a weaker cultivation could restore their lost blood essence without much difficulty. But for someone like Xiao Moxian, her blood essence could be called that of the highest grade within the entire Divine Realm. Once she lost her blood essence then restoring it would be incomparably hard, a journey filled with endless hardships.

Listening to Lin Ming’s words, Xiao Moxian lightly sighed. “We both might die here. If you don’t break through to the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, do you think I will still live on?”

Speaking to here, she seemed to suddenly remember something. She said in an extremely quiet voice, “In the future, won’t you and I be mortal enemies? If I give my blood essence to you and discard my own bloodline, then my grandfather and the Monster Emperor will have no need for me to become the future ruler of their two races. Then, I’ll have saved you the trouble of having to fight with me. Isn’t that just wonderful?”

Chapter 1531 – Crimson Space

Lin Ming’s breakthrough was originally defying the heavens’ will to forcefully change one’s life. To break through the chains of the Heavenly Dao was indescribably difficult. Even though Lin Ming’s mortal bodily foundation had reached this degree of tempering, he still only had a 10% chance of succeeding. Finally, he still had to rely on absorbing Xiao Moxian’s phoenix blood essence in order to have some hopes of succeeding.

In this sort of situation, Lin Ming simply wasn’t able to tolerate any interference.

And Tian Mingzi was doing things to the extreme; he didn’t want to give Lin Ming even the smallest chance of rising back up. Even if he had to desperately damage his blood vitality and affect his future cultivation, he still wouldn’t hesitate!

“Lin Ming, your life is too resilient. You being my enemy is a challenge to my own destiny, the most dangerous risk! I will stop at nothing in order to kill you, today is the day you die!”

Ever since ancient times, those who dared to oppose extraordinary individuals with great destinies always had to face enormous risks. Not to mention the world of martial artists, even in the mortal world, those emperors that founded their own kingdoms would have to face countless assassination attempts as they tried to rule the world. And in the end, all of those assassins would fail!

Tian Mingzi crazily raved. Not only did he use his heart demon technique but he also attacked Primordius Heavenly Palace at the same time, causing the entire Heavenly Palace to tremble!

If Primordius Heavenly Palace trembled, that would inevitably cause the energy around Lin Ming to become chaotic. Moreover, with the addition of the ghostly illusion energy, all of this caused Lin Ming to have even more difficulties in his breakthrough.

“Hah!”

Lin Ming’s eyes were red with rage. He roared out loud as his fist smashed out. Swathes of illusions were shattered by his fist, but when this fist reached the nine star dao diagram it had already weakened by a great deal. Finally, it only tore open an infinitesimally small part of the dao diagram, one not even worthy of mentioning.

Not just this, but the nine star dao diagram slowly regenerated. If Lin Ming couldn’t tear open the nine star dao diagram then the result would be defeat!

If his breakthrough failed then Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian would both die!

“Lin Ming!”

In Primordius Heavenly Palace, Xiao Moxian was anxious. She continued to hold Lin Ming’s hand. Because she had consumed her source blood vitality, her face was pale as if she were sick.

She grit her teeth, opening her lips wide once again to pass more of her phoenix blood essence to Lin Ming.

At this time, Xiao Moxian’s smooth and soft arms and body were weightless, as if she would fall into Lin Ming’s embrace at any moment.

In the dark void, Lin Ming was concerned as he felt the pure strength of Xiao Moxian’s phoenix blood essence enter him. She had already used up a great deal of her blood essence. If she were to use up any more then the damage would be inconceivable!

“Ji Xian’er, do not pass me the energy of your blood vitality!”

Lin Ming shouted out, but Xiao Moxian didn’t stop at all. Lin Ming became increasingly anxious. “Ji Xian’er, even if you pass me your phoenix blood essence it will only allow the two yang energies within my body to achieve yin yang harmony, but I actually cannot fuse them. With Tian Mingzi disturbing me, I won’t be able to break through the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace like this!”

Lin Ming was burning with impatience, his eyes widened to the point of cracking. There was too much weighing down on his shoulders and yet he couldn’t fulfill his promise.

He hated himself. He was unwilling!

“Break for me!”

Lin Ming roared out loud, his entire body releasing explosive crackling sounds. He burned the Gate of Life’s blood essence without regard for the consequences in exchange for strength that he could barely control. The meridians all throughout his body began to tear apart.

Celestial Tyrant Manual – Hundred Layered Waves!

Lin Ming’s fist punched out through burning his life to the limit. His strike smashed through the illusions and crashed into the nine star dao diagram, causing a shocking gap to be ripped open!

However, as Lin Ming tore through the nine star dao diagram, he could sense infinite ghosts and illusions swell up from all around him, attacking his innermost feelings! The fiercer Lin Ming’s attack was, the more energy he released and the more emotional his heart was, making it much easier to experience a backlash of his heart demons.

Puff!

Lin Ming spat out a mouthful of blood. His vision dimmed and he was sent flying backwards.

Kacha! Kacha!

The nine star illusions shattered and Lin Ming’s consciousness was ejected into the endless void. Like this, his breakthrough had already reached the brink of failure!

Outside of Primordius Heavenly Palace, Tian Mingzi had also realized this point. He devilishly grinned.

Although he couldn’t see what was happening inside of Primordius Heavenly Palace, he could extrapolate what was occurring from the starlight outside that suddenly dimmed down.

“Nearly 20 years of grudges will be brought to completion today!”

Tian Mingzi lifted his grievously wounded body and bit down on his tongue, taking out a wisp of blood essence. He wet his finger with this blood essence and began to draw a scarlet blood symbol in the air!

Curse of the Demon Heart!

Peng!

As this curse seal landed on Primordius Heavenly Palace’s array formation, Lin Ming shook like he had been struck and began to fall down.

“Lin Ming!”

Seeing Lin Ming fall down, Xiao Moxian felt like someone had violently gripped her heart. She stretched out her delicate arms, embracing Lin Ming against her chest.

Xiao Moxian’s front was dyed red with blood. Lin Ming felt as if he had fallen into a bath of warm and fragrant incense; all he could smell was the fresh virgin scent of beauty.

He opened his eyes. What he saw was Xiao Moxian’s pale face and her two eyes filled with tears.

Xiao Moxian tightly held onto Lin Ming. At this moment, it was like only the two of them existed in this world. At their time of death, they could still lean upon each other.

“If we die here, will you regret it?” Xiao Moxian asked, her whispering lips close to Lin Ming’s ear.

Lin Ming’s nearly torn open eyes revealed a rare tenderness in this moment. He gently shook his head.

At this time, it was like all the sounds of the world had fallen far away.

Xiao Moxian suddenly cried, large drops of tears falling down her cheeks. “At the precipice of death, when someone is accompanying you, dying doesn’t seem as scary as it should. But Lin Ming, I don’t want you to die. I will give you my everything… and when you break through the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace and escape from here, you will live on for a billion years, a trillion years, and my blood will always follow you!”

As Xiao Moxian said this, she seemed to affirm a great determination. She wrapped her hands around Lin Ming’s head and bent down over him, deeply kissing him.

Two pairs of warm lips brought with them a hint of blood as they touched together.

In that instant, time seemed to come to a standstill. In the endless starry skies, Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian hugged each other, dark enchanting blood red flowers seeming to bloom all around them.

That charming moment nearly made Lin Ming fall into intoxication. However, he soon awakened from this drunken state and discovered that as Xiao Moxian was kissing him, she was pouring all of her phoenix blood essence through this kiss, as if she wanted him to inherit every last drop within her body!

Once she did this, she would perish like broken jade!

“You…”

Lin Ming wanted to shove Xiao Moxian away, but she had tightly latched onto him, not releasing him no matter how much he struggled.

“No… don’t do this!”

Lin Ming passed a sound transmission on with difficulty. “Even if you give me all of your blood essence… I cannot fuse with it so soon… and if it's just bringing those two yang energies into harmony, the blood vitality you passed me before was more than enough!”

Even if Xiao Moxian poured all of her phoenix blood essence into Lin Ming, he still wouldn’t be able to directly absorb it like that. When Lin Ming absorbed the bone of an Azure Dragon in the past, he had consumed a great deal of strength to do so. Although his cultivation was far higher than it was back then, Xiao Moxian’s phoenix blood essence was hundreds and thousands of times purer than the strength of the Azure Dragon within him.

“Can’t fuse? Then I’ll fuse with you!”

Xiao Moxian’s kiss became increasingly intense and fiery. Her body seemed to melt into his, joining together with him as one.

As blood vitality continued streaming into him, Lin Ming was becoming increasingly restless. Raising up his wounded body, he tried to push Xiao Moxian away, but in the chaos and confusion of the moment, he felt his hands shoving against an indescribable softness.

Looking down, Lin Ming could see that his hands were pressed onto Xiao Moxian’s womanly peaks. The two solid peaks on her chest were pushed down by Lin Ming, containing a wondrous bounciness.

In that moment, Xiao Moxian groaned and her body trembled. She wanted to move back but her body instinctively softened, falling into Lin Ming as if she had no more strength left within her.

Her face was lit with a sunset glow illuminating the dappled waters. Her two hands wound up like snakes, winding around Lin Ming’s neck as she affectionately kissed him. Her small red tongue roamed about, sucking on Lin Ming’s everything.

In this time, a strength beyond description passed between their lips and spread to Lin Ming’s limbs and bones. This strength was different from the phoenix blood essence that Xiao Moxian had fed to him, but its degree of purity was no less than her source blood essence. And most importantly, this strength wasn’t blocked from fusing together with Lin Ming. Their two bodies seemed to melt together as one. This was Xiao Moxian’s primordial yin energy. When she offered it freely without reserve, her aura was easily able to fuse with Lin Ming.

For a time, Lin Ming was overcome with chaotic sentiments. His heart filled with the fires of desire. He wanted to press Xiao Moxian beneath his body and wildly make love to her!

She was a perfect woman of the world and carried with her an indescribable gentleness and sharp mind. Even though Lin Ming’s goal was to chase after the peak of martial arts and he had cultivated to the point of having a mind as still as water, it was still impossible for him to prevent the heated feelings growing in his heart.

However, Lin Ming still maintained a trace of clarity in his mind. He was deeply aware of what the word responsibility meant. His union with Xiao Moxian was something that the demon race and monster race would not permit no matter what, and if he took her primordial yin then this would cause a tremendous impact on her future.

The future… was an unknown. In fulfilling the desires of today, they might have to trade it for a painful consequence in the future.

‘I'm married…” Lin Ming said, finding it hard to say.

“And so what?” Xiao Moxian’s body suddenly shook. She slowly separated from Lin Ming’s burning hot lips. She faced him, just several inches away, staring at his face, her eyes so pure that no one would want to injure her.

Lin Ming was at a loss for how to respond.

“I am not looking for some ending with you, nor do I have any hope that I will be together with you in the future. I just want to kiss you, simply give you my body. Isn’t that something you want?”

Xiao Moxian’s voice trembled as she spoke. The tears in her eyes shined, sparkling as they tumbled downwards like little motes of starlight.

With a soft touch, Xiao Moxian’s tears fell onto Lin Ming’s face as they broke apart like shattered crystals.

At this time, Lin Ming was dazed.